<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bass Players on Musicant Family Brain</title>
    <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/tags/bass-players/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bass Players on Musicant Family Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://musicantfamilybrain.info/tags/bass-players/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Did Bootsy Collins pass away?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bootsy-collins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bootsy-collins/</guid>
      <description>How did Bootsy Collins get his name? Collins was born in Cincinnati, Ohio, on October 26, 1951. He said that his mother named him &amp;ldquo;Bootsy&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;I asked her why,&amp;rdquo; he explained to a journalist, &amp;ldquo;and she just said, &amp;lsquo;Because you looked like a Bootsy. &amp;rsquo; I left it at that.&amp;rdquo;
Is Bootsy Collins related to Snoop Dogg? COLLINS: My nephew Snoop.May 27, 2011
Who is William Bootsy Collins? William “Bootsy” Collins (born October 26, 1951 in Cincinnati, Ohio) is a funk bassist, singer, and songwriter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Donald Duck Dunn play with Eric Clapton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/donald-duck-dunn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/donald-duck-dunn/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Donald Duck Dunn? Death. On the morning of May 13, 2012, Dunn died in his sleep after finishing his fifth double show at the Blue Note nightclub in Tokyo with Cropper the night before. He had been in Japan as part of an ongoing tour with Cropper and Eddie Floyd.
Who did Donald Duck Dunn play with? Donald Dunn/Music groups
Did Donald Duck Dunn play with Elvis?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Jack Casady play with Jimi Hendrix?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-casady/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-casady/</guid>
      <description>Are there any original members left in Jefferson Starship? True to its legacy, the members have changed over time, but the heart and the magic of all those hits remain. Paul Kantner died in 2016. Currently, the Jefferson Starship lineup features founding member David Freiberg, along with Donny Baldwin, Jude Gold, Cathy Richardson, and Chris Smith.
Is Grace Slick Still Alive 2021? Grace Slick, seen here being inducted into L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Marcus Miller play with Michael Jackson?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcus-miller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcus-miller/</guid>
      <description>Is Marcus Miller a good bass guitar? Marcus Miller partnered with Sire to bring high quality basses to players who didn&amp;rsquo;t have multi-thousands of dollars to drop on a great bass. I&amp;rsquo;m fortunate to have added a number of great basses to my own collection over several decades including Fender Precisions, Fender Jazzes and Rickenbackers.Sep 22, 2020
Who makes Marcus Miller bass? Sire Guitars
What bass does Marcus Miller use?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Pink Floyd play Tony Levin?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-levin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-levin/</guid>
      <description>Who has Tony Levin played with? A prolific session musician since the 1970s, Levin has played on five hundred albums, including those of Cher, Alice Cooper, John Lennon, Sarah McLachlan, Stevie Nicks, Pink Floyd, Lou Reed, Buddy Rich, The Roches, Todd Rundgren, Seal, and Yes.
Who was John Lennon&amp;rsquo;s best friend? Pete Shotton
What did John Lennon say about paul mccartney&amp;rsquo;s bass playing? “He was coy about his bass playing,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Nathan East have perfect pitch?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nathan-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nathan-east/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass with Eric Clapton? Nathan East
Did Eric Clapton play the drums? ERIC CLAPTON AND HIS BAND I (April 1974 - June 1979) Eric Clapton (guitar/vocals), George Terry (guitar), Dick Sims (organ), Carl Radle (bass), Jamie Oldaker (drums), and Yvonne Elliman (vocals).
Why is Steve Gadd so good? He foretold the &amp;rsquo;80s by introducing a super-precision into recording, almost as if preparing drummers for the arrival of the drum machine and sequenced tracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How good is Abraham Laboriel?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/abraham-laboriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/abraham-laboriel/</guid>
      <description>Who was Paul McCartney&amp;rsquo;s touring drummer? Abraham Laboriel Jr.
How long has Abe Laboriel Jr played with Paul McCartney? Laboriel has been playing with McCartney for over 20 years, and he&amp;rsquo;s one of the most highly respected percussionists in the world. We&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at Laboriel&amp;rsquo;s drumming style, what makes him such a remarkable musician, as well as a bit about the whole Paul McCartney band and their career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many children does Aston Family Man Barrett have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/aston-family-man-barrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/aston-family-man-barrett/</guid>
      <description>What did Carlton W Barrett do to get a Medal of Honor? Medal of Honor citation For gallantry and intrepidity at the risk of his life above and beyond the call of duty on 6 June 1944, in the vicinity of St. Laurent-sur-Mer, France. On the morning of D-day Pvt. Barrett, landing in the face of extremely heavy enemy fire, was forced to wade ashore through neck-deep water.
What did Carlton W Barrett do to get a Medal of Honor?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many people has Lemmy slept with?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lemmy-kilmister/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lemmy-kilmister/</guid>
      <description>What is the name of the theme song on Queen sugar? First Look: &amp;ldquo;My Soul&amp;rsquo;s High Song&amp;rdquo;
Who sings the opening song to Queen sugar? Meshell Ndegeocello on Scoring Ava DuVernay&amp;rsquo;s New OWN Series &amp;lsquo;Queen Sugar&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp; Reviving Her Past. Before Meshell Ndegeocello signed on to score Queen Sugar, the new Ava DuVernay-created drama on OWN about three Louisiana siblings who reunite to run their father&amp;rsquo;s sugarcane farm, she and the Selma…Sep 6, 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Will Lee Sesame Street?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-lee/</guid>
      <description>Who has passed away from Sesame Street? actor Emilio Delgado
What happened to Mr. Hooper on Sesame Street? Hooper, the storekeeper on &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Sesame Street,&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; since the children&amp;rsquo;s program went on the air 13 years ago, died of a heart attack Tuesday night at Lenox Hill Hospital. He was 74 years old.Dec 9, 1982
When did Mr. Hooper died on Sesame Street? December 7, 1982
Who does Lee marry in Boruto?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Anthony Jackson related to Michael Jackson?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/anthony-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/anthony-jackson/</guid>
      <description>What kind of bass does Anthony Jackson play? From 1982 onwards Jackson almost exclusively played a contrabass guitar. Prior to 1982 his main instruments included a 1973 Fender Precision Bass, a 1973 Fender Jazz bass fitted with a 1975 Precision neck, and a Gibson EB-2D bass.
Who plays Jackson bass? Alex Al, Jackson&amp;rsquo;s bassist since 2001 and a member of the seven-piece band featured in the film, concurs. “Bass was the most important instrument to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Billy Sheehan a good bassist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-sheehan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-sheehan/</guid>
      <description>Who played Mr. Big&amp;rsquo;s guitar? Guitarist Paul Gilbert departed the band in 1999, and Richie Kotzen was brought as a guitarist and vocalist. The band released two more albums with this line-up: Get Over It (1999) and Actual Size (2001). Mr. Big disbanded in 2002.
Who is in the band Mr. Big? Mr. Big/Members
Who is Paul Gilbert guitar? Paul Brandon Gilbert is an American hard rock and heavy metal guitarist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Charlie Haden alive?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-haden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-haden/</guid>
      <description>Which bassist was responsible for the harmony in the Ornette Coleman Quartet? Charles Edward Haden (August 6, 1937 – July 11, 2014) was an American jazz double bass player, bandleader, composer and educator whose career spanned more than 50 years. In the late 1950s, he was an original member of the ground-breaking Ornette Coleman Quartet. Shenandoah, Iowa, U.S.
What was Charlie Haden&amp;rsquo;s musical role as the bass player in Ornette Coleman&amp;rsquo;s group?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Dave Holland dead?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-holland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-holland/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dave Holland? Dave Holland, Judas Priest&amp;rsquo;s drummer during their commercial peak in the Eighties, died at the age of 69. He had been living in exile in A Fonsagrada, Spain after being convicted of the attempted rape of a 17-year-old boy and subsequently serving a sentence in prison.Jan 25, 2018
What strings does Dave Holland use? Dave Holland uses Michael Tobias Design Bass Guitars, Thomastik-Infeld Bass Strings, LaBella Bass Guitar Strings and Gallien-Krueger Speakers and Amplifiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Drake related to Larry Graham?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-graham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-graham/</guid>
      <description>How long has Larry Graham been married? 41 years
Is Larry Graham Drake&amp;rsquo;s uncle? Larry Graham Jr. In 1993, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Sly and the Family Stone. He is also the uncle of rapper Drake.
Who invented bass slapping? Larry Graham
What happened to Sly from Sly and the Family Stone? Sly Stone, one of the pioneers of funk music as mastermind for Sly and the Family Stone, is now homeless and living out of a white van in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is John Deacon still friends with Queen?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-deacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-deacon/</guid>
      <description>Does John Deacon still get royalties? The 2018 biopic is still bringing in royalties for Brian May, Roger Taylor and John Deacon.Jul 5, 2021
Who is the richest member of Queen? So, what is the net worth of Brian May? As of 2022, the net worth of Brian May is $210 million. Brian May is the richest Queen member.Oct 24, 2021
What is Mary Austins net worth? Mary Austin net worth: Mary Austin is an English woman who has a net worth of $115 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Les Claypool a redneck?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/les-claypool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/les-claypool/</guid>
      <description>Who performs the Seinfeld theme song? Seinfeld/Artists
Did Les Claypool play the Seinfeld theme? TIL the Seinfeld Theme was played by Les Claypool.
Who is the bass player on Seinfeld theme? Jonathan Wolff
Does Primus still get royalties from South Park? But when South Park went to syndication in 2005 and Matt got to review their deals again, they increased the royalties for Primus members to what they deserved.May 6, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Les Claypool a redneck?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oscar-pettiford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oscar-pettiford/</guid>
      <description>Who performs the Seinfeld theme song? Seinfeld/Artists
Did Les Claypool play the Seinfeld theme? TIL the Seinfeld Theme was played by Les Claypool.
Who is the bass player on Seinfeld theme? Jonathan Wolff
Does Primus still get royalties from South Park? But when South Park went to syndication in 2005 and Matt got to review their deals again, they increased the royalties for Primus members to what they deserved.May 6, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Mike Watt a good bass player?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-watt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-watt/</guid>
      <description>What Bass does Mike Watt use? Watt states on his site that he uses a 1956 Fender Precision bass.
What AMP does Khruangbin use? Fender &amp;lsquo;68 Custom Deluxe Reverb Guitar Amplifier.
What AMP does Mark Speer use? When Khruangbin record, Speer uses a Fender Deluxe Reverb “blackface” and when they go on the road he brings a Fender &amp;lsquo;68 Custom Deluxe Reverb “silverface” reissue. Both are fantastic and powerful tube amps with their Fender-typical spring reverb and a tube vibrato effect, which Speer clearly likes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Paul Jackson married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass on thrust? Paul Jackson
Who played on Head Hunters? In 1973, the band comprised Hancock (keyboards), Bennie Maupin (saxophone, clarinet), Harvey Mason (drums), Paul Jackson (bass), and Bill Summers (percussion). Their first album, Head Hunters, sold more than one million copies.
Is Paul Jackson married? He had one son from that marriage, LaFura Eguchi Jackson, who was born in 1975 and died of cancer in 2000. Jackson&amp;rsquo;s second marriage was to Akiko Suzuki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Peter Hook the best bassist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-hook/</guid>
      <description>Where does Peter Hook live now? Home. I live in Alderley Edge, just south of Manchester.Sep 24, 2011
Where does Peter Hook live now? Home. I live in Alderley Edge, just south of Manchester.Sep 24, 2011
Is Peter Hook still in New Order? Peter Hook has reflected on his last gig with New Order 15 years ago, calling it the “most miserable night of my life”. Hook played his final show with his former Joy Division bandmates in Argentina on November 18, 2006, and discusses the experience in the new mini-documentary The Peter Hook Signature Collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Thundercat in Book of Boba?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hadrien-feraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hadrien-feraud/</guid>
      <description>Are ThunderCats real? ThunderCats is an American media franchise, featuring a fictional group of catlike humanoid aliens.
Is Snarf a cat? In the 2011 cartoon, Snarf is the devoted cat-like pet of Lion-O. Unlike his predecessor, Snarf is primarily quadruped and does not speak beyond the occasional murmured word, although later episodes do feature him making his characteristic &amp;ldquo;SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise, and on occasion &amp;ldquo;SNARFITY-SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise.
What was the name of the female ThunderCat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Thundercat in Book of Boba?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stephen-thundercat-bruner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stephen-thundercat-bruner/</guid>
      <description>Are ThunderCats real? ThunderCats is an American media franchise, featuring a fictional group of catlike humanoid aliens.
Is Snarf a cat? In the 2011 cartoon, Snarf is the devoted cat-like pet of Lion-O. Unlike his predecessor, Snarf is primarily quadruped and does not speak beyond the occasional murmured word, although later episodes do feature him making his characteristic &amp;ldquo;SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise, and on occasion &amp;ldquo;SNARFITY-SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise.
What was the name of the female ThunderCat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Victor Wooten related to Bobby Wooten?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-wooten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-wooten/</guid>
      <description>Does Victor Wooten have a brother? Victor Wooten/Brothers
How many brothers does Victor Wooten have? five Wooten brothers
Where are the Wooten brothers from? He&amp;rsquo;s known as &amp;lsquo;The Teacha&amp;rsquo; because, when the Wooten lads were young tykes milling restlessly around their home in Hawaii, it is rumored to have been Regi who started it all. Beginning on a brokedown ukelele and progressing to an electric guitar, Regi taught himself and then his brothers all about The Funk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Wood Harris and Steve Harris brothers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gary-willis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gary-willis/</guid>
      <description>Who is the current lead singer of Iron Maiden? Iron Maiden/Lead singers
Who replaced Adrian Smith in Iron Maiden? Janick Gers
Why did Bruce Dickinson leave Iron Maiden? After the Fear of the Dark Tour, Dickinson decided to leave Iron Maiden to concentrate on his solo career. At that point the band had already booked a following tour in 1993, which Dickinson did not enjoy.
Why did Iron Maiden add a third guitarist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Wood Harris and Steve Harris brothers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-harris/</guid>
      <description>Who is the richest member of Iron Maiden? As of October 2022, The net worth of Bruce Dickinson is $130 million, which makes him the richest Iron Maiden member.Oct 31, 2021
How much is Iron Maiden net worth? The band has sold over 100 million copies of their entire albums worldwide and received countless successes. As of 2022, Iron Maiden&amp;rsquo;s net worth is $100 million. With this, Iron Maiden is the third richest metal band in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What album did Justin Chancellor join Tool?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/justin-chancellor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/justin-chancellor/</guid>
      <description>Should bass players use a pick? You can use a pick on your bass guitar if you want to. Both finger plucking and using picks are perfectly normal ways to play the bass guitar. You can find plenty of examples of famous bassists who use either technique, and there is no harm to using a pick. It won&amp;rsquo;t damage your strings or create an inferior sound.
Do most bassists use picks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What band was Bobby Vega in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-laswell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-laswell/</guid>
      <description>Do guitars and basses use the same picks? Bass players generally use thicker picks. The thickness improves the bass playing control, and the overall tone of the string. The average pick thickness for bass players is 1.17 mm, while for guitar players is 0.89 mm. Remember, bass strings are much thicker than guitar strings.
Do you need picks for bass guitar? Truthfully, there is no right or wrong way to play a bass guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What band was Bobby Vega in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-vega/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-vega/</guid>
      <description>Who has Bobby Vega played with? In addition to his stellar career as a sideman, Bobby has been a member and co-founder of several of the Bay Area&amp;rsquo;s finest all-star collaborations, including Zero, KVHW, the Avalon Allstars, and Don&amp;rsquo;t Push the Clown; he continues to work with Zero/KVHW guitarist Steve Kimock in various situations.Oct 24, 2011
What size pick does Bobby Vega use? I get the most sounds with a medium; my main pick is a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What bass did Paul Chambers play?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-chambers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-chambers/</guid>
      <description>Who did Paul Chambers play with? Paul Chambers/Music groups
Who has Paul Chambers bass? Although Paul Chambers&amp;rsquo; bass work was firmly rooted in the East Coast scene of bop and modal jazz for most of his career, he does appear on several of the great cool records of the day too. This is one example: joining Chet, Johnny Griffin &amp;amp; Al Haig alongside his longtime rhythm section colleague Philly Joe Jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did Chris Squire of Yes died from?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-squire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-squire/</guid>
      <description>Who is the richest guitar player? Paul McCartney
How did Chris Squire get his bass sound? He cited Paul McCartney, Jack Bruce, and Bill Wyman as influences, but it was the Who&amp;rsquo;s John Entwistle that lit Squire up the most. He emulated Entwistle&amp;rsquo;s trebly roundwound sound, filtering it through his own intuition and the keen ear for classical harmony he had developed as a young choir singer.Jan 8, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What ethnicity is Esperanza Spalding?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/esperanza-spalding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/esperanza-spalding/</guid>
      <description>What is Esperanza Spalding known for? Esperanza Emily Spalding (born October 18, 1984) is an American bassist, singer, songwriter, and composer. Her accolades include five Grammy Awards, a Boston Music Award, and a Soul Train Music Award.
How did Esperanza Spalding become famous? &amp;ldquo;Esperanza,&amp;rdquo; her 2008 album, spent more than 70 weeks on the Billboard Contemporary Jazz chart and was the most successful internationally selling debut that year. She recorded her first album, &amp;ldquo;Junjo,&amp;rdquo; in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Grateful Dead songs did Phil Lesh write?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-lesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-lesh/</guid>
      <description>When did Phil Lesh have his liver transplant? Lesh has first-hand knowledge of the benefits of organ donation. After years of living with Hepatitis C, he underwent liver transplant surgery in December 1998.Aug 2, 2002
Why did Phil Lesh get a liver transplant? The party was cut short by Lesh&amp;rsquo;s near-fatal brush with hepatitis C, which had irreparably damaged his liver and sent him into the hospital later that year for liver transplant surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Bob Babbitt?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-babbitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-babbitt/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass on Motown Records? Jamerson was not Motown&amp;rsquo;s only bassist in those early years. Other early Motown bassists include Clarence Isabell, Tweed Beard, Willie Green, and Joe Williams (see, Slutsky, Standing, 12); in later years, bassists Tony Newton and Bob Babbitt recorded for Motown in Detroit as well.
Who played bass on Tears of a Clown? Bob Babbitt, the Motown studio bassist who played on hits including Smokey Robinson &amp;amp; the Miracles&amp;rsquo; “Tears of a Clown” and the Temptations&amp;rsquo; “Ball of Confusion,” died yesterday in Nashville after suffering complications from brain cancer, his spokesperson confirmed to Rolling Stone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Mick Karn?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-moore/</guid>
      <description>What was Japan&amp;rsquo;s biggest hit? Ghosts
Who is Yuka Fujii? Photographer, curator. Based in London, England. The majority of Yuka&amp;rsquo;s activities are based in that vast but ambiguous area where the visual arts, design, and music cross over.
What happened to the Japanese band move? On December 7, 2012, the band announced on their official website that, after a stint of 15 years, they will disband after their last live performance on March 16, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Mick Karn?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-karn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-karn/</guid>
      <description>What was Japan&amp;rsquo;s biggest hit? Ghosts
Who is Yuka Fujii? Photographer, curator. Based in London, England. The majority of Yuka&amp;rsquo;s activities are based in that vast but ambiguous area where the visual arts, design, and music cross over.
What happened to the Japanese band move? On December 7, 2012, the band announced on their official website that, after a stint of 15 years, they will disband after their last live performance on March 16, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Robbie Shakespeare?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/robbie-shakespeare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/robbie-shakespeare/</guid>
      <description>What happened Robbie Shakespeare? He was 68. Guillaume Bougard, a close friend and frequent collaborator, said the cause was complications of kidney and liver transplants. Starting in the mid-1970s, Mr. Shakespeare and the drummer Sly Dunbar were among the most prolific musicians in the business, reggae or otherwise.Feb 26, 2022
Did Robbie Shakespeare play for Bob Marley? Shakespeare, who died in Florida on December 8, is best known for being a member of famed drum and bass team, Sly and Robbie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Berry Oakley Jr?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/andrew-gouche/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/andrew-gouche/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dickey Betts now? For years now, Betts has lived in Sarasota County, just off the Highway 41 he sings about in the Allman Brothers&amp;rsquo; best known song.Dec 10, 2020
Who has died from the Allman Brothers Band? This feature was originally published in Classic Rock 57, in October 2003. Dan Toler died in 2011, Butch Trucks died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound in January 2017, and Gregg Allman passed away in June of the same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Berry Oakley Jr?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/berry-oakley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/berry-oakley/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dickey Betts now? For years now, Betts has lived in Sarasota County, just off the Highway 41 he sings about in the Allman Brothers&amp;rsquo; best known song.Dec 10, 2020
Who has died from the Allman Brothers Band? This feature was originally published in Classic Rock 57, in October 2003. Dan Toler died in 2011, Butch Trucks died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound in January 2017, and Gregg Allman passed away in June of the same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Berry Oakley Jr?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/eddie-gomez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/eddie-gomez/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dickey Betts now? For years now, Betts has lived in Sarasota County, just off the Highway 41 he sings about in the Allman Brothers&amp;rsquo; best known song.Dec 10, 2020
Who has died from the Allman Brothers Band? This feature was originally published in Classic Rock 57, in October 2003. Dan Toler died in 2011, Butch Trucks died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound in January 2017, and Gregg Allman passed away in June of the same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Francis Rocco Prestia?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/rocco-prestia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/rocco-prestia/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Francis Rocco Prestia? OAKLAND (CBS SF) &amp;ndash; Francis &amp;ldquo;Rocco&amp;rdquo; Prestia, the longtime bassist for Oakland funk pioneers Tower Of Power, died overnight Wednesday after a long battle with various illnesses, according to friends and family. He was 69.Sep 30, 2020
Who passed away from Tower of Power? — Rick Stevens, the former lead singer of Oakland&amp;rsquo;s Tower of Power rhythm and blues band who spent 36 years in prison, has died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Jack Bruce?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-bruce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-bruce/</guid>
      <description>Who did vocals for Cream? Jack Bruce
Who was the main singer in Cream? Cream/Members
Who was the lead singer of Cream? Jack Bruce
Who died from the band Cream? Ginger Baker
Who are the Cream band members? Cream/Members
What did Ginger Baker think of Eric Clapton? “Eric Clapton is probably my best friend,” Ginger says. “Him and Stevie Winwood. Eric is like my younger brother. I&amp;rsquo;m very proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Louis Johnson?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/louis-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/louis-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Which one of the Brothers Johnson are dead? Louis Johnson
Are the Brothers Johnson really brothers? The Los Angeles-based Brothers Johnson, a group featuring Louis and his brother George, got their start backing up Quincy Jones before releasing their acclaimed, Jones-produced debut LP Look Out for #1 in 1976.May 22, 2015
Is the group Brothers Johnson still alive? Funk and R&amp;amp;B bassist Louis Johnson died at age 60 on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Ron Baker?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leroy-slam-stewart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leroy-slam-stewart/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Ron Baker? After the Knicks waived Baker, he played briefly for the Wizards. He spent the 2019-20 season with CSKA Moscow. Now, the 28-year-old is moving onto the next stage of his life.Aug 26, 2021
Why is Ron Baker not in the NBA? Baker decided that it was time that he moved on in life and the physical strain on his body got to be too much for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Ron Baker?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-baker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-baker/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Ron Baker? After the Knicks waived Baker, he played briefly for the Wizards. He spent the 2019-20 season with CSKA Moscow. Now, the 28-year-old is moving onto the next stage of his life.Aug 26, 2021
Why is Ron Baker not in the NBA? Baker decided that it was time that he moved on in life and the physical strain on his body got to be too much for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to the bass player from Chic?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-edwards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-edwards/</guid>
      <description>What happened to the members of Chic? But “I&amp;rsquo;ll Be There” derives from decades-old Chic tapes only recently uncovered. Rodgers — the last surviving member of the original core trio — completed the song with a new lineup, as bassist Bernard Edwards died from pneumonia after playing a 1996 concert and drummer Tony Thompson was lost to cancer in 2003.Mar 21, 2015
Is Chic still alive? Chic was initially believed to have been killed by the Black Hood after Betty gave him up, but it was later revealed that Hal spared Chic and mentored him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to the bass player from Chic?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-berlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-berlin/</guid>
      <description>What happened to the members of Chic? But “I&amp;rsquo;ll Be There” derives from decades-old Chic tapes only recently uncovered. Rodgers — the last surviving member of the original core trio — completed the song with a new lineup, as bassist Bernard Edwards died from pneumonia after playing a 1996 concert and drummer Tony Thompson was lost to cancer in 2003.Mar 21, 2015
Is Chic still alive? Chic was initially believed to have been killed by the Black Hood after Betty gave him up, but it was later revealed that Hal spared Chic and mentored him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Victor Bailey?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-manring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-manring/</guid>
      <description>Where was Victor Bailey Jr? Victor Bailey Jr. - Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball - University of Tennessee Athletics.
Who is Victor Bailey? Victor Bailey, the virtuoso electric bassist and educator best known as the final bass player in Weather Report, following Jaco Pastorius, died on the morning of Nov. 11. He was 56, and had long suffered with Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease, essentially a form of muscular dystrophy that ran in his family.Nov 12, 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Victor Bailey?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-bailey/</guid>
      <description>Where was Victor Bailey Jr? Victor Bailey Jr. - Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball - University of Tennessee Athletics.
Who is Victor Bailey? Victor Bailey, the virtuoso electric bassist and educator best known as the final bass player in Weather Report, following Jaco Pastorius, died on the morning of Nov. 11. He was 56, and had long suffered with Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease, essentially a form of muscular dystrophy that ran in his family.Nov 12, 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Verdine White?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/george-porter-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/george-porter-jr/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Maurice White of Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Death. On the morning of February 4, 2016, White died in his sleep at his Los Angeles home from the effects of Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease. He was 74 years old. His brother Verdine said, &amp;ldquo;My brother, hero and best friend Maurice White passed away peacefully last night in his sleep.
Who recently died from Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Andrew Woolfolk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Verdine White?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/verdine-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/verdine-white/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Maurice White of Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Death. On the morning of February 4, 2016, White died in his sleep at his Los Angeles home from the effects of Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease. He was 74 years old. His brother Verdine said, &amp;ldquo;My brother, hero and best friend Maurice White passed away peacefully last night in his sleep.
Who recently died from Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Andrew Woolfolk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pino Palladino doing now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pino-palladino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pino-palladino/</guid>
      <description>What kind of strings does Pino Palladino use? Thomastik-Infeld Flatwound strings As already mentioned, Palladino&amp;rsquo;s use of flatwound strings has been a major component of his sound and Thomastik-Infeld are his preferred choice.May 24, 2017
What happened Pino Palladino? Palladino says he&amp;rsquo;s “not exactly crazy about touring any more” – he stopped playing live with the Who in 2016 – but is considering doing some gigs around Notes With Attachments, pandemic permitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Ray Brown known for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ray-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ray-brown/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Ella Fitzgerald husband? Webb died of spinal tuberculosis on June 16, 1939, and his band was renamed Ella and Her Famous Orchestra with Fitzgerald taking on the role of bandleader.
Who inherited Ella Fitzgerald estate? Richard Rosman, executor of the Fitzgerald estate, is particularly pleased that &amp;ldquo;memorabilia which really exemplifies Ella&amp;rsquo;s music and career is going to be at the Smithsonian and her music at the Library of Congress for all of America to enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the significance of Willie Dixon?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-dixon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-dixon/</guid>
      <description>What songs are Led Zeppelin accused of stealing? In 2010, American folk singer Jake Holmes sued Led Zeppelin for $1 million. Holmes claims that Jimmy Page stole his licks and lyrics for “Dazed and Confused,” perhaps the greatest tune on the Zep&amp;rsquo;s first album. Holmes says his version of the song was written in 1967, two years before Led Zeppelin&amp;rsquo;s.Nov 10, 2021
Did Led Zeppelin steal lemon song? The song&amp;rsquo;s titular &amp;ldquo;lemon&amp;rdquo; is also taken from another old blues song: Robert Johnson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Travelling Riverside Blues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What made James Jamerson so great?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-jamerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-jamerson/</guid>
      <description>What made James Jamerson so great? He had a very unique skill set that gave him the ability to create and execute bass lines and grooves like no other bass player had ever done before. That&amp;rsquo;s what gave James Jamerson his unique super power, and ultimately why he became one of the most game-changing bass players in the history of modern music.Nov 3, 2018
Who was the legendary bass player for the Funk Brothers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What makes RON CARTER a great bass player?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-carter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-carter/</guid>
      <description>Did RON CARTER ever play electric bass? Carter didn&amp;rsquo;t play much pure fusion, but he did record a bit on electric bass, for example on Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s Red Clay from 1970. Many of Carter&amp;rsquo;s own albums from the &amp;rsquo;70s on CTI and Milestone added strings, brass, and percussion, not to mention funk and even disco beats (Anything Goes, 1975).Mar 10, 2021
Who is the most recorded bassist? Carol Kaye (née Smith, born March 24, 1935) is an American musician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was Charles Mingus most famous for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charles-mingus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charles-mingus/</guid>
      <description>Where did Charles Mingus grow up? Los Angeles
Is Charles Mingus Chinese? Mingus Junior was largely raised in the Watts area of Los Angeles. His maternal grandfather was a Chinese British subject from Hong Kong, and his maternal grandmother was an African-American from the southern United States.
Where did Charles Mingus live? Charles Mingus/Places lived
What nationality is Charles Mingus? Charles Mingus, byname Charlie Mingus, (born April 22, 1922, Nogales, Arizona, U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What were Cliff Burton&#39;s last words?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cliff-burton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cliff-burton/</guid>
      <description>How old would Cliff Burton be today? Feb. 10, 2018 would have been Burton&amp;rsquo;s 56th birthday. The upcoming Cliff Burton Day would be his 60th birthday and a special livestream is scheduled for 7PM PT.Feb 8, 2022
What were Cliff Burton&amp;rsquo;s last words? After chatting for some time, Frank Bello and Cliff Burton separated saying maybe they will see each other the next day and the last word he heard from the late bassist was &amp;lsquo;Maybe I will&amp;rsquo; which makes them even more meaningful than usual since he left this world a few hours after saying these words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What were John Lennon&#39;s last words to Paul McCartney?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-mccartney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-mccartney/</guid>
      <description>Who is the wealthiest rock star in the world? Paul McCartney
Did Paul McCartney get along with George Harrison? More often than not, Harrison was concerned with spirituality and the internal struggles but on this track, he chose to put his feelings on the canvas and aim one directly as McCartney. Luckily, the two became close friends again before Harrison&amp;rsquo;s tragic death in 2001.Aug 20, 2021
What did Paul McCartney say about George Harrison?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When did Bill Black leave Elvis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-black/</guid>
      <description>How long did Bill Black play with Elvis? The Beatles discuss meeting Elvis When Elvis Presley first shot to fame in 1956 he had a trio called The Blue Moon Boys with guitarist Scotty Moore and bassist Bill Black. But less than 10 years later and Bill was dead. Having gone on to form the Bill Black Combo, the bassist became ill in the early 1960s.Oct 21, 2021
When did Bill Black leave Elvis?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When did Bill Black leave Elvis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/red-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/red-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Scotty Moore and Bill Black? Two musicians who have been with him since he started his singing career four years ago have quit in a pay dispute. Bill Black and Scotty Moore said they resigned Saturday, effective Sept. 21. Mr.Jan 9, 2012
Why did Scotty Moore leave Elvis band? While faring well with romance, Presley was having trouble with his business affairs. Two musicians who have been with him since he started his singing career four years ago have quit in a pay dispute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where do fleas originally come from?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/flea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/flea/</guid>
      <description>Are cat fleas visible to the human eye? Fleas are small flightless insects that can live on cats. They are dark brown in colour and are approximately 2-4mm in length so they are just visible to the naked eye. Although fleas cannot fly they jump from one place to another.
What is the actual size of a flea? The adult flea varies from about 0.1 to 0.32 cm (0.039 to 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where does Bakithi Kumalo live?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bakithi-kumalo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bakithi-kumalo/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass guitar for Michael Jackson? Louis Johnson (April 13, 1955 – May 21, 2015) was an American bass guitarist. Johnson was best known for his work with the group the Brothers Johnson and his session playing on several hit albums of the 1970s and 1980s, including the best-selling album of all time, Michael Jackson&amp;rsquo;s Thriller.
Who played bass on Jackson 5 albums? For starters, there&amp;rsquo;s been some debate on who actually played bass on the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where does Oteil Burbridge live now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oteil-burbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oteil-burbridge/</guid>
      <description>Who is playing bass for dead and Company? Burbridge
What Bass does Oteil Burbridge? Gibson EB-2 Bass Guitar &amp;ldquo;I bought this bass because it looked just like a Cherry Red Gibson ES-335 guitar that Mark Kimbrell played in my band, Oteil and the Peacemakers.
What does Oteil Burbridge? Oteil Burbridge is an American multi-instrumentalist, specializing on the bass guitar, trained in playing jazz and classical music from an early age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Carol Kaye today?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carol-kaye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carol-kaye/</guid>
      <description>Where is Carol Kaye now? Since 1969, Kaye&amp;rsquo;s shared her expertise via tutoring books — and today she&amp;rsquo;s a tech-savvy educator. “I&amp;rsquo;m teaching jazz on Skype because people worldwide want to learn real jazz,” she tells The Post, sounding almost giddy. “That&amp;rsquo;s great for me. I&amp;rsquo;m in it again, giving lessons in guitar and bass.”Jan 2, 2020
Where is Carol Kaye now? Since 1969, Kaye&amp;rsquo;s shared her expertise via tutoring books — and today she&amp;rsquo;s a tech-savvy educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michael Rhodes now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-rodriguez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-rodriguez/</guid>
      <description>Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Who has Michael Rhodes played with? As country music began to boom in the late 1980s, so did Rhodes&amp;rsquo; career as a session player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michael Rhodes now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-rhodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-rhodes/</guid>
      <description>Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Who has Michael Rhodes played with? As country music began to boom in the late 1980s, so did Rhodes&amp;rsquo; career as a session player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Stanley Clarke today?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stanley-clarke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stanley-clarke/</guid>
      <description>Who played drums on Stanley Clarke School Days? Gerry Brown
Who played guitar with Stanley Clarke? Stanley&amp;rsquo;s storied career includes a world tour with guitarist Jeff Beck (1979), collaborations with The Police drummer Stewart Copeland as part of Animal Logic with (two albums and tours in 1989) , the Superband (which included Larry Carlton, Billy Cobham, Najee and Deron Johnson, 1993-1994), The Rite of Strings (Jean- &amp;hellip;
Does Stanley Clarke have kids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who died from Vanilla Fudge?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stuart-hamm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stuart-hamm/</guid>
      <description>What songs did Vanilla Fudge make famous? The members of Vanilla Fudge were great admirers of the Beatles, and covered several of their songs including &amp;ldquo;Ticket to Ride&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Eleanor Rigby&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;You Can&amp;rsquo;t Do That&amp;rdquo;.
Is Vanilla Fudge in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame? “I&amp;rsquo;m in there because of my influence and what I&amp;rsquo;ve done for drumming. Long Island has a Music Hall Of Fame; Vanilla Fudge are in there for the same reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who died from Vanilla Fudge?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tim-bogert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tim-bogert/</guid>
      <description>Where does Carmine Appice live? New York
Is Carmine Appice a good drummer? Carmine&amp;rsquo;s career is exceptional if for no other reason than its longevity. He was the first rock drummer to appear alone on the cover of Modern Drummer magazine, in the April/June 1978 issue. Thirty years later, in April of 2007, he was the cover subject again.
Is Vanilla Fudge in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who has Leland Sklar played for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leland-sklar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leland-sklar/</guid>
      <description>Who is the bass player for Carole King and James Taylor? bassist Lee Sklar
Who is the bass player with the long beard? When it comes to session bassists, Leland Sklar is definitely one of those names. Instantly recognizable by his long white beard, he&amp;rsquo;s been an established presence on the L.A. scene for decades.Apr 2, 2018
Who played bass on sussudio? Leland Sklar
Who played Carole King&amp;rsquo;s guitar? Danny Kortchmar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who has Willie Weeks played with?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-weeks/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass on Donny Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s This Christmas? BP sez it&amp;rsquo;s Hathaway playing the piano bass with his left hand, Fender Rhodes with his right. 7 horn players &amp;amp; members of the Chicago Symphony are also mentioned. Is your version from the original album?Dec 9, 2017
Who performed this Christmas? Donny Hathaway
What floor did Donny Hathaway jump from? 15th floor
Where is Donny Hathaway today? On January 13th, 1979, his body was found outside New York&amp;rsquo;s Essex House below his 15th floor hotel room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is considered the father of the US Navy?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-paul-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-paul-jones/</guid>
      <description>What is John Paul Jones most known for? John Paul Jones (born John Paul; July 6, 1747 – July 18, 1792) was a Scottish-American naval captain who was the United States&amp;rsquo; first well-known naval commander in the American Revolutionary War.
Who was John Paul Jones and what was his significance in the war quizlet? John Paul Jones was a daring naval officer who was one of the war&amp;rsquo;s great heroes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Mark King Taco Bell?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-king/</guid>
      <description>How good a bass player was Mark King? Mark King grew up on the Isle Of Wight and moved to London with the aim of being a professional drummer. Instead he became one of the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest bass players, but his earlier ambition may explain his highly rhythmic slap bass style. Mark King rose to fame in the eighties as bassist and vocalist of Level 42.
Who is the best bass player in the world 2020?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Walter Page?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/percy-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/percy-jones/</guid>
      <description>What made the Count Basie big band unique for its time? Count Basie is considered one of the greatest bandleaders of all times. He was the arbiter of the big-band swing sound and his unique style of fusing blues and jazz established swing as a predominant music style.
What was Count Basie&amp;rsquo;s orchestra known for? From its inception, Basie&amp;rsquo;s band was well known for its outstanding rhythm section of Basie on piano, Freddie Green on guitar, Walter Page on bass, and &amp;ldquo;Papa&amp;rdquo; Jo Jones on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Walter Page?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/walter-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/walter-page/</guid>
      <description>What made the Count Basie big band unique for its time? Count Basie is considered one of the greatest bandleaders of all times. He was the arbiter of the big-band swing sound and his unique style of fusing blues and jazz established swing as a predominant music style.
What was Count Basie&amp;rsquo;s orchestra known for? From its inception, Basie&amp;rsquo;s band was well known for its outstanding rhythm section of Basie on piano, Freddie Green on guitar, Walter Page on bass, and &amp;ldquo;Papa&amp;rdquo; Jo Jones on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Elton John fire his band in 1975?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dee-murray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dee-murray/</guid>
      <description>Why did Elton John fire his band in 1975? They on world tours with John for several years. In 1975, after recording Captain Fantastic and the Brown Dirt Cowboy, Murray and Olsson were released from the band because John wanted to achieve a different sound. Murray and Olsson re-joined the band in 1980, starting with 21 at 33.
Who was Elton John&amp;rsquo;s bass player? Bob Birch, a bass player and prolific session sideman best known as a long-time member of Elton John&amp;rsquo;s band, died Wednesday of an apparent suicide at his home in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Geddy leave Rush?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geddy-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geddy-lee/</guid>
      <description>Is Geddy Lee still married? Lee supports many causes through personal and band donations. He is known as an avid baseball fan and wine connoisseur. Lee has been married to Nancy Young for over 35 years and they have 2 children.
Is Rush still performing? Rush ceased touring at the end of 2015, and Lifeson announced in January 2018 that the band would not continue. On January 7, 2020, Peart died of glioblastoma, a type of brain cancer, at the age of 67.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Geezer Butler called geezer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geezer-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geezer-butler/</guid>
      <description>Is Geezer Butler Irish? Roots notes. Geezer, who was born Terence Michael Joseph Butler in 1949, was raised in a large Anglo-Irish family in Aston and credits his background with giving him the will and tenacity to persevere with music. “I had a nice working-class upbringing; we never went without anything,” he explains.Sep 6, 2019
Did Ozzy Osbourne rejoin Black Sabbath? Ozzy Osbourne has reportedly rejoined the original line up of Black Sabbath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Richard Bona famous?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/doug-wimbish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/doug-wimbish/</guid>
      <description>Has Richard Bona won Grammy Award? One of these accomplished personalities, Grammy Award-winning Cameroonian bassist Richard Bona, will be making his way to India to speak at a TEDxGateway event on February 23rd at Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s NSCI Dome. Bona – who grew up in Minta – was surrounded by a family full of musicians.Feb 14, 2020
What nationality is Richard Bona? Richard Bona (born 28 October 1967) is a Cameroon-born American musician, multi-instrumentalist and vocalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Richard Bona famous?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/niels-henning-orsted-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/niels-henning-orsted-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>Has Richard Bona won Grammy Award? One of these accomplished personalities, Grammy Award-winning Cameroonian bassist Richard Bona, will be making his way to India to speak at a TEDxGateway event on February 23rd at Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s NSCI Dome. Bona – who grew up in Minta – was surrounded by a family full of musicians.Feb 14, 2020
What nationality is Richard Bona? Richard Bona (born 28 October 1967) is a Cameroon-born American musician, multi-instrumentalist and vocalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Richard Bona famous?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/richard-bona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/richard-bona/</guid>
      <description>Has Richard Bona won Grammy Award? One of these accomplished personalities, Grammy Award-winning Cameroonian bassist Richard Bona, will be making his way to India to speak at a TEDxGateway event on February 23rd at Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s NSCI Dome. Bona – who grew up in Minta – was surrounded by a family full of musicians.Feb 14, 2020
What nationality is Richard Bona? Richard Bona (born 28 October 1967) is a Cameroon-born American musician, multi-instrumentalist and vocalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Sting is called Sting?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sting/</guid>
      <description>What is Sting&amp;rsquo;s net worth? around $300 million
How did Sting get so rich? According to Celebrity Net Worth, Sting has an estimated net worth of $400 million. He has predominantly made this money through his work in the music industry, both with &amp;lsquo;Police&amp;rsquo; and as a solo artist. However, he has also made some of his fortunes through his acting career.
What&amp;rsquo;s Billy Joel&amp;rsquo;s net worth? But Joel&amp;rsquo;s total net worth is several times more than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why was Jaco Pastorius beaten to death?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jaco-pastorius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jaco-pastorius/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Jaco Pastorius that ended his life? Twenty years ago Friday, bassist Jaco Pastorius died in a Ft. Lauderdale, Fla., hospital as a result of injuries sustained during a fight in a local nightclub. He was 35.Sep 21, 2007
Was Jaco Pastorius a junkie? For a jazz musician, Jaco Pastorius died in pretty creditable rock n&amp;rsquo; roll style: drugs, delusions, alcohol and itinerancy.Aug 3, 2015
What was Jaco addicted to?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
