<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Musicant Family Brain</title>
    <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Musicant Family Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://musicantfamilybrain.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Did Bootsy Collins pass away?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bootsy-collins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bootsy-collins/</guid>
      <description>How did Bootsy Collins get his name? Collins was born in Cincinnati, Ohio, on October 26, 1951. He said that his mother named him &amp;ldquo;Bootsy&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;I asked her why,&amp;rdquo; he explained to a journalist, &amp;ldquo;and she just said, &amp;lsquo;Because you looked like a Bootsy. &amp;rsquo; I left it at that.&amp;rdquo;
Is Bootsy Collins related to Snoop Dogg? COLLINS: My nephew Snoop.May 27, 2011
Who is William Bootsy Collins? William “Bootsy” Collins (born October 26, 1951 in Cincinnati, Ohio) is a funk bassist, singer, and songwriter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Donald Duck Dunn play with Eric Clapton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/donald-duck-dunn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/donald-duck-dunn/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Donald Duck Dunn? Death. On the morning of May 13, 2012, Dunn died in his sleep after finishing his fifth double show at the Blue Note nightclub in Tokyo with Cropper the night before. He had been in Japan as part of an ongoing tour with Cropper and Eddie Floyd.
Who did Donald Duck Dunn play with? Donald Dunn/Music groups
Did Donald Duck Dunn play with Elvis?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Jack Casady play with Jimi Hendrix?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-casady/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-casady/</guid>
      <description>Are there any original members left in Jefferson Starship? True to its legacy, the members have changed over time, but the heart and the magic of all those hits remain. Paul Kantner died in 2016. Currently, the Jefferson Starship lineup features founding member David Freiberg, along with Donny Baldwin, Jude Gold, Cathy Richardson, and Chris Smith.
Is Grace Slick Still Alive 2021? Grace Slick, seen here being inducted into L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Marcus Miller play with Michael Jackson?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcus-miller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcus-miller/</guid>
      <description>Is Marcus Miller a good bass guitar? Marcus Miller partnered with Sire to bring high quality basses to players who didn&amp;rsquo;t have multi-thousands of dollars to drop on a great bass. I&amp;rsquo;m fortunate to have added a number of great basses to my own collection over several decades including Fender Precisions, Fender Jazzes and Rickenbackers.Sep 22, 2020
Who makes Marcus Miller bass? Sire Guitars
What bass does Marcus Miller use?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Pink Floyd play Tony Levin?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-levin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-levin/</guid>
      <description>Who has Tony Levin played with? A prolific session musician since the 1970s, Levin has played on five hundred albums, including those of Cher, Alice Cooper, John Lennon, Sarah McLachlan, Stevie Nicks, Pink Floyd, Lou Reed, Buddy Rich, The Roches, Todd Rundgren, Seal, and Yes.
Who was John Lennon&amp;rsquo;s best friend? Pete Shotton
What did John Lennon say about paul mccartney&amp;rsquo;s bass playing? “He was coy about his bass playing,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Nathan East have perfect pitch?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nathan-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nathan-east/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass with Eric Clapton? Nathan East
Did Eric Clapton play the drums? ERIC CLAPTON AND HIS BAND I (April 1974 - June 1979) Eric Clapton (guitar/vocals), George Terry (guitar), Dick Sims (organ), Carl Radle (bass), Jamie Oldaker (drums), and Yvonne Elliman (vocals).
Why is Steve Gadd so good? He foretold the &amp;rsquo;80s by introducing a super-precision into recording, almost as if preparing drummers for the arrival of the drum machine and sequenced tracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How good is Abraham Laboriel?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/abraham-laboriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/abraham-laboriel/</guid>
      <description>Who was Paul McCartney&amp;rsquo;s touring drummer? Abraham Laboriel Jr.
How long has Abe Laboriel Jr played with Paul McCartney? Laboriel has been playing with McCartney for over 20 years, and he&amp;rsquo;s one of the most highly respected percussionists in the world. We&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at Laboriel&amp;rsquo;s drumming style, what makes him such a remarkable musician, as well as a bit about the whole Paul McCartney band and their career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many children does Aston Family Man Barrett have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/aston-family-man-barrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/aston-family-man-barrett/</guid>
      <description>What did Carlton W Barrett do to get a Medal of Honor? Medal of Honor citation For gallantry and intrepidity at the risk of his life above and beyond the call of duty on 6 June 1944, in the vicinity of St. Laurent-sur-Mer, France. On the morning of D-day Pvt. Barrett, landing in the face of extremely heavy enemy fire, was forced to wade ashore through neck-deep water.
What did Carlton W Barrett do to get a Medal of Honor?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many people has Lemmy slept with?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lemmy-kilmister/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lemmy-kilmister/</guid>
      <description>What is the name of the theme song on Queen sugar? First Look: &amp;ldquo;My Soul&amp;rsquo;s High Song&amp;rdquo;
Who sings the opening song to Queen sugar? Meshell Ndegeocello on Scoring Ava DuVernay&amp;rsquo;s New OWN Series &amp;lsquo;Queen Sugar&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp; Reviving Her Past. Before Meshell Ndegeocello signed on to score Queen Sugar, the new Ava DuVernay-created drama on OWN about three Louisiana siblings who reunite to run their father&amp;rsquo;s sugarcane farm, she and the Selma…Sep 6, 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Will Lee Sesame Street?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-lee/</guid>
      <description>Who has passed away from Sesame Street? actor Emilio Delgado
What happened to Mr. Hooper on Sesame Street? Hooper, the storekeeper on &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Sesame Street,&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; since the children&amp;rsquo;s program went on the air 13 years ago, died of a heart attack Tuesday night at Lenox Hill Hospital. He was 74 years old.Dec 9, 1982
When did Mr. Hooper died on Sesame Street? December 7, 1982
Who does Lee marry in Boruto?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Anthony Jackson related to Michael Jackson?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/anthony-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/anthony-jackson/</guid>
      <description>What kind of bass does Anthony Jackson play? From 1982 onwards Jackson almost exclusively played a contrabass guitar. Prior to 1982 his main instruments included a 1973 Fender Precision Bass, a 1973 Fender Jazz bass fitted with a 1975 Precision neck, and a Gibson EB-2D bass.
Who plays Jackson bass? Alex Al, Jackson&amp;rsquo;s bassist since 2001 and a member of the seven-piece band featured in the film, concurs. “Bass was the most important instrument to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Billy Sheehan a good bassist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-sheehan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-sheehan/</guid>
      <description>Who played Mr. Big&amp;rsquo;s guitar? Guitarist Paul Gilbert departed the band in 1999, and Richie Kotzen was brought as a guitarist and vocalist. The band released two more albums with this line-up: Get Over It (1999) and Actual Size (2001). Mr. Big disbanded in 2002.
Who is in the band Mr. Big? Mr. Big/Members
Who is Paul Gilbert guitar? Paul Brandon Gilbert is an American hard rock and heavy metal guitarist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Charlie Haden alive?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-haden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-haden/</guid>
      <description>Which bassist was responsible for the harmony in the Ornette Coleman Quartet? Charles Edward Haden (August 6, 1937 – July 11, 2014) was an American jazz double bass player, bandleader, composer and educator whose career spanned more than 50 years. In the late 1950s, he was an original member of the ground-breaking Ornette Coleman Quartet. Shenandoah, Iowa, U.S.
What was Charlie Haden&amp;rsquo;s musical role as the bass player in Ornette Coleman&amp;rsquo;s group?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Dave Holland dead?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-holland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-holland/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dave Holland? Dave Holland, Judas Priest&amp;rsquo;s drummer during their commercial peak in the Eighties, died at the age of 69. He had been living in exile in A Fonsagrada, Spain after being convicted of the attempted rape of a 17-year-old boy and subsequently serving a sentence in prison.Jan 25, 2018
What strings does Dave Holland use? Dave Holland uses Michael Tobias Design Bass Guitars, Thomastik-Infeld Bass Strings, LaBella Bass Guitar Strings and Gallien-Krueger Speakers and Amplifiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Drake related to Larry Graham?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-graham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-graham/</guid>
      <description>How long has Larry Graham been married? 41 years
Is Larry Graham Drake&amp;rsquo;s uncle? Larry Graham Jr. In 1993, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Sly and the Family Stone. He is also the uncle of rapper Drake.
Who invented bass slapping? Larry Graham
What happened to Sly from Sly and the Family Stone? Sly Stone, one of the pioneers of funk music as mastermind for Sly and the Family Stone, is now homeless and living out of a white van in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is John Deacon still friends with Queen?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-deacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-deacon/</guid>
      <description>Does John Deacon still get royalties? The 2018 biopic is still bringing in royalties for Brian May, Roger Taylor and John Deacon.Jul 5, 2021
Who is the richest member of Queen? So, what is the net worth of Brian May? As of 2022, the net worth of Brian May is $210 million. Brian May is the richest Queen member.Oct 24, 2021
What is Mary Austins net worth? Mary Austin net worth: Mary Austin is an English woman who has a net worth of $115 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Les Claypool a redneck?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/les-claypool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/les-claypool/</guid>
      <description>Who performs the Seinfeld theme song? Seinfeld/Artists
Did Les Claypool play the Seinfeld theme? TIL the Seinfeld Theme was played by Les Claypool.
Who is the bass player on Seinfeld theme? Jonathan Wolff
Does Primus still get royalties from South Park? But when South Park went to syndication in 2005 and Matt got to review their deals again, they increased the royalties for Primus members to what they deserved.May 6, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Les Claypool a redneck?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oscar-pettiford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oscar-pettiford/</guid>
      <description>Who performs the Seinfeld theme song? Seinfeld/Artists
Did Les Claypool play the Seinfeld theme? TIL the Seinfeld Theme was played by Les Claypool.
Who is the bass player on Seinfeld theme? Jonathan Wolff
Does Primus still get royalties from South Park? But when South Park went to syndication in 2005 and Matt got to review their deals again, they increased the royalties for Primus members to what they deserved.May 6, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Mike Watt a good bass player?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-watt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-watt/</guid>
      <description>What Bass does Mike Watt use? Watt states on his site that he uses a 1956 Fender Precision bass.
What AMP does Khruangbin use? Fender &amp;lsquo;68 Custom Deluxe Reverb Guitar Amplifier.
What AMP does Mark Speer use? When Khruangbin record, Speer uses a Fender Deluxe Reverb “blackface” and when they go on the road he brings a Fender &amp;lsquo;68 Custom Deluxe Reverb “silverface” reissue. Both are fantastic and powerful tube amps with their Fender-typical spring reverb and a tube vibrato effect, which Speer clearly likes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Paul Jackson married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass on thrust? Paul Jackson
Who played on Head Hunters? In 1973, the band comprised Hancock (keyboards), Bennie Maupin (saxophone, clarinet), Harvey Mason (drums), Paul Jackson (bass), and Bill Summers (percussion). Their first album, Head Hunters, sold more than one million copies.
Is Paul Jackson married? He had one son from that marriage, LaFura Eguchi Jackson, who was born in 1975 and died of cancer in 2000. Jackson&amp;rsquo;s second marriage was to Akiko Suzuki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Peter Hook the best bassist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-hook/</guid>
      <description>Where does Peter Hook live now? Home. I live in Alderley Edge, just south of Manchester.Sep 24, 2011
Where does Peter Hook live now? Home. I live in Alderley Edge, just south of Manchester.Sep 24, 2011
Is Peter Hook still in New Order? Peter Hook has reflected on his last gig with New Order 15 years ago, calling it the “most miserable night of my life”. Hook played his final show with his former Joy Division bandmates in Argentina on November 18, 2006, and discusses the experience in the new mini-documentary The Peter Hook Signature Collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Thundercat in Book of Boba?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hadrien-feraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hadrien-feraud/</guid>
      <description>Are ThunderCats real? ThunderCats is an American media franchise, featuring a fictional group of catlike humanoid aliens.
Is Snarf a cat? In the 2011 cartoon, Snarf is the devoted cat-like pet of Lion-O. Unlike his predecessor, Snarf is primarily quadruped and does not speak beyond the occasional murmured word, although later episodes do feature him making his characteristic &amp;ldquo;SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise, and on occasion &amp;ldquo;SNARFITY-SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise.
What was the name of the female ThunderCat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Thundercat in Book of Boba?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stephen-thundercat-bruner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stephen-thundercat-bruner/</guid>
      <description>Are ThunderCats real? ThunderCats is an American media franchise, featuring a fictional group of catlike humanoid aliens.
Is Snarf a cat? In the 2011 cartoon, Snarf is the devoted cat-like pet of Lion-O. Unlike his predecessor, Snarf is primarily quadruped and does not speak beyond the occasional murmured word, although later episodes do feature him making his characteristic &amp;ldquo;SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise, and on occasion &amp;ldquo;SNARFITY-SNARF-SNARF&amp;rdquo; noise.
What was the name of the female ThunderCat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Victor Wooten related to Bobby Wooten?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-wooten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-wooten/</guid>
      <description>Does Victor Wooten have a brother? Victor Wooten/Brothers
How many brothers does Victor Wooten have? five Wooten brothers
Where are the Wooten brothers from? He&amp;rsquo;s known as &amp;lsquo;The Teacha&amp;rsquo; because, when the Wooten lads were young tykes milling restlessly around their home in Hawaii, it is rumored to have been Regi who started it all. Beginning on a brokedown ukelele and progressing to an electric guitar, Regi taught himself and then his brothers all about The Funk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Wood Harris and Steve Harris brothers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gary-willis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gary-willis/</guid>
      <description>Who is the current lead singer of Iron Maiden? Iron Maiden/Lead singers
Who replaced Adrian Smith in Iron Maiden? Janick Gers
Why did Bruce Dickinson leave Iron Maiden? After the Fear of the Dark Tour, Dickinson decided to leave Iron Maiden to concentrate on his solo career. At that point the band had already booked a following tour in 1993, which Dickinson did not enjoy.
Why did Iron Maiden add a third guitarist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Wood Harris and Steve Harris brothers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-harris/</guid>
      <description>Who is the richest member of Iron Maiden? As of October 2022, The net worth of Bruce Dickinson is $130 million, which makes him the richest Iron Maiden member.Oct 31, 2021
How much is Iron Maiden net worth? The band has sold over 100 million copies of their entire albums worldwide and received countless successes. As of 2022, Iron Maiden&amp;rsquo;s net worth is $100 million. With this, Iron Maiden is the third richest metal band in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What album did Justin Chancellor join Tool?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/justin-chancellor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/justin-chancellor/</guid>
      <description>Should bass players use a pick? You can use a pick on your bass guitar if you want to. Both finger plucking and using picks are perfectly normal ways to play the bass guitar. You can find plenty of examples of famous bassists who use either technique, and there is no harm to using a pick. It won&amp;rsquo;t damage your strings or create an inferior sound.
Do most bassists use picks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What band was Bobby Vega in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-laswell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-laswell/</guid>
      <description>Do guitars and basses use the same picks? Bass players generally use thicker picks. The thickness improves the bass playing control, and the overall tone of the string. The average pick thickness for bass players is 1.17 mm, while for guitar players is 0.89 mm. Remember, bass strings are much thicker than guitar strings.
Do you need picks for bass guitar? Truthfully, there is no right or wrong way to play a bass guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What band was Bobby Vega in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-vega/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-vega/</guid>
      <description>Who has Bobby Vega played with? In addition to his stellar career as a sideman, Bobby has been a member and co-founder of several of the Bay Area&amp;rsquo;s finest all-star collaborations, including Zero, KVHW, the Avalon Allstars, and Don&amp;rsquo;t Push the Clown; he continues to work with Zero/KVHW guitarist Steve Kimock in various situations.Oct 24, 2011
What size pick does Bobby Vega use? I get the most sounds with a medium; my main pick is a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What bass did Paul Chambers play?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-chambers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-chambers/</guid>
      <description>Who did Paul Chambers play with? Paul Chambers/Music groups
Who has Paul Chambers bass? Although Paul Chambers&amp;rsquo; bass work was firmly rooted in the East Coast scene of bop and modal jazz for most of his career, he does appear on several of the great cool records of the day too. This is one example: joining Chet, Johnny Griffin &amp;amp; Al Haig alongside his longtime rhythm section colleague Philly Joe Jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did Chris Squire of Yes died from?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-squire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-squire/</guid>
      <description>Who is the richest guitar player? Paul McCartney
How did Chris Squire get his bass sound? He cited Paul McCartney, Jack Bruce, and Bill Wyman as influences, but it was the Who&amp;rsquo;s John Entwistle that lit Squire up the most. He emulated Entwistle&amp;rsquo;s trebly roundwound sound, filtering it through his own intuition and the keen ear for classical harmony he had developed as a young choir singer.Jan 8, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What ethnicity is Esperanza Spalding?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/esperanza-spalding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/esperanza-spalding/</guid>
      <description>What is Esperanza Spalding known for? Esperanza Emily Spalding (born October 18, 1984) is an American bassist, singer, songwriter, and composer. Her accolades include five Grammy Awards, a Boston Music Award, and a Soul Train Music Award.
How did Esperanza Spalding become famous? &amp;ldquo;Esperanza,&amp;rdquo; her 2008 album, spent more than 70 weeks on the Billboard Contemporary Jazz chart and was the most successful internationally selling debut that year. She recorded her first album, &amp;ldquo;Junjo,&amp;rdquo; in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Grateful Dead songs did Phil Lesh write?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-lesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-lesh/</guid>
      <description>When did Phil Lesh have his liver transplant? Lesh has first-hand knowledge of the benefits of organ donation. After years of living with Hepatitis C, he underwent liver transplant surgery in December 1998.Aug 2, 2002
Why did Phil Lesh get a liver transplant? The party was cut short by Lesh&amp;rsquo;s near-fatal brush with hepatitis C, which had irreparably damaged his liver and sent him into the hospital later that year for liver transplant surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Bob Babbitt?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-babbitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-babbitt/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass on Motown Records? Jamerson was not Motown&amp;rsquo;s only bassist in those early years. Other early Motown bassists include Clarence Isabell, Tweed Beard, Willie Green, and Joe Williams (see, Slutsky, Standing, 12); in later years, bassists Tony Newton and Bob Babbitt recorded for Motown in Detroit as well.
Who played bass on Tears of a Clown? Bob Babbitt, the Motown studio bassist who played on hits including Smokey Robinson &amp;amp; the Miracles&amp;rsquo; “Tears of a Clown” and the Temptations&amp;rsquo; “Ball of Confusion,” died yesterday in Nashville after suffering complications from brain cancer, his spokesperson confirmed to Rolling Stone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Mick Karn?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-moore/</guid>
      <description>What was Japan&amp;rsquo;s biggest hit? Ghosts
Who is Yuka Fujii? Photographer, curator. Based in London, England. The majority of Yuka&amp;rsquo;s activities are based in that vast but ambiguous area where the visual arts, design, and music cross over.
What happened to the Japanese band move? On December 7, 2012, the band announced on their official website that, after a stint of 15 years, they will disband after their last live performance on March 16, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Mick Karn?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-karn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-karn/</guid>
      <description>What was Japan&amp;rsquo;s biggest hit? Ghosts
Who is Yuka Fujii? Photographer, curator. Based in London, England. The majority of Yuka&amp;rsquo;s activities are based in that vast but ambiguous area where the visual arts, design, and music cross over.
What happened to the Japanese band move? On December 7, 2012, the band announced on their official website that, after a stint of 15 years, they will disband after their last live performance on March 16, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Robbie Shakespeare?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/robbie-shakespeare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/robbie-shakespeare/</guid>
      <description>What happened Robbie Shakespeare? He was 68. Guillaume Bougard, a close friend and frequent collaborator, said the cause was complications of kidney and liver transplants. Starting in the mid-1970s, Mr. Shakespeare and the drummer Sly Dunbar were among the most prolific musicians in the business, reggae or otherwise.Feb 26, 2022
Did Robbie Shakespeare play for Bob Marley? Shakespeare, who died in Florida on December 8, is best known for being a member of famed drum and bass team, Sly and Robbie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Berry Oakley Jr?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/andrew-gouche/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/andrew-gouche/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dickey Betts now? For years now, Betts has lived in Sarasota County, just off the Highway 41 he sings about in the Allman Brothers&amp;rsquo; best known song.Dec 10, 2020
Who has died from the Allman Brothers Band? This feature was originally published in Classic Rock 57, in October 2003. Dan Toler died in 2011, Butch Trucks died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound in January 2017, and Gregg Allman passed away in June of the same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Berry Oakley Jr?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/berry-oakley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/berry-oakley/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dickey Betts now? For years now, Betts has lived in Sarasota County, just off the Highway 41 he sings about in the Allman Brothers&amp;rsquo; best known song.Dec 10, 2020
Who has died from the Allman Brothers Band? This feature was originally published in Classic Rock 57, in October 2003. Dan Toler died in 2011, Butch Trucks died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound in January 2017, and Gregg Allman passed away in June of the same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Berry Oakley Jr?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/eddie-gomez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/eddie-gomez/</guid>
      <description>Where is Dickey Betts now? For years now, Betts has lived in Sarasota County, just off the Highway 41 he sings about in the Allman Brothers&amp;rsquo; best known song.Dec 10, 2020
Who has died from the Allman Brothers Band? This feature was originally published in Classic Rock 57, in October 2003. Dan Toler died in 2011, Butch Trucks died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound in January 2017, and Gregg Allman passed away in June of the same year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Francis Rocco Prestia?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/rocco-prestia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/rocco-prestia/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Francis Rocco Prestia? OAKLAND (CBS SF) &amp;ndash; Francis &amp;ldquo;Rocco&amp;rdquo; Prestia, the longtime bassist for Oakland funk pioneers Tower Of Power, died overnight Wednesday after a long battle with various illnesses, according to friends and family. He was 69.Sep 30, 2020
Who passed away from Tower of Power? — Rick Stevens, the former lead singer of Oakland&amp;rsquo;s Tower of Power rhythm and blues band who spent 36 years in prison, has died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Jack Bruce?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-bruce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-bruce/</guid>
      <description>Who did vocals for Cream? Jack Bruce
Who was the main singer in Cream? Cream/Members
Who was the lead singer of Cream? Jack Bruce
Who died from the band Cream? Ginger Baker
Who are the Cream band members? Cream/Members
What did Ginger Baker think of Eric Clapton? “Eric Clapton is probably my best friend,” Ginger says. “Him and Stevie Winwood. Eric is like my younger brother. I&amp;rsquo;m very proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Louis Johnson?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/louis-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/louis-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Which one of the Brothers Johnson are dead? Louis Johnson
Are the Brothers Johnson really brothers? The Los Angeles-based Brothers Johnson, a group featuring Louis and his brother George, got their start backing up Quincy Jones before releasing their acclaimed, Jones-produced debut LP Look Out for #1 in 1976.May 22, 2015
Is the group Brothers Johnson still alive? Funk and R&amp;amp;B bassist Louis Johnson died at age 60 on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Ron Baker?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leroy-slam-stewart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leroy-slam-stewart/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Ron Baker? After the Knicks waived Baker, he played briefly for the Wizards. He spent the 2019-20 season with CSKA Moscow. Now, the 28-year-old is moving onto the next stage of his life.Aug 26, 2021
Why is Ron Baker not in the NBA? Baker decided that it was time that he moved on in life and the physical strain on his body got to be too much for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Ron Baker?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-baker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-baker/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Ron Baker? After the Knicks waived Baker, he played briefly for the Wizards. He spent the 2019-20 season with CSKA Moscow. Now, the 28-year-old is moving onto the next stage of his life.Aug 26, 2021
Why is Ron Baker not in the NBA? Baker decided that it was time that he moved on in life and the physical strain on his body got to be too much for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to the bass player from Chic?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-edwards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-edwards/</guid>
      <description>What happened to the members of Chic? But “I&amp;rsquo;ll Be There” derives from decades-old Chic tapes only recently uncovered. Rodgers — the last surviving member of the original core trio — completed the song with a new lineup, as bassist Bernard Edwards died from pneumonia after playing a 1996 concert and drummer Tony Thompson was lost to cancer in 2003.Mar 21, 2015
Is Chic still alive? Chic was initially believed to have been killed by the Black Hood after Betty gave him up, but it was later revealed that Hal spared Chic and mentored him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to the bass player from Chic?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-berlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-berlin/</guid>
      <description>What happened to the members of Chic? But “I&amp;rsquo;ll Be There” derives from decades-old Chic tapes only recently uncovered. Rodgers — the last surviving member of the original core trio — completed the song with a new lineup, as bassist Bernard Edwards died from pneumonia after playing a 1996 concert and drummer Tony Thompson was lost to cancer in 2003.Mar 21, 2015
Is Chic still alive? Chic was initially believed to have been killed by the Black Hood after Betty gave him up, but it was later revealed that Hal spared Chic and mentored him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Victor Bailey?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-manring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-manring/</guid>
      <description>Where was Victor Bailey Jr? Victor Bailey Jr. - Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball - University of Tennessee Athletics.
Who is Victor Bailey? Victor Bailey, the virtuoso electric bassist and educator best known as the final bass player in Weather Report, following Jaco Pastorius, died on the morning of Nov. 11. He was 56, and had long suffered with Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease, essentially a form of muscular dystrophy that ran in his family.Nov 12, 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Victor Bailey?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/victor-bailey/</guid>
      <description>Where was Victor Bailey Jr? Victor Bailey Jr. - Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball - University of Tennessee Athletics.
Who is Victor Bailey? Victor Bailey, the virtuoso electric bassist and educator best known as the final bass player in Weather Report, following Jaco Pastorius, died on the morning of Nov. 11. He was 56, and had long suffered with Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease, essentially a form of muscular dystrophy that ran in his family.Nov 12, 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Verdine White?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/george-porter-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/george-porter-jr/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Maurice White of Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Death. On the morning of February 4, 2016, White died in his sleep at his Los Angeles home from the effects of Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease. He was 74 years old. His brother Verdine said, &amp;ldquo;My brother, hero and best friend Maurice White passed away peacefully last night in his sleep.
Who recently died from Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Andrew Woolfolk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Verdine White?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/verdine-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/verdine-white/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Maurice White of Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Death. On the morning of February 4, 2016, White died in his sleep at his Los Angeles home from the effects of Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease. He was 74 years old. His brother Verdine said, &amp;ldquo;My brother, hero and best friend Maurice White passed away peacefully last night in his sleep.
Who recently died from Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire? Andrew Woolfolk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pino Palladino doing now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pino-palladino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pino-palladino/</guid>
      <description>What kind of strings does Pino Palladino use? Thomastik-Infeld Flatwound strings As already mentioned, Palladino&amp;rsquo;s use of flatwound strings has been a major component of his sound and Thomastik-Infeld are his preferred choice.May 24, 2017
What happened Pino Palladino? Palladino says he&amp;rsquo;s “not exactly crazy about touring any more” – he stopped playing live with the Who in 2016 – but is considering doing some gigs around Notes With Attachments, pandemic permitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Ray Brown known for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ray-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ray-brown/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Ella Fitzgerald husband? Webb died of spinal tuberculosis on June 16, 1939, and his band was renamed Ella and Her Famous Orchestra with Fitzgerald taking on the role of bandleader.
Who inherited Ella Fitzgerald estate? Richard Rosman, executor of the Fitzgerald estate, is particularly pleased that &amp;ldquo;memorabilia which really exemplifies Ella&amp;rsquo;s music and career is going to be at the Smithsonian and her music at the Library of Congress for all of America to enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the significance of Willie Dixon?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-dixon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-dixon/</guid>
      <description>What songs are Led Zeppelin accused of stealing? In 2010, American folk singer Jake Holmes sued Led Zeppelin for $1 million. Holmes claims that Jimmy Page stole his licks and lyrics for “Dazed and Confused,” perhaps the greatest tune on the Zep&amp;rsquo;s first album. Holmes says his version of the song was written in 1967, two years before Led Zeppelin&amp;rsquo;s.Nov 10, 2021
Did Led Zeppelin steal lemon song? The song&amp;rsquo;s titular &amp;ldquo;lemon&amp;rdquo; is also taken from another old blues song: Robert Johnson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Travelling Riverside Blues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What made James Jamerson so great?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-jamerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-jamerson/</guid>
      <description>What made James Jamerson so great? He had a very unique skill set that gave him the ability to create and execute bass lines and grooves like no other bass player had ever done before. That&amp;rsquo;s what gave James Jamerson his unique super power, and ultimately why he became one of the most game-changing bass players in the history of modern music.Nov 3, 2018
Who was the legendary bass player for the Funk Brothers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What makes RON CARTER a great bass player?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-carter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ron-carter/</guid>
      <description>Did RON CARTER ever play electric bass? Carter didn&amp;rsquo;t play much pure fusion, but he did record a bit on electric bass, for example on Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s Red Clay from 1970. Many of Carter&amp;rsquo;s own albums from the &amp;rsquo;70s on CTI and Milestone added strings, brass, and percussion, not to mention funk and even disco beats (Anything Goes, 1975).Mar 10, 2021
Who is the most recorded bassist? Carol Kaye (née Smith, born March 24, 1935) is an American musician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was Charles Mingus most famous for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charles-mingus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charles-mingus/</guid>
      <description>Where did Charles Mingus grow up? Los Angeles
Is Charles Mingus Chinese? Mingus Junior was largely raised in the Watts area of Los Angeles. His maternal grandfather was a Chinese British subject from Hong Kong, and his maternal grandmother was an African-American from the southern United States.
Where did Charles Mingus live? Charles Mingus/Places lived
What nationality is Charles Mingus? Charles Mingus, byname Charlie Mingus, (born April 22, 1922, Nogales, Arizona, U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What were Cliff Burton&#39;s last words?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cliff-burton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cliff-burton/</guid>
      <description>How old would Cliff Burton be today? Feb. 10, 2018 would have been Burton&amp;rsquo;s 56th birthday. The upcoming Cliff Burton Day would be his 60th birthday and a special livestream is scheduled for 7PM PT.Feb 8, 2022
What were Cliff Burton&amp;rsquo;s last words? After chatting for some time, Frank Bello and Cliff Burton separated saying maybe they will see each other the next day and the last word he heard from the late bassist was &amp;lsquo;Maybe I will&amp;rsquo; which makes them even more meaningful than usual since he left this world a few hours after saying these words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What were John Lennon&#39;s last words to Paul McCartney?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-mccartney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-mccartney/</guid>
      <description>Who is the wealthiest rock star in the world? Paul McCartney
Did Paul McCartney get along with George Harrison? More often than not, Harrison was concerned with spirituality and the internal struggles but on this track, he chose to put his feelings on the canvas and aim one directly as McCartney. Luckily, the two became close friends again before Harrison&amp;rsquo;s tragic death in 2001.Aug 20, 2021
What did Paul McCartney say about George Harrison?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When did Bill Black leave Elvis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-black/</guid>
      <description>How long did Bill Black play with Elvis? The Beatles discuss meeting Elvis When Elvis Presley first shot to fame in 1956 he had a trio called The Blue Moon Boys with guitarist Scotty Moore and bassist Bill Black. But less than 10 years later and Bill was dead. Having gone on to form the Bill Black Combo, the bassist became ill in the early 1960s.Oct 21, 2021
When did Bill Black leave Elvis?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When did Bill Black leave Elvis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/red-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/red-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Scotty Moore and Bill Black? Two musicians who have been with him since he started his singing career four years ago have quit in a pay dispute. Bill Black and Scotty Moore said they resigned Saturday, effective Sept. 21. Mr.Jan 9, 2012
Why did Scotty Moore leave Elvis band? While faring well with romance, Presley was having trouble with his business affairs. Two musicians who have been with him since he started his singing career four years ago have quit in a pay dispute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where do fleas originally come from?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/flea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/flea/</guid>
      <description>Are cat fleas visible to the human eye? Fleas are small flightless insects that can live on cats. They are dark brown in colour and are approximately 2-4mm in length so they are just visible to the naked eye. Although fleas cannot fly they jump from one place to another.
What is the actual size of a flea? The adult flea varies from about 0.1 to 0.32 cm (0.039 to 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where does Bakithi Kumalo live?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bakithi-kumalo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bakithi-kumalo/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass guitar for Michael Jackson? Louis Johnson (April 13, 1955 – May 21, 2015) was an American bass guitarist. Johnson was best known for his work with the group the Brothers Johnson and his session playing on several hit albums of the 1970s and 1980s, including the best-selling album of all time, Michael Jackson&amp;rsquo;s Thriller.
Who played bass on Jackson 5 albums? For starters, there&amp;rsquo;s been some debate on who actually played bass on the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where does Oteil Burbridge live now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oteil-burbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oteil-burbridge/</guid>
      <description>Who is playing bass for dead and Company? Burbridge
What Bass does Oteil Burbridge? Gibson EB-2 Bass Guitar &amp;ldquo;I bought this bass because it looked just like a Cherry Red Gibson ES-335 guitar that Mark Kimbrell played in my band, Oteil and the Peacemakers.
What does Oteil Burbridge? Oteil Burbridge is an American multi-instrumentalist, specializing on the bass guitar, trained in playing jazz and classical music from an early age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Carol Kaye today?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carol-kaye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carol-kaye/</guid>
      <description>Where is Carol Kaye now? Since 1969, Kaye&amp;rsquo;s shared her expertise via tutoring books — and today she&amp;rsquo;s a tech-savvy educator. “I&amp;rsquo;m teaching jazz on Skype because people worldwide want to learn real jazz,” she tells The Post, sounding almost giddy. “That&amp;rsquo;s great for me. I&amp;rsquo;m in it again, giving lessons in guitar and bass.”Jan 2, 2020
Where is Carol Kaye now? Since 1969, Kaye&amp;rsquo;s shared her expertise via tutoring books — and today she&amp;rsquo;s a tech-savvy educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michael Rhodes now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-rodriguez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-rodriguez/</guid>
      <description>Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Who has Michael Rhodes played with? As country music began to boom in the late 1980s, so did Rhodes&amp;rsquo; career as a session player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michael Rhodes now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-rhodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-rhodes/</guid>
      <description>Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Where is Michael Rhodes now? Michael Kenworthy Rhodes (born 19 December 1987 in Durban, South Africa) is a rugby union footballer who currently plays with English Premiership side Saracens.
Who has Michael Rhodes played with? As country music began to boom in the late 1980s, so did Rhodes&amp;rsquo; career as a session player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Stanley Clarke today?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stanley-clarke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stanley-clarke/</guid>
      <description>Who played drums on Stanley Clarke School Days? Gerry Brown
Who played guitar with Stanley Clarke? Stanley&amp;rsquo;s storied career includes a world tour with guitarist Jeff Beck (1979), collaborations with The Police drummer Stewart Copeland as part of Animal Logic with (two albums and tours in 1989) , the Superband (which included Larry Carlton, Billy Cobham, Najee and Deron Johnson, 1993-1994), The Rite of Strings (Jean- &amp;hellip;
Does Stanley Clarke have kids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who died from Vanilla Fudge?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stuart-hamm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stuart-hamm/</guid>
      <description>What songs did Vanilla Fudge make famous? The members of Vanilla Fudge were great admirers of the Beatles, and covered several of their songs including &amp;ldquo;Ticket to Ride&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Eleanor Rigby&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;You Can&amp;rsquo;t Do That&amp;rdquo;.
Is Vanilla Fudge in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame? “I&amp;rsquo;m in there because of my influence and what I&amp;rsquo;ve done for drumming. Long Island has a Music Hall Of Fame; Vanilla Fudge are in there for the same reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who died from Vanilla Fudge?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tim-bogert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tim-bogert/</guid>
      <description>Where does Carmine Appice live? New York
Is Carmine Appice a good drummer? Carmine&amp;rsquo;s career is exceptional if for no other reason than its longevity. He was the first rock drummer to appear alone on the cover of Modern Drummer magazine, in the April/June 1978 issue. Thirty years later, in April of 2007, he was the cover subject again.
Is Vanilla Fudge in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who has Leland Sklar played for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leland-sklar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/leland-sklar/</guid>
      <description>Who is the bass player for Carole King and James Taylor? bassist Lee Sklar
Who is the bass player with the long beard? When it comes to session bassists, Leland Sklar is definitely one of those names. Instantly recognizable by his long white beard, he&amp;rsquo;s been an established presence on the L.A. scene for decades.Apr 2, 2018
Who played bass on sussudio? Leland Sklar
Who played Carole King&amp;rsquo;s guitar? Danny Kortchmar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who has Willie Weeks played with?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/willie-weeks/</guid>
      <description>Who played bass on Donny Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s This Christmas? BP sez it&amp;rsquo;s Hathaway playing the piano bass with his left hand, Fender Rhodes with his right. 7 horn players &amp;amp; members of the Chicago Symphony are also mentioned. Is your version from the original album?Dec 9, 2017
Who performed this Christmas? Donny Hathaway
What floor did Donny Hathaway jump from? 15th floor
Where is Donny Hathaway today? On January 13th, 1979, his body was found outside New York&amp;rsquo;s Essex House below his 15th floor hotel room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is considered the father of the US Navy?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-paul-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-paul-jones/</guid>
      <description>What is John Paul Jones most known for? John Paul Jones (born John Paul; July 6, 1747 – July 18, 1792) was a Scottish-American naval captain who was the United States&amp;rsquo; first well-known naval commander in the American Revolutionary War.
Who was John Paul Jones and what was his significance in the war quizlet? John Paul Jones was a daring naval officer who was one of the war&amp;rsquo;s great heroes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Mark King Taco Bell?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-king/</guid>
      <description>How good a bass player was Mark King? Mark King grew up on the Isle Of Wight and moved to London with the aim of being a professional drummer. Instead he became one of the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest bass players, but his earlier ambition may explain his highly rhythmic slap bass style. Mark King rose to fame in the eighties as bassist and vocalist of Level 42.
Who is the best bass player in the world 2020?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Walter Page?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/percy-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/percy-jones/</guid>
      <description>What made the Count Basie big band unique for its time? Count Basie is considered one of the greatest bandleaders of all times. He was the arbiter of the big-band swing sound and his unique style of fusing blues and jazz established swing as a predominant music style.
What was Count Basie&amp;rsquo;s orchestra known for? From its inception, Basie&amp;rsquo;s band was well known for its outstanding rhythm section of Basie on piano, Freddie Green on guitar, Walter Page on bass, and &amp;ldquo;Papa&amp;rdquo; Jo Jones on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Walter Page?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/walter-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/walter-page/</guid>
      <description>What made the Count Basie big band unique for its time? Count Basie is considered one of the greatest bandleaders of all times. He was the arbiter of the big-band swing sound and his unique style of fusing blues and jazz established swing as a predominant music style.
What was Count Basie&amp;rsquo;s orchestra known for? From its inception, Basie&amp;rsquo;s band was well known for its outstanding rhythm section of Basie on piano, Freddie Green on guitar, Walter Page on bass, and &amp;ldquo;Papa&amp;rdquo; Jo Jones on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Elton John fire his band in 1975?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dee-murray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dee-murray/</guid>
      <description>Why did Elton John fire his band in 1975? They on world tours with John for several years. In 1975, after recording Captain Fantastic and the Brown Dirt Cowboy, Murray and Olsson were released from the band because John wanted to achieve a different sound. Murray and Olsson re-joined the band in 1980, starting with 21 at 33.
Who was Elton John&amp;rsquo;s bass player? Bob Birch, a bass player and prolific session sideman best known as a long-time member of Elton John&amp;rsquo;s band, died Wednesday of an apparent suicide at his home in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Geddy leave Rush?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geddy-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geddy-lee/</guid>
      <description>Is Geddy Lee still married? Lee supports many causes through personal and band donations. He is known as an avid baseball fan and wine connoisseur. Lee has been married to Nancy Young for over 35 years and they have 2 children.
Is Rush still performing? Rush ceased touring at the end of 2015, and Lifeson announced in January 2018 that the band would not continue. On January 7, 2020, Peart died of glioblastoma, a type of brain cancer, at the age of 67.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Geezer Butler called geezer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geezer-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/geezer-butler/</guid>
      <description>Is Geezer Butler Irish? Roots notes. Geezer, who was born Terence Michael Joseph Butler in 1949, was raised in a large Anglo-Irish family in Aston and credits his background with giving him the will and tenacity to persevere with music. “I had a nice working-class upbringing; we never went without anything,” he explains.Sep 6, 2019
Did Ozzy Osbourne rejoin Black Sabbath? Ozzy Osbourne has reportedly rejoined the original line up of Black Sabbath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Richard Bona famous?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/doug-wimbish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/doug-wimbish/</guid>
      <description>Has Richard Bona won Grammy Award? One of these accomplished personalities, Grammy Award-winning Cameroonian bassist Richard Bona, will be making his way to India to speak at a TEDxGateway event on February 23rd at Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s NSCI Dome. Bona – who grew up in Minta – was surrounded by a family full of musicians.Feb 14, 2020
What nationality is Richard Bona? Richard Bona (born 28 October 1967) is a Cameroon-born American musician, multi-instrumentalist and vocalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Richard Bona famous?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/niels-henning-orsted-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/niels-henning-orsted-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>Has Richard Bona won Grammy Award? One of these accomplished personalities, Grammy Award-winning Cameroonian bassist Richard Bona, will be making his way to India to speak at a TEDxGateway event on February 23rd at Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s NSCI Dome. Bona – who grew up in Minta – was surrounded by a family full of musicians.Feb 14, 2020
What nationality is Richard Bona? Richard Bona (born 28 October 1967) is a Cameroon-born American musician, multi-instrumentalist and vocalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Richard Bona famous?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/richard-bona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/richard-bona/</guid>
      <description>Has Richard Bona won Grammy Award? One of these accomplished personalities, Grammy Award-winning Cameroonian bassist Richard Bona, will be making his way to India to speak at a TEDxGateway event on February 23rd at Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s NSCI Dome. Bona – who grew up in Minta – was surrounded by a family full of musicians.Feb 14, 2020
What nationality is Richard Bona? Richard Bona (born 28 October 1967) is a Cameroon-born American musician, multi-instrumentalist and vocalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Sting is called Sting?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sting/</guid>
      <description>What is Sting&amp;rsquo;s net worth? around $300 million
How did Sting get so rich? According to Celebrity Net Worth, Sting has an estimated net worth of $400 million. He has predominantly made this money through his work in the music industry, both with &amp;lsquo;Police&amp;rsquo; and as a solo artist. However, he has also made some of his fortunes through his acting career.
What&amp;rsquo;s Billy Joel&amp;rsquo;s net worth? But Joel&amp;rsquo;s total net worth is several times more than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why was Jaco Pastorius beaten to death?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jaco-pastorius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jaco-pastorius/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Jaco Pastorius that ended his life? Twenty years ago Friday, bassist Jaco Pastorius died in a Ft. Lauderdale, Fla., hospital as a result of injuries sustained during a fight in a local nightclub. He was 35.Sep 21, 2007
Was Jaco Pastorius a junkie? For a jazz musician, Jaco Pastorius died in pretty creditable rock n&amp;rsquo; roll style: drugs, delusions, alcohol and itinerancy.Aug 3, 2015
What was Jaco addicted to?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Chad Smith and Will Ferrell friends?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chad-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chad-smith/</guid>
      <description>Is Will Ferrell and Chad Smith twins? Of course, the stars are not related, with Chad Smith born on 25 October 1961 to Joan and Curtis Smith in Saint Paul, Minnesota while Will Ferrell was born on 16 July 1967 to Betty Kay and Roy Lee Ferrell in Irvine California. However, it&amp;rsquo;s never stopped the comparisons.Oct 25, 2021
Does Will Ferrell have a twin? Will Ferrell Has a Drum-Off with his Twin, Chad Smith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Paul and Ringo still friends?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ringo-starr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ringo-starr/</guid>
      <description>Who is the richest Beatle member? McCartney
What is Ringo Starr&amp;rsquo;s net worth? $350 million
What were John Lennon&amp;rsquo;s last words to Paul McCartney? &amp;rsquo; She said that the last words that John Lennon said to Paul in the hallway of the Dakota building were, he patted him on the shoulder and said, &amp;lsquo;Think about me every now and then, old friend. &amp;lsquo;Sep 17, 2020
Did the remaining Beatles go to John Lennon&amp;rsquo;s funeral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Dennis Chambers read music?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dennis-chambers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dennis-chambers/</guid>
      <description>Did Dennis Chambers play for James Brown? When Dennis Chambers was just 13-years-old and gigging around his hometown of Baltimore, he was already so precociously talented that he was asked to join James Brown&amp;rsquo;s group.Feb 21, 2019
Did Dennis Chambers play for Steely Dan? Dennis has played with many greats throughout the years including John Scofield, Steely Dan, Santana, and many others. He also became part of the Sugar Hill record label and can be heard on many hip-hop classics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Stewart Copeland and Sting get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stewart-copeland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stewart-copeland/</guid>
      <description>Who is Stewart Copeland&amp;rsquo;s wife? Stewart Copeland/Wife
Was Stewart Copeland&amp;rsquo;s dad in the CIA? In it, he digs deep into the life of his father, Miles Copeland Jr., a musician, businessman, and secret CIA operative (who was interviewed for this magazine in 1986).Oct 20, 2020
Are Sting and Stewart Copeland friends? As long as they don&amp;rsquo;t make music together, they are close friends. During an interview last year, Stewart Copeland stated that they have different reasons for making music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Jim Gordon become Batman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jim-gordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jim-gordon/</guid>
      <description>Does Jim Gordon Trust Batman? In most modern story arcs, however, Gordon is often skeptical of Batman&amp;rsquo;s vigilante methods, and hesitant to work with a guy dressed as a bat. Over time, however, Gordon learns to trust Bats and comes to recognize the necessity of his role in Gotham. A mutual respect develops, and eventually, a friendship.Feb 7, 2022
Who is Batman&amp;rsquo;s closest friend? Batman And Alfred Pennyworth Batman and Alfred is the first and most important friendship most fans came to know in comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Neil Peart pass away?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/neil-peart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/neil-peart/</guid>
      <description>Why Neil Peart is the greatest drummer of all time? Neil Peart was the fantastic drummer for the band Rush. He was chosen as the drummer for the band because he reminded them of Keith Moon from The Who. When it was all said and done, the only thing he had in common was his hard-hitting style.Nov 11, 2020
Where does Neil Peart rank as a drummer? No. 3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Tony from Hi-Five died?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-thompson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-thompson/</guid>
      <description>How did lead singer of Hi-Five died? On June 1, 2007, Thompson&amp;rsquo;s body was discovered by security officers at around 10 p.m. near an air-conditioning unit outside of an apartment complex in his native Waco, Texas. An autopsy later determined that he had died from &amp;ldquo;toxic effects of chlorodifluoromethane,&amp;rdquo; or inhaling a toxic amount of freon.
Who died from Hi 5? Roderick &amp;ldquo;Pooh&amp;rdquo; Clark, an original member of Hi-Five, has died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How good a drummer is Alex Van Halen?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/alex-van-halen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/alex-van-halen/</guid>
      <description>Do Alex and Eddie Van Halen have the same parents? Eddie &amp;amp; Alex&amp;rsquo;s parents, Jan and Eugenia Van Halen circa 1951 | Eddie van halen, Van halen, Alex van halen.
Was Eddie Van Halen a twin? Both brothers were trained as classical pianists during childhood. Although Alex is known as a professional drummer, he began his musical aspirations as a guitarist, with his brother Eddie taking up drums.
Is Van Halen ever going to tour again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Mick Fleetwood related to Eric Clapton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-fleetwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-fleetwood/</guid>
      <description>Did Fleetwood Mac sleep with each other? Stevie Nicks had an affair with Mick Fleetwood in 1977 Shortly after her breakup from Buckingham, Nicks fell for and began having an affair with fellow bandmate, Mick Fleetwood, while Fleetwood Mac was on tour promoting Rumours in 1977.Jan 11, 2021
What is the meaning of Tusk by Fleetwood Mac? The &amp;ldquo;Tusk&amp;rdquo; is slang for penis, so the song is basically about sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Manu Katche?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/manu-katche/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/manu-katche/</guid>
      <description>Is Manu Katche a good drummer? Not a household name but Manu Katche&amp;rsquo; might be one of the most under-rated or perhaps under-the-radar drummers of all time. His resume is nothing short of a who&amp;rsquo;s who of rock and roll ranging from pretty much everything Peter Gabriel has done from the album So to today.Jul 26, 2018
Who played drums Peter Gabriel? Manu Katche
Who played drums on In Your Eyes Peter Gabriel?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bernard Purdie the most recorded drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-purdie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-purdie/</guid>
      <description>Did Bernard Purdie play with the Beatles? While it&amp;rsquo;s true that Purdie&amp;rsquo;s name appears on hundreds of albums released during the past 40 years, he has never been officially credited for his work with The Beatles. In fact, the only known source for this astonishing bit of music trivia is Bernard Purdie himself!
Is Bernard Purdie the most recorded drummer? Purdie, who has played on over 4,000 albums, is widely regarded as “the world&amp;rsquo;s most recorded drummer”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Billy Cobham a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-cobham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-cobham/</guid>
      <description>What kind of drums does Billy Cobham play? Billy also was integral in the creation of the original Gong Bass Drums. Cobham did not initially play a large kit with two bass drums (The Inner Mounting Flame and early live Mahavishnu gigs were done with a smaller, single bass drum kit), and he wasn&amp;rsquo;t the first jazz drummer to play with two bass drums.
Is Billy Cobham a good drummer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Carlos Santana still married to Cindy Blackman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cindy-blackman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cindy-blackman/</guid>
      <description>Is Santana&amp;rsquo;s drummer his wife? Cindy Blackman Santana, a drum dynamo in jazz and rock, riffs on music, her all-star new album and famous husband. How did acclaimed drummer Cindy Blackman Santana react when her husband and musical partner, guitar legend Carlos Santana, first suggested she make an album featuring her singing?Oct 5, 2020
Is Cindy Blackman still married to Carlos Santana? Soulfulness has defined Blackman Santana&amp;rsquo;s playing since her breakout in the mid-1980s, and it&amp;rsquo;s the lifeblood of Give The Drummer Some, her joyful new jazz-fusion record featuring a cast of A-listers, including her husband of 10 years, Carlos Santana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Carmine Appice a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carmine-appice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carmine-appice/</guid>
      <description>Are Carmine and Vinny Appice brothers? Vincent Samson Appice (born September 13, 1957) is an American rock drummer best known for his work with the bands Dio, Black Sabbath, and Heaven &amp;amp; Hell. Of Italian descent, he is the younger brother of drummer Carmine Appice. Brooklyn, New York City, New York, U.S.
Is Vinny Appice a good drummer? Vinny Appice may not be the most recognized drummer because his brother often overshadows him, but he is certainly one worth studying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Clem Burke a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clem-burke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clem-burke/</guid>
      <description>Who is Blondie&amp;rsquo;s partner? Christopher Stein (born January 5, 1950) is the co-founder and guitarist of the new wave band Blondie.
Did Clem Burke play drums for the Eurythmics? Clem went on to lay down drums for Annie Lennox and Dave Stewart in Eurythmics, joined The Ramones for a spell, played with Iggy Pop and then rejoined Blondie when they reunited in 1997 with a hit comeback album, No Exit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Danny Carey the best drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/danny-carey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/danny-carey/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Danny Carey at the airport? Danny Carey, the renowned drummer for rock band Tool, was arrested for misdemeanor assault at Kansas City International Airport after getting into an altercation with a security guard, according to reports.Dec 13, 2021
Is Danny Carey still in Tool? Daniel Edwin Carey (born May 10, 1961) is an American musician and songwriter. He is the drummer for the American rock band Tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Dave Grohl deaf?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-grohl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-grohl/</guid>
      <description>Why did original drummer leave Foo Fighters? What happened to Foo Fighters original drummer? The original drummer for the Foo Fighters was William Goldsmith. The reason for him leaving the Foo Fighters was Dave Grohl&amp;rsquo;s perfectionism.
When did Dave Grohl leave Foo Fighters? A few months later, his bandmates said that they wanted to replace his wife, Gloria Bujnowski, as their manager. Grieving and feeling betrayed, he left in December 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Derek Trucks kin to Butch Trucks?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/butch-trucks-and-jaimoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/butch-trucks-and-jaimoe/</guid>
      <description>What are the names of the original Ohio Players? The band formed in Dayton, Ohio, United States, in 1959 as the Ohio Untouchables and initially included members Robert Ward (vocals/guitar), Marshall &amp;ldquo;Rock&amp;rdquo; Jones (bass), Clarence &amp;ldquo;Satch&amp;rdquo; Satchell (saxophone/guitar), Cornelius Johnson (drums), and Ralph &amp;ldquo;Pee Wee&amp;rdquo; Middlebrooks (trumpet/trombone).
Are any of the original Ohio Players still alive? They were unable to resolve their disputes and the ensemble disbanded in 1980. Of the original Ohio Players, Clarence Satchell died at the age of 65 on December 30, 1995, Ralph Middlebrooks died on November 15, 1997, at the age of 78, Robert Ward died on December 25, 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Larry Mullen Jr a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-dave/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-dave/</guid>
      <description>How much is each member of U2 worth? The Irish group formed in 1976 consists of singer Bono, known name of Paul David Hewson ($700 million), guitarist The Edge, by-name of David Howell Evans ($400 million), bassist Adam Charles Clayton ($400 million), and drummer Larry Mullen ($300 million).Apr 6, 2021
Who is the richest rock star? Paul McCartney
Is Bono a billionaire? According to a leading media portal, Bono&amp;rsquo;s net worth as of 2020, is estimated to be roughly $700 million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Larry Mullen Jr a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-mullen-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-mullen-jr/</guid>
      <description>How much is each member of U2 worth? The Irish group formed in 1976 consists of singer Bono, known name of Paul David Hewson ($700 million), guitarist The Edge, by-name of David Howell Evans ($400 million), bassist Adam Charles Clayton ($400 million), and drummer Larry Mullen ($300 million).Apr 6, 2021
Who is the richest rock star? Paul McCartney
Is Bono a billionaire? According to a leading media portal, Bono&amp;rsquo;s net worth as of 2020, is estimated to be roughly $700 million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Matt Cameron a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/matt-cameron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/matt-cameron/</guid>
      <description>How was Matt Cameron in Soundgarden and Pearl Jam? If you think you heard Matt Cameron&amp;rsquo;s name before Pearl Jam, you are right. He rose to prominence as the drummer for Soundgarden, a Seattle-based rock band he joined in 1986. Soundgarden developed the grunge sound and became legendary worldwide, achieving its biggest success with the 1994 album “Superunknown.”
Where does Matt Cameron rank as a drummer? Prior to joining Soundgarden, Cameron was a member of the Seattle rock bands Bam Bam and Skin Yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Terry Bozzio Italian?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/terry-bozzio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/terry-bozzio/</guid>
      <description>Is Terry Bozzio married? Terry Bozzio/Spouse
Is Terry Bozzio Italian? Virtuoso drummer Terry John Bozzio was born on December 27, 1950 to Italian-American parents in San Francisco, California.
Who is Terry Bozzio married to? Terry Bozzio/Spouse
Are Dale and Terry Bozzio still married? During her work with Zappa, she met drummer Terry Bozzio in 1976. They married in 1979 after Terry had become a member of the band U.K. They divorced in 1986 with Dale retaining her married name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tomas Haake a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ralph-molina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ralph-molina/</guid>
      <description>What drums does Tomas Haake use? &amp;ldquo;To me, SONOR drums are the perfect symbiosis of sound, craftsmanship and inventive solutions down to even the most minute details! Reliable, thought-through, beautiful and most of all - They sound awesome!!!&amp;rdquo; Haake is noted for his technical abilities.
What snare does Tomas Haake use? Tomas Haake also uses Trick Pro1-V pedals, Evans heads (G2 Clear tom batters, G1 Clear tom resos, EMAD2 Clear bass batters, Hybrid snare batter, and Hazy 300 snare reso), Vic Firth Tomas Haake signature sticks, and Shure microphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tomas Haake a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tomas-haake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tomas-haake/</guid>
      <description>What drums does Tomas Haake use? &amp;ldquo;To me, SONOR drums are the perfect symbiosis of sound, craftsmanship and inventive solutions down to even the most minute details! Reliable, thought-through, beautiful and most of all - They sound awesome!!!&amp;rdquo; Haake is noted for his technical abilities.
What snare does Tomas Haake use? Tomas Haake also uses Trick Pro1-V pedals, Evans heads (G2 Clear tom batters, G1 Clear tom resos, EMAD2 Clear bass batters, Hybrid snare batter, and Hazy 300 snare reso), Vic Firth Tomas Haake signature sticks, and Shure microphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tony Williams related to Kanye?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joseph-zigaboo-modeliste/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joseph-zigaboo-modeliste/</guid>
      <description>Who did Miles Davis admire? More recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to keep up on all the &amp;rsquo;80s stuff. I had all of it, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really listened to it — Decoy, and those live albums. My favorite period was with Wayne Shorter, Ron Carter, Herbie Hancock, and Tony Williams.May 26, 2016
Who did Miles Davis get influenced by? He wanted someone who could play modal jazz, so he hired Bill Evans, a young pianist with a background in classical music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tony Williams related to Kanye?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-williams/</guid>
      <description>Who did Miles Davis admire? More recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to keep up on all the &amp;rsquo;80s stuff. I had all of it, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really listened to it — Decoy, and those live albums. My favorite period was with Wayne Shorter, Ron Carter, Herbie Hancock, and Tony Williams.May 26, 2016
Who did Miles Davis get influenced by? He wanted someone who could play modal jazz, so he hired Bill Evans, a young pianist with a background in classical music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-drumbo-french/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-drumbo-french/</guid>
      <description>Why did Vinnie Colaiuta leave Sting? After three intense and challenging years with Zappa, Vinnie decided that it was time to pursue his dream of becoming a session drummer and left the band with Frank&amp;rsquo;s blessing. &amp;ldquo;I wanted to play all different kind of music,&amp;rdquo; he explains.
Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer? Vinnie Colaiuta His contribution to the work of Sting, Frank Zappa, Joni Mitchell, Herbie Hancock, Chick Corea and Jeff Beck has for a good many years made him the go-to guy for any artists needing a man capable of absolute mastery of sublime rhythms, odd-time and incredible chops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vinnie-colaiuta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vinnie-colaiuta/</guid>
      <description>Why did Vinnie Colaiuta leave Sting? After three intense and challenging years with Zappa, Vinnie decided that it was time to pursue his dream of becoming a session drummer and left the band with Frank&amp;rsquo;s blessing. &amp;ldquo;I wanted to play all different kind of music,&amp;rdquo; he explains.
Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer? Vinnie Colaiuta His contribution to the work of Sting, Frank Zappa, Joni Mitchell, Herbie Hancock, Chick Corea and Jeff Beck has for a good many years made him the go-to guy for any artists needing a man capable of absolute mastery of sublime rhythms, odd-time and incredible chops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Clifton James in Dukes of Hazzard?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clifton-james/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clifton-james/</guid>
      <description>Who was JW in Man with the Golden Gun? actor Clifton James
Was Clifton James in the A team? The A-Team (TV Series 1983–1987) - Clifton James as Sheriff Jake Dawson, Warden Beale - IMDb.
Why was JW Pepper in The Man with the Golden Gun? Pepper as a racist small-town southern sheriff, setting him up for mockery as a foolish pompous figure that the audience is meant to side against.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Hal Blaine a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hal-blaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hal-blaine/</guid>
      <description>Was Hal Blaine a good drummer? Blaine was a prolific session player and by his estimation played on over 35,000 recordings, including 6,000 singles. He is widely regarded as one of the most in-demand drummers in rock and roll history, having &amp;ldquo;certainly played on more hit records than any drummer in the rock era&amp;rdquo;.
What drummer has 150 gold records? Hal Blaine
What cymbals did Hal Blaine use? Hal always used Zildjian cymbals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did Earl Young do?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-young/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-young/</guid>
      <description>Who designed the mushroom houses in Charlevoix Michigan? Earl Young
When was the Mushroom House built? The Studio (also known as the Mushroom House) is an ornately fanciful home built by architect Terry Brown in the Hyde Park neighborhood of Cincinnati, Ohio. The one-bedroom house features a cone shaped addition and a spiral staircase entry. It was built between 1992 and 2006.
Where are the mushroom houses located? Charlevoix, Michigan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What disease does Tommy Lee Jones have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-lee/</guid>
      <description>Who was the guy who stole Pam and Tommy tape? Rand Gauthier has become a household name again thanks to the Hulu series Pam and Tommy. The electrician became known for allegedly stealing the infamous Pamela Anderson and Tommy Lee sex tape in 1995.Feb 23, 2022
How did Pam and Tommy tape get stolen? In real life, Rand Gauthier did break in and steal the tape in 1995 after being unceremoniously fired without pay from doing contracting work on Pam and Tommy&amp;rsquo;s house renovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What disease does Travis Barker have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/travis-barker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/travis-barker/</guid>
      <description>Where does Travis Barker rank as a drummer? Today, Rolling Stone published its list of the “100 Greatest Drummers of All Time,” and spoiler: Meg White is ranked higher than U2&amp;rsquo;s Larry Mullen Jr. and Blink-182&amp;rsquo;s Travis Barker; Red Hot Chili Peppers&amp;rsquo; Chad Smith comes in at No. 64; Phil Collins is at No. 43; Tool&amp;rsquo;s Danny Carey and Dave Grohl are ranked No.Mar 31, 2016
Who is considered the best ever drummer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Bill Ward?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-ward/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-ward/</guid>
      <description>Did Black Sabbath regret firing Ozzy? On April 27, 1979, after various attempts to get Ozzy back on the team, Black Sabbath fired their lead singer. “We just couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue with Ozzy,” guitarist Tony Iommi said. “As much as everyone wanted us to, we just couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it. Nothing was happening and it would have meant the end of the band.Apr 27, 2022
What did Ozzy Osbourne do in Black Sabbath?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Carter Beauford?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carter-beauford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carter-beauford/</guid>
      <description>Is Carter Beauford still with DMB? Dave Matthews Band Members Stefan Lessard and Carter Beauford Reunite After Hiatus in Irvine. Dave Matthews Band bassist Stefan Lessard and drummer Carter Beauford rejoined the group for two performances in Irvine, Calif.Sep 12, 2021
Is Carter Beauford a great drummer? Carter Beauford is the groove-meister and founding member of The Dave Matthews Band. A powerhouse and technically gifted drummer, Carter&amp;rsquo;s open-handed approach to drums open him up to be an incredibly musical drummer, creating unique rhythms and grooves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Carter Beauford?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-dejohnette/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-dejohnette/</guid>
      <description>Is Carter Beauford a great drummer? Carter Beauford is the groove-meister and founding member of The Dave Matthews Band. A powerhouse and technically gifted drummer, Carter&amp;rsquo;s open-handed approach to drums open him up to be an incredibly musical drummer, creating unique rhythms and grooves.Nov 2, 2021
How much does Carter Beauford make? Carter Beauford net worth: Carter Beauford is an American musician, drummer, and percussionist who has a net worth of $65 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Carter Beauford?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ramon-tiki-fullwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ramon-tiki-fullwood/</guid>
      <description>Is Carter Beauford a great drummer? Carter Beauford is the groove-meister and founding member of The Dave Matthews Band. A powerhouse and technically gifted drummer, Carter&amp;rsquo;s open-handed approach to drums open him up to be an incredibly musical drummer, creating unique rhythms and grooves.Nov 2, 2021
How much does Carter Beauford make? Carter Beauford net worth: Carter Beauford is an American musician, drummer, and percussionist who has a net worth of $65 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Meg White?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/meg-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/meg-white/</guid>
      <description>When did Meg and Jack break up? After a long hiatus with no new releases, the duo reported that they were disbanding. Taking to their official website on 2 February 2011, they wrote: &amp;ldquo;The reason is not due to artistic differences or lack of wanting to continue, nor any health issues as both Meg and Jack are feeling fine and in good health.Mar 30, 2022
Are Jack and Meg still married?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Cozy Powell?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cozy-powell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cozy-powell/</guid>
      <description>Was COSY Powell a good drummer? He is one of the best drummers the hard rock and metal industry has ever had. Cozy was best described as talented, reliable, and versatile. Talented because he was an innovator. He came up with different styles of making music every time he held the drums.Jul 14, 2021
Who is the best technical drummer? Having played drums since the age of two, Virgil Donati is regarded as one of the most technically proficient drummers in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to football player Steve Smith?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/fred-below/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/fred-below/</guid>
      <description>Who is Smitty on NBA TV? NBA Champion Steve Smith is a studio analyst for NBA TV, appearing on the network multiple nights each week. A star guard at Michigan State, Smith had a 14-year NBA career playing for the Miami Heat, Atlanta Hawks, Portland Trail Blazers, San Antonio Spurs, New Orleans Hornets and Charlotte Bobcats.
Did Stevin Smith play in the NBA? Professional basketball career During the 1997 NBA season, Smith signed two consecutive 10-day contracts with the Dallas Mavericks, and received his only NBA playing time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to football player Steve Smith?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-smith/</guid>
      <description>Where did Steve Smith go? NFL.com Analyst joins the NFL Network as an analyst after 16 seasons in the NFL. Smith will appear on numerous NFL Network shows, including NFL GameDay First during the NFL season, which airs every NFL Sunday at 7 a.m. ET.
Is Steve Smith Sr still in the NFL? Steve Smith Sr. Smith Sr. last played in the NFL back in 2016 with the Baltimore Ravens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Jeff Porcaro?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-porcaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-porcaro/</guid>
      <description>Who from Toto died? Mike Porcaro
Why did Bobby leave Toto? The late drummer Jeff Porcaro, Toto co-founder, was designated band spokesperson on the day he was asked to leave, Kimball said. “I was told that I didn&amp;rsquo;t follow rules. Well, I really didn&amp;rsquo;t like taking orders from anyone.”Jun 27, 2011
Who is the current lead singer of Toto? Toto/Lead singers
How many lead singers did Toto have? Today Toto is comprised of four key members: Lukather, Paich, Steve Porcaro and Joseph Williams, the singer who first fronted the group in the late 80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Jimmy Chamberlin?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-chamberlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-chamberlin/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Jimmy Chamberlain? He is currently active under the Jimmy Chamberlin Complex name. In addition to his current work as CEO, Chamberlin has joined Chicago jazz saxophonist Frank Catalano for a string of 2013–15 performances in the Chicago area. An EP by Catalano and Chamberlin Love Supreme Collective - EP was released on July 29, 2014.
What happened to the lead singer of the Smashing Pumpkins? He is best known as the lead singer, primary songwriter, guitarist, and only permanent member of the rock band the Smashing Pumpkins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Keith Moon?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/keith-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/keith-moon/</guid>
      <description>Was Keith Moon a fast drummer? Generally speaking, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to hear the drums as the lead instrument in a song by a four-piece band, but that&amp;rsquo;s the case here. After 35 seconds of subtlety, Moon&amp;rsquo;s hyper-fast drumming goes to work, starting and stopping at various points during the song, essentially controlling the entire dynamic.Aug 23, 2015
Who is considered the greatest drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Levon Helm?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/levon-helm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/levon-helm/</guid>
      <description>Why did Levon Helm not like The Last Waltz? In his 1993 memoir This Wheel&amp;rsquo;s On Fire, Helm details his dissatisfaction with The Last Waltz: Scorsese, he claims, focused on and exalted Robbie Robertson, the Band&amp;rsquo;s songwriter and frequent frontman, to the near exclusion of everyone else in the group.Apr 20, 2012
What happened to Richard Manuel? Richard Manuel, the singer, pianist, songwriter and occasional drummer with the rock group the Band, was found dead Tuesday in his motel room in Winter Park, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Steven Adler?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steven-adler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steven-adler/</guid>
      <description>Who is touring with Guns N Roses 2021? Mammoth WVH
Will Steven Adler rejoin Guns N Roses? Drummer Steven Adler&amp;rsquo;s campaign to rejoin Guns N&amp;rsquo; Roses full-time alongside Slash and Duff McKagan fell short a couple years ago, but the band is still celebrating Adler&amp;rsquo;s guest appearances on the &amp;lsquo;Not in This Lifetime&amp;rsquo; tour.Jul 14, 2021
Why isn&amp;rsquo;t Steven Adler playing with guns and roses? &amp;lsquo;” Adler was fired in 1990 after his addiction issues ran out of control, while Stradlin left the following year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What illness did Ginger Baker have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ginger-baker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ginger-baker/</guid>
      <description>What illness did Ginger Baker die of? chronic obstructive pulmonary disease
What happened to Ginger Baker after Cream? Ginger Baker, performing with Cream in 1966. There are lots of firsts and superlatives in the career of Ginger Baker, the drummer and bandleader who died Sunday morning at age 80. His death was announced by his family on social media; they had said on Sept.Oct 6, 2019
Who is still alive from Cream?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Gene Krupa known for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gene-krupa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gene-krupa/</guid>
      <description>Was Gene Krupa the best drummer? Krupa&amp;rsquo;s reputation still looms large in pop culture: Rolling Stone recently put him at Number 7 in its list of the 100 greatest drummers of all time. Yet among jazz critics and historians, and many musicians, it has become part of the received wisdom that Krupa was an unmusical drummer, and that he played too loud.Mar 15, 2018
Can Gene Krupa read music? Gene moved to New York in 1929 and was recruited by Red Nichols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was Charlie Watts illness?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-watts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-watts/</guid>
      <description>What was the official cause of death of Charlie Watts? Throat Cancer Symptoms As Cause of Rolling Stones&amp;rsquo; Charlie Watts Death Unconfirmed. Charlie Watts, legendary drummer for the Rolling Stones, died at the age of 80 on Sunday.Aug 25, 2021
What sickness did Charlie Watts have? Watts, a smoker until the 1980s, was diagnosed with throat cancer in 2004. He is said to have fully recovered.Aug 25, 2021
How did Charlie from Rolling Stones died?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What were John Bonham&#39;s last words?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bonham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bonham/</guid>
      <description>What is the most famous drum beat? I was definitely curious, so I did some research and found that the “Funky Drummer” beat by Clyde Stubblefield has been the most sampled drum groove ever (over 7 million times!). It&amp;rsquo;s just a basic 16th note groove, but the hi-hat part, ghost notes, and overall feel make this beat one of the hardest to play.Oct 24, 2021
Who is considered the greatest drummer of all time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Jerry Allison now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerry-allison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerry-allison/</guid>
      <description>Is Buddy Holly&amp;rsquo;s wife still alive today? Buddy Holly&amp;rsquo;s widow Maria Elena Holly is still alive today, and although their time together was short, they share a love story that won&amp;rsquo;t soon be forgotten. Buddy Holly met Maria Elena Santiago while visiting Peer-Southern music publishing company in New York City, where Maria worked as a receptionist.Feb 3, 2022
Where did Buddy Holly grow up? Lubbock
Who was Buddy Holly&amp;rsquo;s guitarist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Max Weinberg now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/max-weinberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/max-weinberg/</guid>
      <description>Why is Conan&amp;rsquo;s band leaving? After many years on the air, Jimmy Vivino and the Basic Cable Band made their final appearance on tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode. Host Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien discussed the show&amp;rsquo;s format shift, expressing his sadness that his band wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be joining him in the new year.Oct 4, 2018
Are Conan and Max Weinberg still friends? “I don&amp;rsquo;t know why Max and Conan aren&amp;rsquo;t together anymore,” E Street guitarist Steven Van Zandt told Rolling Stone after it was revealed that Weinberg was permanently leaving Conan&amp;rsquo;s house band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michael Shrieve today?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-shrieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-shrieve/</guid>
      <description>How good of a drummer is Michael Shrieve? Over the course of his prolific career, musician Michael Shrieve has written, produced and played on albums that have sold millions of copies worldwide. In 2016, Rolling Stone listed him among the “100 Greatest Drummers,” and in 2011 the same magazine&amp;rsquo;s readers chose him as one of the “Top 10 Drummers of All Time.”
What happened to the drummer for Santana at Woodstock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who did Earl Palmer play for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-palmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-palmer/</guid>
      <description>Was Gene Krupa the best drummer? Krupa&amp;rsquo;s reputation still looms large in pop culture: Rolling Stone recently put him at Number 7 in its list of the 100 greatest drummers of all time. Yet among jazz critics and historians, and many musicians, it has become part of the received wisdom that Krupa was an unmusical drummer, and that he played too loud.Mar 15, 2018
Can Gene Krupa read music? Gene moved to New York in 1929 and was recruited by Red Nichols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who did Steve Jordan drum for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-jordan/</guid>
      <description>Who is John Mayer&amp;rsquo;s current drummer? Aaron Sterling (born July 9, 1980) is an American drummer, producer, engineer, and session musician who lives in Los Angeles.
Who is Steve Ferrone playing with now? In 2019, Ferrone recorded session drums for Stroke 9&amp;rsquo;s studio album Calafrio. On 10 July 2019, Ferrone was inducted into the Brighton Music Walk of Fame in his hometown of Brighton, England. On 1 Feb 2022, it was announced that Ferrone would be a part of the band for John Mayer&amp;rsquo;s Sob Rock Tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is considered the greatest drummer of All Time?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jr-robinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jr-robinson/</guid>
      <description>What was Michael Jackson&amp;rsquo;s last words before he died? “I can&amp;rsquo;t function if I don&amp;rsquo;t sleep. They&amp;rsquo;ll have to cancel it. “And I don&amp;rsquo;t want them to cancel it, but they will have to cancel it.” According to the doctor who was the last person to see the singer before he was rushed to hospital, these were his final words.Mar 17, 2021
What was the last word Michael Jackson said?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is John jab?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clyde-stubblefield-and-john-jabo-starks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clyde-stubblefield-and-john-jabo-starks/</guid>
      <description>Who invented the funky drummer beat? James Brown released a seven-inch single called Funky Drummer in March, 1970 – a loosely arranged jam session showcasing the talent for improvisation of drummer Clyde Stubblefield, who was employed in Brown&amp;rsquo;s band at the time.Mar 26, 2020
Who started the funk sound in music? James Brown
What is funk drumming? Funk drumming often features syncopation and rhythmic displacement, rudiment-based hand patterns, hi-hat openings, ghost notes, and linear patterns—when no two limbs play at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Questlove and what is his background?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ahmir-questlove-thompson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ahmir-questlove-thompson/</guid>
      <description>Who are the parents of Questlove? Questlove/Parents
Who is Questlove and what is his background? Ahmir Khalib Thompson aka “Questlove” hails from Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and was born January 20, 1971. He is a drummer, DJ, producer, culinary entrepreneur, designer, New York Times bestselling and James Beard Award-nominated author, and cofounder of Philadelphia&amp;rsquo;s most influential hip-hop group, the Roots.
Is Questlove&amp;rsquo;s father Lee Andrews? &amp;lsquo;Roots&amp;rsquo; Drummer Questlove On His Late Father Lee Andrews Fifties doo-wop singer Lee Andrews died Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who played drums in Aretha Franklin Respect?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roger-hawkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roger-hawkins/</guid>
      <description>Do people still record at Muscle Shoals? Muscle Shoals Sound&amp;rsquo;s business model relies heavily on merch sales and studio tours. Recording sessions and fundraisers comprise Muscle Shoals Sounds&amp;rsquo; third-largest revenue stream. In 2018, after renovations, Muscle Shoals Sound began hosting recording sessions again.Jun 23, 2020
Is Muscle Shoals still making music? Still a working studio, this is where the Muscle Shoals Rhythm Section got its start. FAME was host to artists such as Aretha Franklin, Wilson Pickett, Duane Allman, Otis Redding, the Osmonds, Paul Anka and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Nirvana&#39;s first drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dale-crover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dale-crover/</guid>
      <description>Who was Nirvana&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Aaron Burckhard
How many drummers did Nirvana have? Grohl joined the grunge outfit in 1990, replacing &amp;lsquo;Bleach&amp;rsquo; drummer Chad Channing. Dale Crover and Dave Foster had previously played drums in Nirvana, while the band had also worked with session musicians Mark Pickerel and Dan Peters.Apr 6, 2018
Why did the original drummer leave Nirvana? During the sessions, Cobain and Novoselic became disenchanted with Channing&amp;rsquo;s drumming, and Channing expressed frustration at not being actively involved in songwriting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Nirvana&#39;s first drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/greg-errico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/greg-errico/</guid>
      <description>Who was Nirvana&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Aaron Burckhard
How many drummers did Nirvana have? Grohl joined the grunge outfit in 1990, replacing &amp;lsquo;Bleach&amp;rsquo; drummer Chad Channing. Dale Crover and Dave Foster had previously played drums in Nirvana, while the band had also worked with session musicians Mark Pickerel and Dan Peters.Apr 6, 2018
Why did the original drummer leave Nirvana? During the sessions, Cobain and Novoselic became disenchanted with Channing&amp;rsquo;s drumming, and Channing expressed frustration at not being actively involved in songwriting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Nirvana&#39;s first drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerome-bigfoot-brailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerome-bigfoot-brailey/</guid>
      <description>Who was Nirvana&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Aaron Burckhard
How many drummers did Nirvana have? Grohl joined the grunge outfit in 1990, replacing &amp;lsquo;Bleach&amp;rsquo; drummer Chad Channing. Dale Crover and Dave Foster had previously played drums in Nirvana, while the band had also worked with session musicians Mark Pickerel and Dan Peters.Apr 6, 2018
Why did the original drummer leave Nirvana? During the sessions, Cobain and Novoselic became disenchanted with Channing&amp;rsquo;s drumming, and Channing expressed frustration at not being actively involved in songwriting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Sheila E to Prince?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sheila-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sheila-e/</guid>
      <description>Did Sheila E and Prince have a relationship? Sheila E. joined Prince&amp;rsquo;s backing band as their romance grew, and as she recalled in a 2016 Billboard interview, they became briefly engaged after Prince proposed in 1987. However, by the 1988-89 Lovesexy Tour their relationship fractured, and Sheila E. subsequently left Prince and the band once it came to a close.Jan 24, 2021
Why did Sheila E not marry Prince? “We just grew apart,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the drummer for the Ohio Players?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-diamond-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-diamond-williams/</guid>
      <description>Who is the woman on the Ohio Players album cover? Ester Cordet
Who is on the Ohio Players album cover? Ester Cordet
Where did the Ohio Players record? The Ohio Players released their debut album, Pain, in 1971 on Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Westbound Records, a label shared by George Clinton&amp;rsquo;s Funkadelic band. They followed their debut with Pleasure a year later, then Ecstasy in 1973.
Who was the guitar player in Ohio Players?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the Motown drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/benny-benjamin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/benny-benjamin/</guid>
      <description>Where did the Funk Brothers name come from? In the Standing in the Shadows of Motown documentary, Joe Hunter stated that the name &amp;ldquo;The Funk Brothers&amp;rdquo; came from Benny Benjamin.
How many of the Funk Brothers are still living? While Motown recordings utilized many musicians, the film focused on 13 players, of whom five were already dead. Just four Funk Brothers are alive now. Jones is survived by his wife, June, and three children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the singer for Bad Brains?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-hudson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-hudson/</guid>
      <description>What happened to the lead singer of Bad Brains? Singer Chuck Mosley, who had played with Bad Brains in the early 1990s, died in November 2017. Sid McCray died in September 2020.
Who inspired Bad Brains? Bad Brains formed in Washington in the late &amp;rsquo;70s, first as Mind Power, a jazz fusion group inspired by Chick Corea and Mahavishnu Orchestra, but eventually changed its name and vision after discovering the Sex Pistols and the Damned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did ACDC fire Phil Rudd?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-rudd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-rudd/</guid>
      <description>Is ACDC drummer good? In my humble opinion, Phil Rudd was the foundation of the AC/DC, always consistent, always on time, and always holding it down. His timing and precision are impeccable and if you ask me, He&amp;rsquo;s one of the best drummers… in the world!
Who was the bald drummer for ACDC? Chris Slade
Why did AC DC have so many drummers? During the 2015-2016 Rock or Bust tour, three different members of AC/DC were taken out of action by serious medical problems (Malcolm Young, Brian Johnson) and legal issues (Phil Rudd, arguably self-inflicted) over the past couple of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Bill Bruford quit drumming?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-bruford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-bruford/</guid>
      <description>Why did Bill Bruford leave Genesis? Later in 1978, Bruford reunited with John Wetton and formed the progressive rock group U.K. After their debut album U.K. (1978) and several tours, Holdsworth and Bruford left the group due to disagreements on the group&amp;rsquo;s musical direction.
When did Bill Bruford leave Genesis? July 19, 1972
When was Bill Bruford in King Crimson? Bruford played in King Crimson for his third and final tenure from 1994–1997, after which he continued with a new acoustic configuration of Earthworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did David Garibaldi leave Tower of Power?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-garibaldi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-garibaldi/</guid>
      <description>Why did David Garibaldi leave Tower of Power? After ten years with Tower, in 1980 Garibaldi felt it was time to move on and left the San Francisco Bay Area for Los Angeles, with the hopes of building a career in the studios.
Who is the lead singer of Tower of Power today? For the past few years, Marcus Scott has been making a name for himself as the lead singer of the legendary band Tower of Power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Ian Paice leave Whitesnake?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ian-paice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ian-paice/</guid>
      <description>Why did Richie Blackmore leave Deep Purple? Blackmore&amp;rsquo;s marriage had broken down and he was going through the process of a messy divorce. He would later sum up his input on the album as, “There wasn&amp;rsquo;t as much guitar because in a way I was going through more personal problems, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the people there that I wanted to record with.
Who did Tommy Bolin replace in Deep Purple?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Janet Weiss leave Sleater?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/janet-weiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/janet-weiss/</guid>
      <description>When did Janet Weiss leave Sleater-Kinney? Ultimately, Weiss decided the shift in her role signaled it was “time for me to move on,” as Weiss tweeted in July 2019 after announcing her split from the group.Nov 20, 2019
Is Sleater-Kinney still together? Sleater-Kinney Releases A Last Album, Ending An Era For the Indie Rock Trio : NPR. Sleater-Kinney Releases A Last Album, Ending An Era For the Indie Rock Trio Sleater-Kinney&amp;rsquo;s longtime drummer is leaving the band — but not before they release one last album together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Lombardo leave Slayer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-lombardo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-lombardo/</guid>
      <description>Is Dave Lombardo one of the best drummers? The innovator of thrash drumming has been beating drum kits into submission for 40 years. Having sat atop the drum throne for Slayer, Fantomas, Dead Cross and many others, Lombardo is always in the conversation for the best drummer on earth. Lombardo&amp;rsquo;s drumming the most consistent aspect of Slayer&amp;rsquo;s legendary career.May 6, 2019
What is the band Slayers net worth? 11- Slayer And the members have retired in 2018, after making their final world tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Mick Avory leave the Rolling Stones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-avory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-avory/</guid>
      <description>Who is considered the greatest rock drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.Sep 14, 2021
Who is the goat of drumming? Neil Peart, Rush – The G.O.A.T.Sep 10, 2015 Why did Mick Taylor quit Rolling Stones? Taylor admitted in the documentary Crossfire Hurricane that he had become addicted to heroin while living in the eye of the Rolling Stones maelstrom and decided to leave to try to protect his family from the band&amp;rsquo;s caustic lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Mick Avory leave the Rolling Stones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/micky-waller/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/micky-waller/</guid>
      <description>Who is considered the greatest rock drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.Sep 14, 2021
Who is the goat of drumming? Neil Peart, Rush – The G.O.A.T.Sep 10, 2015 Why did Mick Taylor quit Rolling Stones? Taylor admitted in the documentary Crossfire Hurricane that he had become addicted to heroin while living in the eye of the Rolling Stones maelstrom and decided to leave to try to protect his family from the band&amp;rsquo;s caustic lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Phil Collins go deaf?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-collins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-collins/</guid>
      <description>What vocal effect does Phil Collins use? Sounds about right. the AMS 1580 dual delay harmoniser is what is used on phil collins vocal along with a Lexicon reverb probably a 300.Feb 15, 2008
Who are Phil Collins 5 children? His five children, Joely, Simon, Lily, Nicholas and Matthew, are equally as talented and have started to take over Hollywood. When he was just 5 years old, Phil had already begun to play the drums and set his sights on making it into the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Scotty Moore stop playing with Elvis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/d-j-fontana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/d-j-fontana/</guid>
      <description>Who performed Jailhouse Rock? Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s
What happened to Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s band after he died? Tours with other musicians: After the TCB Band disbanded Before Presley&amp;rsquo;s death in 1977, several former members from the TCB Band went on to form Emmylou Harris&amp;rsquo;s Hot Band and The John Denver Band. These musicians include James Burton, Glen D.
Who was Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Dominic Joseph Fontana
Who was the drummer Jailhouse Rock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did the Grateful Dead have two drummers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mickey-hart-and-bill-kreutzmann/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mickey-hart-and-bill-kreutzmann/</guid>
      <description>When did the Grateful Dead have two drummers? 1967- 68. Toward the end of 1967, the Dead were rapidly developing their reputation as a mind-blowing live act. To expand their sound, they brought in Mickey Hart on drums and percussion. The addition of a second drummer gave the band a distinct power, not only in live performances but in the studio too.Nov 12, 2014
What is the point of two drummers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Tommy quit the Ramones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-ramone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-ramone/</guid>
      <description>What made the Ramones great? Ramones was the first so-called punk album. It made us think: “We&amp;rsquo;d better crack on here.” But the Ramones and the Pistols were different animals, with a different flavour. They were more basic, three-chord rock&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;roll. Great songs, really catchy, all two and a half minutes long.Feb 2, 2016
Did the Ramones do drugs? He had used hard drugs since he was a child, had been diagnosed as bipolar, and often mixed mood-disorder medications with cocaine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Elvin Jones is important?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/elvin-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/elvin-jones/</guid>
      <description>Why did Elvin Jones leave Coltrane? But in 1966, Jones left Coltrane&amp;rsquo;s group after Coltrane decided to add a second drummer, a decision Jones felt was inconsistent with his own musical direction. Coltrane died the next year. Jones went to Europe, played with Duke Ellington&amp;rsquo;s band for a couple of weeks and returned to the United States.May 20, 2004
When did McCoy Tyner leave Coltrane? 1965
Why Elvin Jones is important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is John Stanier cymbal so high?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/glenn-kotche/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/glenn-kotche/</guid>
      <description>Why is John Stanier&amp;rsquo;s cymbal so high? John: I didn&amp;rsquo;t want any cymbals but the hi-hats at first. Then I was like, “Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll use one,” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want it near me because I&amp;rsquo;d use it too much. So I set it high so I&amp;rsquo;d have to work to get to it. I wanted it to be significant; I use it as a marker.
Why did Helmet break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is John Stanier cymbal so high?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-stanier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-stanier/</guid>
      <description>Why is John Stanier&amp;rsquo;s cymbal so high? John: I didn&amp;rsquo;t want any cymbals but the hi-hats at first. Then I was like, “Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll use one,” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want it near me because I&amp;rsquo;d use it too much. So I set it high so I&amp;rsquo;d have to work to get to it. I wanted it to be significant; I use it as a marker.
Why did Helmet break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is John Stanier cymbal so high?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ronald-shannon-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ronald-shannon-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Why is John Stanier&amp;rsquo;s cymbal so high? John: I didn&amp;rsquo;t want any cymbals but the hi-hats at first. Then I was like, “Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll use one,” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want it near me because I&amp;rsquo;d use it too much. So I set it high so I&amp;rsquo;d have to work to get to it. I wanted it to be significant; I use it as a marker.
Why did Helmet break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Steve Gadd so good?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-gadd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-gadd/</guid>
      <description>Who played drums on Frosty the Snowman? Description: This holiday classic is always a favorite of young people, and Mike Lewis&amp;rsquo; swinging jazz chart is ideal for the younger band. Mike has come up with some clever ideas for this one, yet this chart will require only minimal rehearsal time.
Who plays drums with Paul Simon? Steve Gadd is the longest band member in Paul Simons group, starting to play with him in 1975.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why was Buddy Rich dishonorably discharged?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buddy-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buddy-rich/</guid>
      <description>Is Buddy Rich the greatest drummer of all time? Buddy Rich has been called the greatest jazz drummer of all time—a statement that few would argue with. Buddy was born on September 30, 1917, and his drumming career spanned seven decades, beginning when he was just eighteen months old and continuing until his death on April 2, 1987.
Who is considered the greatest drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why was Carlton Barrett shot?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carlton-barrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carlton-barrett/</guid>
      <description>What was Carlton Barrett contribution to reggae music? Carlton Barrett is featured on all the albums recorded by the Wailers. Barrett popularised the one drop rhythm, a percussive drumming style created by Winston Grennan. With Carly&amp;rsquo;s beats and his brother Aston&amp;rsquo;s bass, the Wailer rhythm section planted the seeds of today&amp;rsquo;s international reggae.
Why was Carlton Barrett shot? Carlton Barrett, 35, drummer in the band led by the late Bob Marley, was shot dead at the gate to his home in 1987.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Jennifer Nettles and Kristian Bush married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kristian-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kristian-bush/</guid>
      <description>What does Jennifer Nettles do now? Nettles is currently a judge on Go-Big Show (2021).
Is Jennifer Nettles married to Kristian Bush? According to People, Nettles married Miller, an entrepreneur, in a small and private ceremony at Blackberry Farm in the Smoky Mountains of Tennessee with a small group of friends and family present, including Nettles&amp;rsquo; longtime bandmate Kristian Bush.Sep 1, 2021
Is Sugarland still together 2020? With only a couple weeks to go before the scheduled start of their 2020 There Goes the Neighborhood Tour, Sugarland have canceled the entire run of shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Michael Stipe and Peter Buck friends?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-buck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-buck/</guid>
      <description>What is Peter Buck&amp;rsquo;s net worth? 261 on the Forbes 400 list of wealthiest people, with an estimated net worth of $1.6 billion.
Are Michael Stipe and Peter Buck friends? Stipe, Buck and Mills haven&amp;rsquo;t regretted the decision, and Stipe suggests it salvaged their friendship. Buck and Mills both remain active musically as Stipe, until recently, stuck to visual art.Nov 20, 2019
What is Mike Mills of R.E.M. doing now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Kenny Burrell doing?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kenny-burrell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kenny-burrell/</guid>
      <description>Is Kenny Burrell black or white? *Kenny Burrell was born this date in 1931. He is a Black jazz guitarist known for his work on the Blue Note label. Kenneth Earl Burrell was born in Detroit, Michigan. Both his parents played instruments and he began playing guitar at the age of 12 after listening Charlie Christian&amp;rsquo;s recordings.
Is Kenny Burrell black or white? *Kenny Burrell was born this date in 1931.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Charlie Burchill?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-burchill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-burchill/</guid>
      <description>Is Jim Kerr still married? Kerr married Chrissie Hynde, lead singer of The Pretenders, in 1984 (divorced in 1990). They had one daughter named Yasmin. He subsequently married actress Patsy Kensit in 1992 (divorced in 1996) with whom he had a son named James (born September 1993). Jim Kerr is a Celtic fan and an active supporter of the club.
Who is Jim kerrs wife? Jim Kerr/Wife
How many wives has Jim Kerr?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is David Byrne in a relationship?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-byrne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-byrne/</guid>
      <description>What happened to lead singer of Talking Heads? In December 1991, Talking Heads announced that they had disbanded. Frantz said that he learned that Byrne had left from an article in the Los Angeles Times, and said: &amp;ldquo;As far as we&amp;rsquo;re concerned, the band never really broke up. David just decided to leave.&amp;rdquo;
What type of music is David Byrne? David Byrne/Genres
How many instruments can David Byrne play? Byrne recounted these events when he appeared on Desert Island Discs on BBC Radio 4 on 18 March 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Ely Buendia friends with Eraserheads?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ely-buendia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ely-buendia/</guid>
      <description>Are Eraserhead members friends? MANILA, Philippines — Original Pilipino Music (OPM) icon Ely Buendia revealed that he and other members of his &amp;rsquo;90s band Eraserheads were never really friends. In the podcast “Wake Up With Jim &amp;amp; Saab,” the former Eraserheads frontman said they&amp;rsquo;re not Itchyworms nor Parokya ni Edgar that&amp;rsquo;s why they broke up.May 27, 2021
Did Eraserhead disband? The Eraserheads, considered as one of the biggest bands in OPM, disbanded in 2002 after over a decade of making music together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Jimmy Buffett a billionaire?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-buffett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-buffett/</guid>
      <description>Does Warren Buffett have a brother? Howard Graham Buffett - Wikipedia.
Where is Jimmy Buffett now? Today, he is a regular visitor to the Caribbean island of Saint Barts and other islands where he gets inspiration for many of his songs and some of the characters in his books. With the untimely death of friend and mentor Jim Croce in September 1973, ABC/Dunhill Records tapped Buffett to fill his space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was James Burton a good guitarist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-burton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-burton/</guid>
      <description>Who invented chicken pickin guitar? A session ace, sideman to the stars and contributor to a laundry list of hit records, James Burton remains one of the Telecaster&amp;rsquo;s greatest exponents.Apr 30, 2019
Who invented hybrid picking? Isaac Guillory (born 1947) Made it his signature technique. Rory Gallagher (1948–1995) Hybrid picking was used most notably and most often in his acoustic playing, in songs such as &amp;lsquo;Unmilitary Two-Step&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Out on the Western Plain&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;Pistol Slapper blues&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Jeff Buckley&#39;s death an accident?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-buckley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-buckley/</guid>
      <description>How do you get the Arctic Monkeys guitar tone? The Quick Answer. To get the Arctic Monkeys guitar tone, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a crunchy overdriven tone by either having the gain setting on your amp midway, or use an overdriven pedal through a clean amp. Have the gain, mids and treble higher for lead sections and then decrease the gain and mids lower for rhythm sections.
What happened to Tim Buckley?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Roy Buchanan asked to join the Rolling Stones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roy-buchanan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roy-buchanan/</guid>
      <description>Did Roy Buchanan turn down the Rolling Stones? These days he&amp;rsquo;s as infamous for apparently turning down an offer to join the Rolling Stones and his mysterious death in a Virginia jail cell in 1988 as he is for his music. Yet Buchanan&amp;rsquo;s legacy as a guitarist punches way above that of many of the rock stars who held him in such high regard.Jun 19, 2019
Could Roy Buchanan read music?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did Lindsey Buckingham do to Stevie Nicks?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lindsey-buckingham/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lindsey-buckingham/</guid>
      <description>How come Stevie Nicks never had children? Stevie Nicks has said that she consciously chose not to have children of her own, due to her demanding career and desire to follow her art: &amp;ldquo;My mission maybe wasn&amp;rsquo;t to be a mom and a wife; maybe my particular mission was to write songs to make moms and wives feel better.&amp;ldquo;Dec 30, 2020
How many daughters does Stevie Nicks have? Dia Dipasupil/Getty ImagesShe&amp;rsquo;s been married once, albeit very briefly, but Stevie Nicks has never had children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does RL stand for Burnside?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/r-l-burnside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/r-l-burnside/</guid>
      <description>What kind of music is RL Burnside? Blues hill country blues
What tuning is RL Burnside? open-G tuning
Did RL Burnside shoot someone? Back in the south, Burnside shot a man who had wanted to run him off his land. The judge asked Burnside if he intended to kill the man, and he replied: &amp;ldquo;It was between him and the Lord, him dyin&amp;rsquo;. I just shot him in the head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What guitar did Charlie Byrd play?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-byrd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-byrd/</guid>
      <description>What instrument did Charlie Byrd play? guitar
Who played with Charlie Byrd? In 1959, they joined Woody Herman&amp;rsquo;s band and toured Europe for three weeks as part of a State Department-sponsored goodwill tour. The other members of the band were Vince Guaraldi, Bill Harris, Nat Adderley and drummer Jimmy Campbell. Byrd led his own groups that sometimes featured his brother Joe.
What happened to Charlie Byrd? Charlie Byrd, the classically trained jazz guitar virtuoso who was a fixture on the Washington music scene for nearly 50 years and who helped introduce bossa nova to the United States, died of cancer yesterday at his home in Annapolis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Benjamin Burnley?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ben-burnley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ben-burnley/</guid>
      <description>What is wrong with the lead singer of Breaking Benjamin? Breaking Benjamin frontman Ben Burnley says he copes with his mystery illness by using the chronic pain to fuel his live shows. He&amp;rsquo;s suffered from joint and muscle pain for years but says he has been given no answers despite consulting hundreds of doctors.Jul 7, 2015
What kind of guitar does Breaking Benjamin play? Benjamin plays his music primarily on the BB-600 Baritone from the Signature LTD Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Benjamin Burnley?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/christian-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/christian-burns/</guid>
      <description>What is wrong with the lead singer of Breaking Benjamin? Breaking Benjamin frontman Ben Burnley says he copes with his mystery illness by using the chronic pain to fuel his live shows. He&amp;rsquo;s suffered from joint and muscle pain for years but says he has been given no answers despite consulting hundreds of doctors.Jul 7, 2015
What kind of guitar does Breaking Benjamin play? Benjamin plays his music primarily on the BB-600 Baritone from the Signature LTD Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Buckethead?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buckethead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buckethead/</guid>
      <description>Is Buckethead a derogatory term? The term &amp;ldquo;buckethead&amp;rdquo; referred to stormtroopers. &amp;ldquo;Buckethead&amp;rdquo; (also spelled &amp;ldquo;bucket-head&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bucket head&amp;rdquo;) was a derogatory nickname used to refer to stormtroopers during the reign of the Galactic Empire, or others wearing similar armor.
Who was Buckethead? Brian Patrick Carroll
How did Buckethead get his name? &amp;ldquo;I just put it on my head and I looked in the mirror. And I was like &amp;lsquo;That&amp;rsquo;s Buckethead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is John Butler&#39;s religion?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-butler/</guid>
      <description>Is John Butler still married? Butler is married to Danielle Caruana, an Australian musician and vocalist who performs under the name of Mama Kin. They have two children, a daughter and a son.
Is Mama Kin John Butlers wife? Four years ago Butler, wife Danielle Caruana (also known as musician Mama Kin) and their teenage kids, daughter Banjo and son Jahli, moved to a 2.8ha property just outside Margs.Sep 29, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Jonny Buckland worth?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jonny-buckland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jonny-buckland/</guid>
      <description>Which guitar does Chris Martin use? Gibson Blues King Acoustic Guitar.
Who plays the electric guitar in Coldplay? Jonny Buckland
Which guitar does Coldplay use? The ultimate &amp;ldquo;Coldplay Guitar&amp;rdquo; is without any doubt the Fender Telecaster Thinline a semi hollow electric guitar. Jon uses several models of this guitar, which is really cool: basically, a semi-hollow Telecaster with f-holes and humbuckers.Jan 21, 2009
Does Chris Martin own Martin Guitars? Chris Martin IV took the reins of the business – which has been owned by the Martin family for six generations – following the death of his grandfather and mentor, CF Martin III, in 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Mark Bryan now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-bryan/</guid>
      <description>Where did Michael Bruce live? Early life Michael Owen Bruce was born to Alvin and Ruth (Owen) Bruce. The Bruce and Owen families had moved to Arizona from Kansas.
Who was Michael Bruce? Michael Bruce, (born March 27, 1746, Kinnesswood, Kinross-shire [now Perth and Kinross], Scot. —died July 5, 1767, Kinnesswood), Scottish poet whose works were allegedly “stolen” by the poet John Logan, provoking a long-lasting controversy.Mar 23, 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Michael Bruce?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-bruno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-bruno/</guid>
      <description>What has happened to Purplebricks? Purplebricks announced the closure of its Australian business in May 2019, followed by the closure of its US operation two months later.Jan 17, 2022
Why did ComFree change to Purplebricks? The Canadian business, set up via the acquisition of DuProprio/ComFree in July 2018 for around £29 million, was the only business that was successful. This signaled the end of PurpleBricks expansion into overseas markets and its ambitions to become a global brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Michael Bruce?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-bruce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-bruce/</guid>
      <description>What has happened to Purplebricks? Purplebricks announced the closure of its Australian business in May 2019, followed by the closure of its US operation two months later.Jan 17, 2022
Why did ComFree change to Purplebricks? The Canadian business, set up via the acquisition of DuProprio/ComFree in July 2018 for around £29 million, was the only business that was successful. This signaled the end of PurpleBricks expansion into overseas markets and its ambitions to become a global brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Bernard Butler leave?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-butler/</guid>
      <description>When did Bernard leave Suede? 1994
Why did Bernard leave Suede? Speaking to the Daily Record newspaper, Butler said that he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have left Suede after a dispute over the producer who was working with the band at the time. He said: “I&amp;rsquo;ve fallen out with two people in my entire adult life and both were in public.Sep 20, 2002
Why did Bernard leave Suede? Speaking to the Daily Record newspaper, Butler said that he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have left Suede after a dispute over the producer who was working with the band at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jean-paul-bourelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jean-paul-bourelly/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-boston/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-bourge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-bourge/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/wes-borland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/wes-borland/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Isaac Brock break his jaw?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/isaac-brock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/isaac-brock/</guid>
      <description>Why did Judy leave Modest Mouse? Tom Peloso, who joined in 2004, has been integral during the past decade. But Eric Judy, who had been the band&amp;rsquo;s bassist since Modest Mouse began in 1993, decided to leave the group while they were gearing up for Strangers To Ourselves. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t any drama, just adulthood.Mar 6, 2015
When did Eric Judy leave Modest Mouse? 2011
Why does Modest Mouse have two drummers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How good of a guitarist was Mike Bloomfield?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-bloomfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-bloomfield/</guid>
      <description>Who played lead guitar on Tombstone Blues? The sensational story of Mike Bloomfield: from prodigy to tragedy. A 60s guitar prodigy who shaped Dylan&amp;rsquo;s sound and blew Clapton away, Bloomfield had the world at his feet. But he would never quite fulfil his promise.Oct 7, 2018
Did Mike Bloomfield play at Woodstock? By 1969 Butterfield was the only original member, so it was a new Butterfield Blues Band that played Woodstock — no Elvin Bishop or Mike Bloomfield, but future saxophone superstar David Sanborn was in the brass section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-brett/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-brett/</guid>
      <description>Is Thom Bresh Merle Travis son? Biography. Bresh was born on February 23, 1948 in Hollywood, California as the son of country singer Merle Travis. As a child, Bresh began acting in films and recording his own music. He also worked as a movie stuntman at the Corriganville Movie Ranch.
Is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis? He was inducted into the Nashville Songwriters Hall of Fame in 1970 and elected to the Country Music Hall of Fame in 1977.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thom-bresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thom-bresh/</guid>
      <description>Is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis? He was inducted into the Nashville Songwriters Hall of Fame in 1970 and elected to the Country Music Hall of Fame in 1977. THOM BRESH is the son of Merle Travis and a world-class guitar master in his own right. Bresh did not begin his music career until his adult years.Feb 2, 2021
Is Thom Bresh Merle Travis son? Biography. Bresh was born on February 23, 1948 in Hollywood, California as the son of country singer Merle Travis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Is Garth Brooks worth right now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/garth-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/garth-brooks/</guid>
      <description>Who is worth more Garth Brooks and Trisha Yearwood? Trisha Yearwood Net Worth: Trisha Yearwood is a country singer and actress who has a net worth of $400 million. That is a combined net worth with her husband, fellow country singer Garth Brooks. The majority of their combined fortune ($300 – $350 million) is attributable to Garth.
Why did Garth Brooks change his name? The real reason Garth Brooks took on the Chris Gaines persona was to create buzz for a movie that had not even been made yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Drew Brown?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/drew-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/drew-brown/</guid>
      <description>Who was Muhammad Ali&amp;rsquo;s corner man? Drew Bundini Brown (March 21, 1928 – September 24, 1987) was an assistant trainer and cornerman of heavyweight champion boxer Muhammad Ali.
Who was Muhammad Ali&amp;rsquo;s motivator? At the Greenwood Lake training facility, Bundini oversaw every aspect of Robinson&amp;rsquo;s preparation. For seven straight years, he fulfilled the role of Sugar Ray&amp;rsquo;s personal motivator, leaning over the ropes during sparring sessions, cheering him on as he worked the double-end bag, urging him to victory from ringside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Mick Box?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-box/</guid>
      <description>What did James Bowman do? An internationally recognized expert on pathology, inherited blood diseases and population genetics, Bowman was the first tenured African American professor in the University&amp;rsquo;s Biological Sciences Division. He also was a powerful advocate for minority scholars seeking access to academic medical careers.Sep 29, 2011
What was James e Bowman famous for? Bowman, MD, the first tenured African-American faculty member in medicine at the University of Chicago whose work paved the way for new understandings in inherited blood diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bob Bogle of The Ventures still alive?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-bogle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-bogle/</guid>
      <description>What kind of guitar did the Ventures play? Guitars. During their first years (1958–1961), the Ventures played Fender guitars (a Jazzmaster, a Stratocaster and a Precision Bass) for both their live performances and their recording sessions. These instruments are prominently visible on the covers of two early albums: The Ventures and The Colorful Ventures.
Who inducted the Ventures into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame? John Fogerty
Are any of the original Ventures still alive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bonamassa blind?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joe-bonamassa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joe-bonamassa/</guid>
      <description>Are Joe Bonamassa and Beth Hart married? Personal life. Hart is married to her road manager Scott Guetzkow, and currently resides in Los Angeles.
Does Joe Bonamassa have a child? Bonamassa is promoting a new album titled &amp;ldquo;Time Clocks.&amp;rdquo; Sharing the notion that he does not want to have kids, Joe noted: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not the parenting kind, I don&amp;rsquo;t have that in me. There&amp;rsquo;s no right or wrong, it&amp;rsquo;s just that I choose not to bring another human into the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed Bratton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/creed-bratton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/creed-bratton/</guid>
      <description>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed? Character history. A product of the 1960s, Creed is older than all of the other employees at the office. Prior to joining Dunder Mifflin, he was most notably a member of the rock band The Grass Roots in the late 1960s (as was the real-life Creed Bratton).
Who was real Creed in The Office? But for actor Creed Bratton — who plays an oddball version of himself on the show — The Office&amp;rsquo;s end just means there&amp;rsquo;s more time for music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed Bratton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jacques-brautbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jacques-brautbar/</guid>
      <description>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed? Character history. A product of the 1960s, Creed is older than all of the other employees at the office. Prior to joining Dunder Mifflin, he was most notably a member of the rock band The Grass Roots in the late 1960s (as was the real-life Creed Bratton).
Who was real Creed in The Office? But for actor Creed Bratton — who plays an oddball version of himself on the show — The Office&amp;rsquo;s end just means there&amp;rsquo;s more time for music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Edd China still friends with Mike?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brewer/</guid>
      <description>Why did ant leave Wheeler Dealers? However, Wheeler Dealers moved back to the U.K., but Ant decided not to return with it. Once he got a taste of the colonies, he (probably) decided he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go back to Jolly Old England and would much rather pursue a full-time career in American reality TV.Nov 2, 2021
Where is Ant Anstead of Wheeler Dealers? While the thought of watching Wheeler Dealers sans Anstead is unheard of, he added that he&amp;rsquo;s staying &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; in California because he currently has three new shows in the works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is James Dean Bradfield still married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-dean-bradfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-dean-bradfield/</guid>
      <description>Why did Richey Edwards disappear? By the time their third album was released – the dark masterpiece that is The Holy Bible – Richey was lost in a world of self-destruction battling self-harm, alcohol abuse and obsessing over the concept of a perfect disappearance. On 1 February 1995 he left his London hotel room and was never seen or heard from again.Apr 23, 2020
Who died from the Manic Street Preachers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Kix Brooks related to Garth Brooks?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kix-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kix-brooks/</guid>
      <description>Who from Brooks and Dunn died? Randy “Baja” Fletcher, a production manager for Waylon Jennings, Brooks &amp;amp; Dunn, Randy Travis, ZZ Top and, for the last 10 years, Keith Urban, died Aug. 27 after suffering an injury while setting up an Aug. 26 Urban concert at Bash on the Bay in Put In Bay, Ohio. He was 72.Aug 30, 2021
How old is Brooks &amp;amp; Dunn? Founded in 1990, the duo signed to Arista Nashville that year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was John Brewster Jr born Deaf?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-brewster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-brewster/</guid>
      <description>Who started deaf art? Ann Silver
Who was the first deaf artist? Quintus Pedius
Who was the deaf painter? John Brewster Jr. (1766–1854) was a deaf portrait painter who created beautiful and ethereal images of American people during the formative period of the nation. This is the first major exhibition in more than forty years to highlight Brewster&amp;rsquo;s extraordinary life and work.
Who is Fred Beam? Fred Michael Beam is an internationally acclaimed dancer, actor, poet, educator, director, and choreographer for numerous stage, film, and television productions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Julian Bream married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/julian-bream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/julian-bream/</guid>
      <description>Why did Julian Bream stop playing? Bream told The Guardian in 2013 that he had to &amp;ldquo;renounce making music seriously&amp;rdquo; in 2011 after being knocked off his feet by a neighbour&amp;rsquo;s dog while out walking. He broke both hips and injured his left hand in the fall, but said: &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing sad about not playing any more.Aug 14, 2020
Who is Mr Bream? Mr. Bream was the most eloquent guitarist of the generation that came of age soon after Andrés Segovia carved out a place for the guitar in the mainstream concert world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to David Bromberg?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-bromberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-bromberg/</guid>
      <description>What genre is David Bromberg? David Bromberg/Genres
What happened to David Bromberg? Bromberg currently lives in Wilmington, Delaware, where he and his wife, artist Nancy Josephson, own an extensive violin sales and repair shop, which receives a partial subsidy from the City of Wilmington, Delaware.
Is David Bromberg related to Brian Bromberg? Biography. Bromberg was born on December 5, 1960, in Tucson, Arizona. His father and brother, David, who both played drums, influenced him to take up the instrument himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to David Bromberg?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/devin-bronson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/devin-bronson/</guid>
      <description>What genre is David Bromberg? David Bromberg/Genres
Is David Bromberg related to Brian Bromberg? Biography. Bromberg was born on December 5, 1960, in Tucson, Arizona. His father and brother, David, who both played drums, influenced him to take up the instrument himself. At the age of 13, he began seriously pursuing a career as a drummer.
Are David and Brian Bromberg related? In 2002 Brian recorded his first acoustic jazz trio CD Wood featuring the incredible Randy Waldman on piano and Brian&amp;rsquo;s brother David Bromberg on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to David Bromberg?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-brook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-brook/</guid>
      <description>What genre is David Bromberg? David Bromberg/Genres
Is David Bromberg related to Brian Bromberg? Biography. Bromberg was born on December 5, 1960, in Tucson, Arizona. His father and brother, David, who both played drums, influenced him to take up the instrument himself. At the age of 13, he began seriously pursuing a career as a drummer.
Are David and Brian Bromberg related? In 2002 Brian recorded his first acoustic jazz trio CD Wood featuring the incredible Randy Waldman on piano and Brian&amp;rsquo;s brother David Bromberg on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Phoenix the band?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/laurent-brancowitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/laurent-brancowitz/</guid>
      <description>What genre is Phoenix? Phoenix/Genres
Is Phoenix still a band? Phoenix have teased that they are currently recording new music – check out the video below. The French four-piece shared the standalone single &amp;lsquo;Identical&amp;rsquo; last summer, and haven&amp;rsquo;t released a full-length album since 2017&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Ti Amo&amp;rsquo;.Jan 13, 2021
What kind of genre of music is Phoenix? Indie pop pop rock
What genre is Wolfgang Amadeus Phoenix? Wolfgang Amadeus Phoenix/Genres</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Phoenix the band?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/srdan-brankovic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/srdan-brankovic/</guid>
      <description>What genre is Phoenix? Phoenix/Genres
Is Phoenix still a band? Phoenix have teased that they are currently recording new music – check out the video below. The French four-piece shared the standalone single &amp;lsquo;Identical&amp;rsquo; last summer, and haven&amp;rsquo;t released a full-length album since 2017&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Ti Amo&amp;rsquo;.Jan 13, 2021
Why are Phoenix songs in English? There wasn&amp;rsquo;t even a French-music scene, it was just American standards and Motown and they would just translate the lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Pierre Bouvier?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pierre-bouvier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pierre-bouvier/</guid>
      <description>Is Simple Plan British? Simple Plan is a Canadian rock band from Montreal, Quebec formed in 1999. The band&amp;rsquo;s lineup consists of Pierre Bouvier (lead vocals and bass), Chuck Comeau (drums), Jeff Stinco (lead guitar), and Sébastien Lefebvre (rhythm guitar, backing vocals), with all four performing with the group since its inception.
How is Pierre SD pronounced? Peer
Is Simple Plan country? Unsourced material may be challenged and removed. Simple Plan is a Canadian rock band from Montreal, Quebec formed in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to volbeat original guitarist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thomas-bredahl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thomas-bredahl/</guid>
      <description>Why did Anders leave Volbeat? &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been very easy for us to get Kaspar into the band. The first European tour we did was actually with Kaspar as a stand-in bass player, because Anders couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it because of circumstances at home with his wife and kids.Sep 10, 2016
Did Volbeat get a new guitarist? Until the band is able to name a full time replacement, they&amp;rsquo;ve been using Mercyful Fate guitarist Hank Shermann as a fill-in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Vito Bratta?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vito-bratta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vito-bratta/</guid>
      <description>Why did the band White Lion break up? “In all our times together, Vito and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a single argument,” he states. “The problem was that we were very different people, with no friendship outside of the band. White Lion could have had a future, all we needed was to take a break and regroup, get a new haircut and catch our breath.”Oct 26, 2020
Why did White Lion break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Chris Broderick doing these days?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-broderick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-broderick/</guid>
      <description>Is Chris Poland a good guitarist? Frontman Dave Mustaine referred to Poland as &amp;ldquo;an amazing guitar player—he can play circles around me&amp;rdquo;. Poland joined Megadeth in 1984, after seeing them play as a three-piece, and after being recommended to Mustaine and Ellefson by Megadeth&amp;rsquo;s then-new drummer Gar Samuelson, a friend and former bandmate of Poland&amp;rsquo;s.
What guitar does Chris Broderick play? In January 2011, Broderick left Ibanez and is now endorsing Jackson Guitars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Jackson Browne&#39;s most famous song?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-brozman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-brozman/</guid>
      <description>Are Jackson Browne and Dianna Cohen still together? Browne, who lives in Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; Mid-City with his longtime partner, Dianna Cohen, has two adult children from previous marriages.Jul 26, 2021
Who is Jackson Browne&amp;rsquo;s current wife? Jackson Browne/Wife
Who has Jackson Browne dated? After two marriages - the first, to the actress Phyllis Major, ended with her suicide in 1976 and the second, to the Australian model Lynne Sweeney, ended in 1983 when he began a relationship with Hollywood star Daryl Hannah - Browne has been living with the environmentalist Dianna Cohen since the mid-1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Jackson Browne&#39;s most famous song?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jackson-browne/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jackson-browne/</guid>
      <description>Are Jackson Browne and Dianna Cohen still together? Browne, who lives in Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; Mid-City with his longtime partner, Dianna Cohen, has two adult children from previous marriages.Jul 26, 2021
Who is Jackson Browne&amp;rsquo;s current wife? Jackson Browne/Wife
Who has Jackson Browne dated? After two marriages - the first, to the actress Phyllis Major, ended with her suicide in 1976 and the second, to the Australian model Lynne Sweeney, ended in 1983 when he began a relationship with Hollywood star Daryl Hannah - Browne has been living with the environmentalist Dianna Cohen since the mid-1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is coach Mike Brown now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brown/</guid>
      <description>Where is coach Mike Brown now? May 10, 2022 at 8:30 a.m. SAN FRANCISCO — Mike Brown&amp;rsquo;s Monday was one for the books. On the morning of the Warriors&amp;rsquo; big Game 4 against Memphis, it was confirmed that Brown would be the Sacramento Kings&amp;rsquo; head coach. He signed a four-year deal and will move to his new role after the Warriors&amp;rsquo; playoff run.May 10, 2022
How much is Mike Brown paid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is James Bourne now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bourne/</guid>
      <description>Did Busted write their own songs? Busted wrote their own songs, played their own instruments and weren&amp;rsquo;t scared to say what they thought.Jan 15, 2005
Who was bigger McFly or Busted? Regarding the McBusted Tour, Judd said, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s bigger than what Busted ever were and it&amp;rsquo;s bigger than what McFly ever were&amp;rdquo;. On 6 July 2014, McBusted announced that they would be headlining British Summer Time Hyde Park, with the Backstreet Boys, Five, Scouting for Girls and dance troupe Diversity as special guests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michelle Branch now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michelle-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michelle-branch/</guid>
      <description>What was Michelle Branch&amp;rsquo;s first song? Fallen
In what year was Michelle Branch popular? Michelle Branch first charted in 2001. Her last appearance in the charts was 2003. She had chart topping singles covering a span of 3 years. See if Michelle made the list of most famous people with first name Michelle.
What happened to singer Michelle Branch? In 2015, Branch filed for divorce from her husband of eleven years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who got Marc Bolan&#39;s money?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marc-bolan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marc-bolan/</guid>
      <description>Was Marc Bolan a good guitar player? Rex album and the perfect encapsulation of Marc Bolan&amp;rsquo;s genius. Having spent years toiling away on the club and festival circuit with his acoustic duo, Tyrannosaurus Rex, Bolan fully embraced the sound of electric guitar and the spirit of rock &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll to score his first hit with Ride a White Swan in 1970.Jul 20, 2021
Was Marc Bolan and Bowie friends? One day, Conn hailed them both into his office, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for professional reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who got Marc Bolan&#39;s money?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcie-bolen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcie-bolen/</guid>
      <description>Was Marc Bolan a good guitar player? Rex album and the perfect encapsulation of Marc Bolan&amp;rsquo;s genius. Having spent years toiling away on the club and festival circuit with his acoustic duo, Tyrannosaurus Rex, Bolan fully embraced the sound of electric guitar and the spirit of rock &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll to score his first hit with Ride a White Swan in 1970.Jul 20, 2021
Was Marc Bolan and Bowie friends? One day, Conn hailed them both into his office, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for professional reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is James Bowman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bowman/</guid>
      <description>Who is James Bowman? James Edward Bowman Jr. He was a professor of pathology and genetics at the Pritzker School of Medicine at the University of Chicago. He published more than ninety works across the fields of human genetics; population genetics; and ethical, legal and public policy issues in human genetics.
What did Dr James Bowman advocate for with regards to genetic screening and counseling? Later in his career, Bowman focused on ethical, legal and policy issues raised by human genetics and mandatory screening tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is James Bowman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-boyd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-boyd/</guid>
      <description>What did James Bowman do? An internationally recognized expert on pathology, inherited blood diseases and population genetics, Bowman was the first tenured African American professor in the University&amp;rsquo;s Biological Sciences Division. He also was a powerful advocate for minority scholars seeking access to academic medical careers.Sep 29, 2011
Who is James Bowman? James Edward Bowman Jr. He was a professor of pathology and genetics at the Pritzker School of Medicine at the University of Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is John Bolinger?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bohlinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bohlinger/</guid>
      <description>Who does the Premier Guitar Rig Rundown? Rig Rundown: JD Simo. The Nashville-based power player uses classic-style guitars and amps to create big tones that echo from the past to the future. Our last Rundown with J.D. Simo was eight years ago.
Who owns Premier Guitar? Gearhead Communications, LLC
What tuning is all them witches? All the guitars take D&amp;rsquo;Addario NYXLs (. 010–. 046) and are typically tuned to D standard or drop C (C-G-C-F-A-D).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Tommy Bolin leave Deep Purple?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-bolin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-bolin/</guid>
      <description>How old was Tommy Bolin when he passed away? Tommy Bolin died young, at 25, just as he was coming into his own as a rock musician. The one-time lead guitarist for the group Deep Purple was found dead of drug overdose in a Miami hotel in 1976.Dec 22, 2017
When did Tommy Bolin leave Deep Purple? December 4, 1976
Who did Tommy Bolin replace in Deep Purple? guitarist Ritchie Blackmore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Bono called Bono?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/adrian-borland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/adrian-borland/</guid>
      <description>Is Bono embarrassed by U2 music? During an interview on The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rsquo;s Awards Chatter podcast, Bono revealed that most of U2&amp;rsquo;s songs embarrass him. “I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the car when one of our songs has come on the radio and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the color of, as we say in Dublin, scarlet,” Bono said (per Vanity Fair). “I&amp;rsquo;m just so embarrassed.”Jan 23, 2022
Is Bono disliked? Bono remains a world-renowned figure and someone who, indifferent of his past or future achievements, will remain fiercely disliked by a large contingent of rock fans and passionately loved by many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Bono called Bono?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bono/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bono/</guid>
      <description>Is Bono embarrassed by U2 music? During an interview on The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rsquo;s Awards Chatter podcast, Bono revealed that most of U2&amp;rsquo;s songs embarrass him. “I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the car when one of our songs has come on the radio and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the color of, as we say in Dublin, scarlet,” Bono said (per Vanity Fair). “I&amp;rsquo;m just so embarrassed.”Jan 23, 2022
Is Bono disliked? Bono remains a world-renowned figure and someone who, indifferent of his past or future achievements, will remain fiercely disliked by a large contingent of rock fans and passionately loved by many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Bono called Bono?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nicke-borg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nicke-borg/</guid>
      <description>Is Bono embarrassed by U2 music? During an interview on The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rsquo;s Awards Chatter podcast, Bono revealed that most of U2&amp;rsquo;s songs embarrass him. “I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the car when one of our songs has come on the radio and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the color of, as we say in Dublin, scarlet,” Bono said (per Vanity Fair). “I&amp;rsquo;m just so embarrassed.”Jan 23, 2022
Is Bono disliked? Bono remains a world-renowned figure and someone who, indifferent of his past or future achievements, will remain fiercely disliked by a large contingent of rock fans and passionately loved by many others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
