<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Musicant Family Brain</title>
    <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Musicant Family Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://musicantfamilybrain.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are Jennifer Nettles and Kristian Bush married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kristian-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kristian-bush/</guid>
      <description>What does Jennifer Nettles do now? Nettles is currently a judge on Go-Big Show (2021).
Is Jennifer Nettles married to Kristian Bush? According to People, Nettles married Miller, an entrepreneur, in a small and private ceremony at Blackberry Farm in the Smoky Mountains of Tennessee with a small group of friends and family present, including Nettles&amp;rsquo; longtime bandmate Kristian Bush.Sep 1, 2021
Is Sugarland still together 2020? With only a couple weeks to go before the scheduled start of their 2020 There Goes the Neighborhood Tour, Sugarland have canceled the entire run of shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Michael Stipe and Peter Buck friends?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-buck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/peter-buck/</guid>
      <description>What is Peter Buck&amp;rsquo;s net worth? 261 on the Forbes 400 list of wealthiest people, with an estimated net worth of $1.6 billion.
Are Michael Stipe and Peter Buck friends? Stipe, Buck and Mills haven&amp;rsquo;t regretted the decision, and Stipe suggests it salvaged their friendship. Buck and Mills both remain active musically as Stipe, until recently, stuck to visual art.Nov 20, 2019
What is Mike Mills of R.E.M. doing now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Glen Buxton play Billion Dollar Babies?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/glen-buxton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/glen-buxton/</guid>
      <description>Who are Alice Cooper&amp;rsquo;s current guitar players? Nita Strauss (born December 7, 1986) is an American rock musician. She is the current touring guitarist for Alice Cooper and has a successful career as a solo artist.
Who was the real Alice Cooper? Vincent Damon Furnier
Who died in Alice Cooper band? SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. — Alice Cooper guitarist Dick Wagner died Wednesday of respiratory failure at Scottsdale Healthcare Shea Medical Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Glen Buxton play Billion Dollar Babies?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roddy-radiation-byers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roddy-radiation-byers/</guid>
      <description>Who are Alice Cooper&amp;rsquo;s current guitar players? Nita Strauss (born December 7, 1986) is an American rock musician. She is the current touring guitarist for Alice Cooper and has a successful career as a solo artist.
Who was the real Alice Cooper? Vincent Damon Furnier
What happened to the original members of Alice Cooper? The four surviving original members reunited again for a five-song set on May 14, 2017, at a show in Nashville, Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Kenny Burrell doing?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kenny-burrell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kenny-burrell/</guid>
      <description>Is Kenny Burrell black or white? *Kenny Burrell was born this date in 1931. He is a Black jazz guitarist known for his work on the Blue Note label. Kenneth Earl Burrell was born in Detroit, Michigan. Both his parents played instruments and he began playing guitar at the age of 12 after listening Charlie Christian&amp;rsquo;s recordings.
Is Kenny Burrell black or white? *Kenny Burrell was born this date in 1931.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Charlie Burchill?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-burchill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-burchill/</guid>
      <description>Is Jim Kerr still married? Kerr married Chrissie Hynde, lead singer of The Pretenders, in 1984 (divorced in 1990). They had one daughter named Yasmin. He subsequently married actress Patsy Kensit in 1992 (divorced in 1996) with whom he had a son named James (born September 1993). Jim Kerr is a Celtic fan and an active supporter of the club.
Who is Jim kerrs wife? Jim Kerr/Wife
How many wives has Jim Kerr?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is David Byrne in a relationship?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-byrne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-byrne/</guid>
      <description>What happened to lead singer of Talking Heads? In December 1991, Talking Heads announced that they had disbanded. Frantz said that he learned that Byrne had left from an article in the Los Angeles Times, and said: &amp;ldquo;As far as we&amp;rsquo;re concerned, the band never really broke up. David just decided to leave.&amp;rdquo;
What type of music is David Byrne? David Byrne/Genres
How many instruments can David Byrne play? Byrne recounted these events when he appeared on Desert Island Discs on BBC Radio 4 on 18 March 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Ely Buendia friends with Eraserheads?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ely-buendia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ely-buendia/</guid>
      <description>Are Eraserhead members friends? MANILA, Philippines — Original Pilipino Music (OPM) icon Ely Buendia revealed that he and other members of his &amp;rsquo;90s band Eraserheads were never really friends. In the podcast “Wake Up With Jim &amp;amp; Saab,” the former Eraserheads frontman said they&amp;rsquo;re not Itchyworms nor Parokya ni Edgar that&amp;rsquo;s why they broke up.May 27, 2021
Did Eraserhead disband? The Eraserheads, considered as one of the biggest bands in OPM, disbanded in 2002 after over a decade of making music together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Jimmy Buffett a billionaire?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-buffett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-buffett/</guid>
      <description>Does Warren Buffett have a brother? Howard Graham Buffett - Wikipedia.
Where is Jimmy Buffett now? Today, he is a regular visitor to the Caribbean island of Saint Barts and other islands where he gets inspiration for many of his songs and some of the characters in his books. With the untimely death of friend and mentor Jim Croce in September 1973, ABC/Dunhill Records tapped Buffett to fill his space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was James Burton a good guitarist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-burton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-burton/</guid>
      <description>Who invented chicken pickin guitar? A session ace, sideman to the stars and contributor to a laundry list of hit records, James Burton remains one of the Telecaster&amp;rsquo;s greatest exponents.Apr 30, 2019
Who invented hybrid picking? Isaac Guillory (born 1947) Made it his signature technique. Rory Gallagher (1948–1995) Hybrid picking was used most notably and most often in his acoustic playing, in songs such as &amp;lsquo;Unmilitary Two-Step&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Out on the Western Plain&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;Pistol Slapper blues&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Jeff Buckley&#39;s death an accident?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-buckley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-buckley/</guid>
      <description>How do you get the Arctic Monkeys guitar tone? The Quick Answer. To get the Arctic Monkeys guitar tone, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a crunchy overdriven tone by either having the gain setting on your amp midway, or use an overdriven pedal through a clean amp. Have the gain, mids and treble higher for lead sections and then decrease the gain and mids lower for rhythm sections.
What happened to Tim Buckley?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Roy Buchanan asked to join the Rolling Stones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roy-buchanan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roy-buchanan/</guid>
      <description>Did Roy Buchanan turn down the Rolling Stones? These days he&amp;rsquo;s as infamous for apparently turning down an offer to join the Rolling Stones and his mysterious death in a Virginia jail cell in 1988 as he is for his music. Yet Buchanan&amp;rsquo;s legacy as a guitarist punches way above that of many of the rock stars who held him in such high regard.Jun 19, 2019
Could Roy Buchanan read music?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did Lindsey Buckingham do to Stevie Nicks?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lindsey-buckingham/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lindsey-buckingham/</guid>
      <description>How come Stevie Nicks never had children? Stevie Nicks has said that she consciously chose not to have children of her own, due to her demanding career and desire to follow her art: &amp;ldquo;My mission maybe wasn&amp;rsquo;t to be a mom and a wife; maybe my particular mission was to write songs to make moms and wives feel better.&amp;ldquo;Dec 30, 2020
How many daughters does Stevie Nicks have? Dia Dipasupil/Getty ImagesShe&amp;rsquo;s been married once, albeit very briefly, but Stevie Nicks has never had children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does RL stand for Burnside?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/r-l-burnside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/r-l-burnside/</guid>
      <description>What kind of music is RL Burnside? Blues hill country blues
What tuning is RL Burnside? open-G tuning
Did RL Burnside shoot someone? Back in the south, Burnside shot a man who had wanted to run him off his land. The judge asked Burnside if he intended to kill the man, and he replied: &amp;ldquo;It was between him and the Lord, him dyin&amp;rsquo;. I just shot him in the head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What guitar did Charlie Byrd play?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-byrd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-byrd/</guid>
      <description>What instrument did Charlie Byrd play? guitar
Who played with Charlie Byrd? In 1959, they joined Woody Herman&amp;rsquo;s band and toured Europe for three weeks as part of a State Department-sponsored goodwill tour. The other members of the band were Vince Guaraldi, Bill Harris, Nat Adderley and drummer Jimmy Campbell. Byrd led his own groups that sometimes featured his brother Joe.
What happened to Charlie Byrd? Charlie Byrd, the classically trained jazz guitar virtuoso who was a fixture on the Washington music scene for nearly 50 years and who helped introduce bossa nova to the United States, died of cancer yesterday at his home in Annapolis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Benjamin Burnley?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ben-burnley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ben-burnley/</guid>
      <description>What is wrong with the lead singer of Breaking Benjamin? Breaking Benjamin frontman Ben Burnley says he copes with his mystery illness by using the chronic pain to fuel his live shows. He&amp;rsquo;s suffered from joint and muscle pain for years but says he has been given no answers despite consulting hundreds of doctors.Jul 7, 2015
What kind of guitar does Breaking Benjamin play? Benjamin plays his music primarily on the BB-600 Baritone from the Signature LTD Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Benjamin Burnley?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/christian-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/christian-burns/</guid>
      <description>What is wrong with the lead singer of Breaking Benjamin? Breaking Benjamin frontman Ben Burnley says he copes with his mystery illness by using the chronic pain to fuel his live shows. He&amp;rsquo;s suffered from joint and muscle pain for years but says he has been given no answers despite consulting hundreds of doctors.Jul 7, 2015
What kind of guitar does Breaking Benjamin play? Benjamin plays his music primarily on the BB-600 Baritone from the Signature LTD Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Buckethead?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buckethead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buckethead/</guid>
      <description>Is Buckethead a derogatory term? The term &amp;ldquo;buckethead&amp;rdquo; referred to stormtroopers. &amp;ldquo;Buckethead&amp;rdquo; (also spelled &amp;ldquo;bucket-head&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bucket head&amp;rdquo;) was a derogatory nickname used to refer to stormtroopers during the reign of the Galactic Empire, or others wearing similar armor.
Who was Buckethead? Brian Patrick Carroll
How did Buckethead get his name? &amp;ldquo;I just put it on my head and I looked in the mirror. And I was like &amp;lsquo;That&amp;rsquo;s Buckethead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is John Butler&#39;s religion?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-butler/</guid>
      <description>Is John Butler still married? Butler is married to Danielle Caruana, an Australian musician and vocalist who performs under the name of Mama Kin. They have two children, a daughter and a son.
Is Mama Kin John Butlers wife? Four years ago Butler, wife Danielle Caruana (also known as musician Mama Kin) and their teenage kids, daughter Banjo and son Jahli, moved to a 2.8ha property just outside Margs.Sep 29, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Jonny Buckland worth?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jonny-buckland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jonny-buckland/</guid>
      <description>Which guitar does Chris Martin use? Gibson Blues King Acoustic Guitar.
Who plays the electric guitar in Coldplay? Jonny Buckland
Which guitar does Coldplay use? The ultimate &amp;ldquo;Coldplay Guitar&amp;rdquo; is without any doubt the Fender Telecaster Thinline a semi hollow electric guitar. Jon uses several models of this guitar, which is really cool: basically, a semi-hollow Telecaster with f-holes and humbuckers.Jan 21, 2009
Does Chris Martin own Martin Guitars? Chris Martin IV took the reins of the business – which has been owned by the Martin family for six generations – following the death of his grandfather and mentor, CF Martin III, in 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Jonathan Butler now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/damon-buxton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/damon-buxton/</guid>
      <description>When did Jonathan Butler leave South Africa? But Butler didn&amp;rsquo;t remain in South Africa much longer; in the early &amp;rsquo;80s, he escaped and moved to England (where Jive&amp;rsquo;s main office was located, and where he remained for 17 years).
Where does Jonathan Butler live? Encino
Where is Jonathan Butler today? The youngest of 13 children and now based in Los Angeles in the US, Butler lived in the UK for many years before moving to the US after gaining a loyal following in both countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Jonathan Butler now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jonathan-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jonathan-butler/</guid>
      <description>When did Jonathan Butler leave South Africa? But Butler didn&amp;rsquo;t remain in South Africa much longer; in the early &amp;rsquo;80s, he escaped and moved to England (where Jive&amp;rsquo;s main office was located, and where he remained for 17 years).
Where does Jonathan Butler live? Encino
Where is Jonathan Butler today? The youngest of 13 children and now based in Los Angeles in the US, Butler lived in the UK for many years before moving to the US after gaining a loyal following in both countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Mark Bryan now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-bryan/</guid>
      <description>Where did Michael Bruce live? Early life Michael Owen Bruce was born to Alvin and Ruth (Owen) Bruce. The Bruce and Owen families had moved to Arizona from Kansas.
Who was Michael Bruce? Michael Bruce, (born March 27, 1746, Kinnesswood, Kinross-shire [now Perth and Kinross], Scot. —died July 5, 1767, Kinnesswood), Scottish poet whose works were allegedly “stolen” by the poet John Logan, provoking a long-lasting controversy.Mar 23, 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Norman Brown from?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/norman-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/norman-brown/</guid>
      <description>Is Norman Brown still married? While the older jazz drives his musicianship, the drive to succeed in his career came from his family, Brown said. He has been married 30 years and has six children. “Norman Jr. produces rap records,” he said.Aug 7, 2009
What type of guitar does Norman Brown play? Guitars. Norman has played everything from standard George Benson signature Ibanez to his own line of Eastman guitars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Norman Brown from?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oli-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/oli-brown/</guid>
      <description>Is Norman Brown still married? While the older jazz drives his musicianship, the drive to succeed in his career came from his family, Brown said. He has been married 30 years and has six children. “Norman Jr. produces rap records,” he said.Aug 7, 2009
What type of guitar does Norman Brown play? Guitars. Norman has played everything from standard George Benson signature Ibanez to his own line of Eastman guitars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Jake Burns married to?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jake-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jake-burns/</guid>
      <description>Who is Jake Burns married to? Burns&amp;rsquo; second wife, Shirley, is American and they have lived in Chicago since 2004. Burns would eventually become a US citizen, partially so he could help vote out Donald Trump.
Where did Jake Burns grow up? Joanmount</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Jake Burns married to?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vinny-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vinny-burns/</guid>
      <description>Who is Jake Burns married to? Burns&amp;rsquo; second wife, Shirley, is American and they have lived in Chicago since 2004. Burns would eventually become a US citizen, partially so he could help vote out Donald Trump.
Where did Jake Burns grow up? Joanmount</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Michael Bruce?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-bruno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-bruno/</guid>
      <description>What has happened to Purplebricks? Purplebricks announced the closure of its Australian business in May 2019, followed by the closure of its US operation two months later.Jan 17, 2022
Why did ComFree change to Purplebricks? The Canadian business, set up via the acquisition of DuProprio/ComFree in July 2018 for around £29 million, was the only business that was successful. This signaled the end of PurpleBricks expansion into overseas markets and its ambitions to become a global brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Michael Bruce?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-bruce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-bruce/</guid>
      <description>What has happened to Purplebricks? Purplebricks announced the closure of its Australian business in May 2019, followed by the closure of its US operation two months later.Jan 17, 2022
Why did ComFree change to Purplebricks? The Canadian business, set up via the acquisition of DuProprio/ComFree in July 2018 for around £29 million, was the only business that was successful. This signaled the end of PurpleBricks expansion into overseas markets and its ambitions to become a global brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Bernard Butler leave?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-butler/</guid>
      <description>When did Bernard leave Suede? 1994
Why did Bernard leave Suede? Speaking to the Daily Record newspaper, Butler said that he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have left Suede after a dispute over the producer who was working with the band at the time. He said: “I&amp;rsquo;ve fallen out with two people in my entire adult life and both were in public.Sep 20, 2002
Why did Bernard leave Suede? Speaking to the Daily Record newspaper, Butler said that he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have left Suede after a dispute over the producer who was working with the band at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jean-paul-bourelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jean-paul-bourelly/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mark-boston/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-bourge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-bourge/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Wes Borland and Fred Durst get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/wes-borland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/wes-borland/</guid>
      <description>When did Wes Borland rejoin Limp Bizkit? He formed Big Dumb Face with his brother Scott in 1998 and left Limp Bizkit in 2001 to start side projects including Eat the Day and The Damning Well. After rejoining Limp Bizkit in 2004, Borland founded Black Light Burns, with whom he has released three studio albums and a covers album.
Is Wes back with Limp Bizkit? Limp Bizkit just dropped their latest album Still Sucks this past fall, but the rockers are apparently on a creative high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Isaac Brock break his jaw?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/isaac-brock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/isaac-brock/</guid>
      <description>Why did Judy leave Modest Mouse? Tom Peloso, who joined in 2004, has been integral during the past decade. But Eric Judy, who had been the band&amp;rsquo;s bassist since Modest Mouse began in 1993, decided to leave the group while they were gearing up for Strangers To Ourselves. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t any drama, just adulthood.Mar 6, 2015
When did Eric Judy leave Modest Mouse? 2011
Why does Modest Mouse have two drummers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Lenny Breau do that?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lenny-breau/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lenny-breau/</guid>
      <description>How did Lenny Breau do that? On August 12, 1984, his body was found in a swimming pool at his apartment complex in Los Angeles, California. The coroner reported that Breau had been strangled.
Who was Lenny Breau married to? Jewel
How did Lenny Breau do that? On August 12, 1984, his body was found in a swimming pool at his apartment complex in Los Angeles, California. The coroner reported that Breau had been strangled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How good of a guitarist was Mike Bloomfield?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-bloomfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-bloomfield/</guid>
      <description>Who played lead guitar on Tombstone Blues? The sensational story of Mike Bloomfield: from prodigy to tragedy. A 60s guitar prodigy who shaped Dylan&amp;rsquo;s sound and blew Clapton away, Bloomfield had the world at his feet. But he would never quite fulfil his promise.Oct 7, 2018
Did Mike Bloomfield play at Woodstock? By 1969 Butterfield was the only original member, so it was a new Butterfield Blues Band that played Woodstock — no Elvin Bishop or Mike Bloomfield, but future saxophone superstar David Sanborn was in the brass section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-brett/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/paul-brett/</guid>
      <description>Is Thom Bresh Merle Travis son? Biography. Bresh was born on February 23, 1948 in Hollywood, California as the son of country singer Merle Travis. As a child, Bresh began acting in films and recording his own music. He also worked as a movie stuntman at the Corriganville Movie Ranch.
Is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis? He was inducted into the Nashville Songwriters Hall of Fame in 1970 and elected to the Country Music Hall of Fame in 1977.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thom-bresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thom-bresh/</guid>
      <description>Is Thom Bresh related to Merle Travis? He was inducted into the Nashville Songwriters Hall of Fame in 1970 and elected to the Country Music Hall of Fame in 1977. THOM BRESH is the son of Merle Travis and a world-class guitar master in his own right. Bresh did not begin his music career until his adult years.Feb 2, 2021
Is Thom Bresh Merle Travis son? Biography. Bresh was born on February 23, 1948 in Hollywood, California as the son of country singer Merle Travis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Is Garth Brooks worth right now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/garth-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/garth-brooks/</guid>
      <description>Who is worth more Garth Brooks and Trisha Yearwood? Trisha Yearwood Net Worth: Trisha Yearwood is a country singer and actress who has a net worth of $400 million. That is a combined net worth with her husband, fellow country singer Garth Brooks. The majority of their combined fortune ($300 – $350 million) is attributable to Garth.
Why did Garth Brooks change his name? The real reason Garth Brooks took on the Chris Gaines persona was to create buzz for a movie that had not even been made yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Drew Brown?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/drew-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/drew-brown/</guid>
      <description>Who was Muhammad Ali&amp;rsquo;s corner man? Drew Bundini Brown (March 21, 1928 – September 24, 1987) was an assistant trainer and cornerman of heavyweight champion boxer Muhammad Ali.
Who was Muhammad Ali&amp;rsquo;s motivator? At the Greenwood Lake training facility, Bundini oversaw every aspect of Robinson&amp;rsquo;s preparation. For seven straight years, he fulfilled the role of Sugar Ray&amp;rsquo;s personal motivator, leaning over the ropes during sparring sessions, cheering him on as he worked the double-end bag, urging him to victory from ringside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Mick Box?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-box/</guid>
      <description>What did James Bowman do? An internationally recognized expert on pathology, inherited blood diseases and population genetics, Bowman was the first tenured African American professor in the University&amp;rsquo;s Biological Sciences Division. He also was a powerful advocate for minority scholars seeking access to academic medical careers.Sep 29, 2011
What was James e Bowman famous for? Bowman, MD, the first tenured African-American faculty member in medicine at the University of Chicago whose work paved the way for new understandings in inherited blood diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bob Bogle of The Ventures still alive?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-bogle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-bogle/</guid>
      <description>What kind of guitar did the Ventures play? Guitars. During their first years (1958–1961), the Ventures played Fender guitars (a Jazzmaster, a Stratocaster and a Precision Bass) for both their live performances and their recording sessions. These instruments are prominently visible on the covers of two early albums: The Ventures and The Colorful Ventures.
Who inducted the Ventures into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame? John Fogerty
Are any of the original Ventures still alive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bonamassa blind?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joe-bonamassa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joe-bonamassa/</guid>
      <description>Are Joe Bonamassa and Beth Hart married? Personal life. Hart is married to her road manager Scott Guetzkow, and currently resides in Los Angeles.
Does Joe Bonamassa have a child? Bonamassa is promoting a new album titled &amp;ldquo;Time Clocks.&amp;rdquo; Sharing the notion that he does not want to have kids, Joe noted: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not the parenting kind, I don&amp;rsquo;t have that in me. There&amp;rsquo;s no right or wrong, it&amp;rsquo;s just that I choose not to bring another human into the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed Bratton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/creed-bratton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/creed-bratton/</guid>
      <description>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed? Character history. A product of the 1960s, Creed is older than all of the other employees at the office. Prior to joining Dunder Mifflin, he was most notably a member of the rock band The Grass Roots in the late 1960s (as was the real-life Creed Bratton).
Who was real Creed in The Office? But for actor Creed Bratton — who plays an oddball version of himself on the show — The Office&amp;rsquo;s end just means there&amp;rsquo;s more time for music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed Bratton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jacques-brautbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jacques-brautbar/</guid>
      <description>Is Creed Bratton The real Creed? Character history. A product of the 1960s, Creed is older than all of the other employees at the office. Prior to joining Dunder Mifflin, he was most notably a member of the rock band The Grass Roots in the late 1960s (as was the real-life Creed Bratton).
Who was real Creed in The Office? But for actor Creed Bratton — who plays an oddball version of himself on the show — The Office&amp;rsquo;s end just means there&amp;rsquo;s more time for music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Edd China still friends with Mike?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brewer/</guid>
      <description>Why did ant leave Wheeler Dealers? However, Wheeler Dealers moved back to the U.K., but Ant decided not to return with it. Once he got a taste of the colonies, he (probably) decided he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go back to Jolly Old England and would much rather pursue a full-time career in American reality TV.Nov 2, 2021
Where is Ant Anstead of Wheeler Dealers? While the thought of watching Wheeler Dealers sans Anstead is unheard of, he added that he&amp;rsquo;s staying &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; in California because he currently has three new shows in the works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is James Dean Bradfield still married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-dean-bradfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-dean-bradfield/</guid>
      <description>Why did Richey Edwards disappear? By the time their third album was released – the dark masterpiece that is The Holy Bible – Richey was lost in a world of self-destruction battling self-harm, alcohol abuse and obsessing over the concept of a perfect disappearance. On 1 February 1995 he left his London hotel room and was never seen or heard from again.Apr 23, 2020
Who died from the Manic Street Preachers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Kix Brooks related to Garth Brooks?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kix-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/kix-brooks/</guid>
      <description>Who from Brooks and Dunn died? Randy “Baja” Fletcher, a production manager for Waylon Jennings, Brooks &amp;amp; Dunn, Randy Travis, ZZ Top and, for the last 10 years, Keith Urban, died Aug. 27 after suffering an injury while setting up an Aug. 26 Urban concert at Bash on the Bay in Put In Bay, Ohio. He was 72.Aug 30, 2021
How old is Brooks &amp;amp; Dunn? Founded in 1990, the duo signed to Arista Nashville that year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was John Brewster Jr born Deaf?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-brewster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-brewster/</guid>
      <description>Who started deaf art? Ann Silver
Who was the first deaf artist? Quintus Pedius
Who was the deaf painter? John Brewster Jr. (1766–1854) was a deaf portrait painter who created beautiful and ethereal images of American people during the formative period of the nation. This is the first major exhibition in more than forty years to highlight Brewster&amp;rsquo;s extraordinary life and work.
Who is Fred Beam? Fred Michael Beam is an internationally acclaimed dancer, actor, poet, educator, director, and choreographer for numerous stage, film, and television productions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Julian Bream married?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/julian-bream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/julian-bream/</guid>
      <description>Why did Julian Bream stop playing? Bream told The Guardian in 2013 that he had to &amp;ldquo;renounce making music seriously&amp;rdquo; in 2011 after being knocked off his feet by a neighbour&amp;rsquo;s dog while out walking. He broke both hips and injured his left hand in the fall, but said: &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing sad about not playing any more.Aug 14, 2020
Who is Mr Bream? Mr. Bream was the most eloquent guitarist of the generation that came of age soon after Andrés Segovia carved out a place for the guitar in the mainstream concert world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does Meredith Brooks claim to be?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/meredith-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/meredith-brooks/</guid>
      <description>What kind of music is Meredith Brooks? In 1995, Brooks landed a solo contract with Capitol Records. After two years, her first single, &amp;ldquo;Bitch&amp;rdquo;, was released, and she was nominated twice for the 1998 Grammy Awards, for Best Female Rock Vocal Performance and Best Rock Song. The single went Platinum in Australia.
What happened to the singer Meredith Brooks? Meredith is currently 55 years old, and started her career back in the &amp;rsquo;70s, when she started up an all-girl rock band called Sapphire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to David Bromberg?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-bromberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/david-bromberg/</guid>
      <description>What genre is David Bromberg? David Bromberg/Genres
What happened to David Bromberg? Bromberg currently lives in Wilmington, Delaware, where he and his wife, artist Nancy Josephson, own an extensive violin sales and repair shop, which receives a partial subsidy from the City of Wilmington, Delaware.
Is David Bromberg related to Brian Bromberg? Biography. Bromberg was born on December 5, 1960, in Tucson, Arizona. His father and brother, David, who both played drums, influenced him to take up the instrument himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to David Bromberg?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/devin-bronson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/devin-bronson/</guid>
      <description>What genre is David Bromberg? David Bromberg/Genres
Is David Bromberg related to Brian Bromberg? Biography. Bromberg was born on December 5, 1960, in Tucson, Arizona. His father and brother, David, who both played drums, influenced him to take up the instrument himself. At the age of 13, he began seriously pursuing a career as a drummer.
Are David and Brian Bromberg related? In 2002 Brian recorded his first acoustic jazz trio CD Wood featuring the incredible Randy Waldman on piano and Brian&amp;rsquo;s brother David Bromberg on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to David Bromberg?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-brook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-brook/</guid>
      <description>What genre is David Bromberg? David Bromberg/Genres
Is David Bromberg related to Brian Bromberg? Biography. Bromberg was born on December 5, 1960, in Tucson, Arizona. His father and brother, David, who both played drums, influenced him to take up the instrument himself. At the age of 13, he began seriously pursuing a career as a drummer.
Are David and Brian Bromberg related? In 2002 Brian recorded his first acoustic jazz trio CD Wood featuring the incredible Randy Waldman on piano and Brian&amp;rsquo;s brother David Bromberg on drums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Phoenix the band?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/laurent-brancowitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/laurent-brancowitz/</guid>
      <description>What genre is Phoenix? Phoenix/Genres
Is Phoenix still a band? Phoenix have teased that they are currently recording new music – check out the video below. The French four-piece shared the standalone single &amp;lsquo;Identical&amp;rsquo; last summer, and haven&amp;rsquo;t released a full-length album since 2017&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Ti Amo&amp;rsquo;.Jan 13, 2021
What kind of genre of music is Phoenix? Indie pop pop rock
What genre is Wolfgang Amadeus Phoenix? Wolfgang Amadeus Phoenix/Genres</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Phoenix the band?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/srdan-brankovic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/srdan-brankovic/</guid>
      <description>What genre is Phoenix? Phoenix/Genres
Is Phoenix still a band? Phoenix have teased that they are currently recording new music – check out the video below. The French four-piece shared the standalone single &amp;lsquo;Identical&amp;rsquo; last summer, and haven&amp;rsquo;t released a full-length album since 2017&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Ti Amo&amp;rsquo;.Jan 13, 2021
Why are Phoenix songs in English? There wasn&amp;rsquo;t even a French-music scene, it was just American standards and Motown and they would just translate the lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Pierre Bouvier?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pierre-bouvier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/pierre-bouvier/</guid>
      <description>Is Simple Plan British? Simple Plan is a Canadian rock band from Montreal, Quebec formed in 1999. The band&amp;rsquo;s lineup consists of Pierre Bouvier (lead vocals and bass), Chuck Comeau (drums), Jeff Stinco (lead guitar), and Sébastien Lefebvre (rhythm guitar, backing vocals), with all four performing with the group since its inception.
How is Pierre SD pronounced? Peer
Is Simple Plan country? Unsourced material may be challenged and removed. Simple Plan is a Canadian rock band from Montreal, Quebec formed in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Pierre Bouvier?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/robert-bowlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/robert-bowlin/</guid>
      <description>Is Simple Plan British? Simple Plan is a Canadian rock band from Montreal, Quebec formed in 1999. The band&amp;rsquo;s lineup consists of Pierre Bouvier (lead vocals and bass), Chuck Comeau (drums), Jeff Stinco (lead guitar), and Sébastien Lefebvre (rhythm guitar, backing vocals), with all four performing with the group since its inception.
How is Pierre SD pronounced? Peer
Is Simple Plan country? Unsourced material may be challenged and removed. Simple Plan is a Canadian rock band from Montreal, Quebec formed in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to volbeat original guitarist?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thomas-bredahl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/thomas-bredahl/</guid>
      <description>Why did Anders leave Volbeat? &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been very easy for us to get Kaspar into the band. The first European tour we did was actually with Kaspar as a stand-in bass player, because Anders couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it because of circumstances at home with his wife and kids.Sep 10, 2016
Did Volbeat get a new guitarist? Until the band is able to name a full time replacement, they&amp;rsquo;ve been using Mercyful Fate guitarist Hank Shermann as a fill-in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Vito Bratta?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vito-bratta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vito-bratta/</guid>
      <description>Why did the band White Lion break up? “In all our times together, Vito and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a single argument,” he states. “The problem was that we were very different people, with no friendship outside of the band. White Lion could have had a future, all we needed was to take a break and regroup, get a new haircut and catch our breath.”Oct 26, 2020
Why did White Lion break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Chris Broderick doing these days?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-broderick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-broderick/</guid>
      <description>Is Chris Poland a good guitarist? Frontman Dave Mustaine referred to Poland as &amp;ldquo;an amazing guitar player—he can play circles around me&amp;rdquo;. Poland joined Megadeth in 1984, after seeing them play as a three-piece, and after being recommended to Mustaine and Ellefson by Megadeth&amp;rsquo;s then-new drummer Gar Samuelson, a friend and former bandmate of Poland&amp;rsquo;s.
What guitar does Chris Broderick play? In January 2011, Broderick left Ibanez and is now endorsing Jackson Guitars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Jackson Browne&#39;s most famous song?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-brozman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bob-brozman/</guid>
      <description>Are Jackson Browne and Dianna Cohen still together? Browne, who lives in Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; Mid-City with his longtime partner, Dianna Cohen, has two adult children from previous marriages.Jul 26, 2021
Who is Jackson Browne&amp;rsquo;s current wife? Jackson Browne/Wife
Who has Jackson Browne dated? After two marriages - the first, to the actress Phyllis Major, ended with her suicide in 1976 and the second, to the Australian model Lynne Sweeney, ended in 1983 when he began a relationship with Hollywood star Daryl Hannah - Browne has been living with the environmentalist Dianna Cohen since the mid-1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Jackson Browne&#39;s most famous song?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jackson-browne/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jackson-browne/</guid>
      <description>Are Jackson Browne and Dianna Cohen still together? Browne, who lives in Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; Mid-City with his longtime partner, Dianna Cohen, has two adult children from previous marriages.Jul 26, 2021
Who is Jackson Browne&amp;rsquo;s current wife? Jackson Browne/Wife
Who has Jackson Browne dated? After two marriages - the first, to the actress Phyllis Major, ended with her suicide in 1976 and the second, to the Australian model Lynne Sweeney, ended in 1983 when he began a relationship with Hollywood star Daryl Hannah - Browne has been living with the environmentalist Dianna Cohen since the mid-1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What rock band was Lincoln Brewster in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lincoln-brewster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/lincoln-brewster/</guid>
      <description>Where does Lincoln Brewster live? Lincoln Brewster (born July 30, 1971) is an American contemporary Christian musician and worship pastor. As a guitarist, singer, and songwriter, Brewster became a sought-after session guitarist in the early 90s. Brewster is the senior worship pastor at Bayside Church in Granite Bay, California.
What guitar does Lincoln Brewster use? Lincoln runs dimarzio Area 51 and 52 pickups with a treble bleed mod on his volume knob on his strats with a Pod X3 live to a Boss OD-3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What rock band was Lincoln Brewster in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/terry-britten/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/terry-britten/</guid>
      <description>Where does Lincoln Brewster live? Lincoln Brewster (born July 30, 1971) is an American contemporary Christian musician and worship pastor. As a guitarist, singer, and songwriter, Brewster became a sought-after session guitarist in the early 90s. Brewster is the senior worship pastor at Bayside Church in Granite Bay, California.
What guitar does Lincoln Brewster use? Lincoln runs dimarzio Area 51 and 52 pickups with a treble bleed mod on his volume knob on his strats with a Pod X3 live to a Boss OD-3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What rock band was Lincoln Brewster in?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vic-briggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vic-briggs/</guid>
      <description>Where does Lincoln Brewster live? Lincoln Brewster (born July 30, 1971) is an American contemporary Christian musician and worship pastor. As a guitarist, singer, and songwriter, Brewster became a sought-after session guitarist in the early 90s. Brewster is the senior worship pastor at Bayside Church in Granite Bay, California.
What guitar does Lincoln Brewster use? Lincoln runs dimarzio Area 51 and 52 pickups with a treble bleed mod on his volume knob on his strats with a Pod X3 live to a Boss OD-3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Big Bill Broonzy died which two notable figures were his pallbearers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/big-bill-broonzy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/big-bill-broonzy/</guid>
      <description>When was big Broonzy born? Big Bill Broonzy, byname of William Lee Conley Broonzy, (born June 26, 1893, Scott, Mississippi, U.S.—died August 14, 1958, Chicago, Illinois), American blues singer and guitarist who represented a tradition of itinerant folk blues.
When was big Broonzy born? Big Bill Broonzy, byname of William Lee Conley Broonzy, (born June 26, 1893, Scott, Mississippi, U.S.—died August 14, 1958, Chicago, Illinois), American blues singer and guitarist who represented a tradition of itinerant folk blues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Big Bill Broonzy died which two notable figures were his pallbearers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-broom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bobby-broom/</guid>
      <description>When was big Broonzy born? Big Bill Broonzy, byname of William Lee Conley Broonzy, (born June 26, 1893, Scott, Mississippi, U.S.—died August 14, 1958, Chicago, Illinois), American blues singer and guitarist who represented a tradition of itinerant folk blues.
How did Muddy Waters get his name? “When I got big enough to crawl around, I would play in the mud and try to eat it,” he once told me. His nickname, “Muddy,” bestowed by his grandmother, celebrated that early fondness for mud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Big Bill Broonzy died which two notable figures were his pallbearers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/eric-brosius/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/eric-brosius/</guid>
      <description>When was big Broonzy born? Big Bill Broonzy, byname of William Lee Conley Broonzy, (born June 26, 1893, Scott, Mississippi, U.S.—died August 14, 1958, Chicago, Illinois), American blues singer and guitarist who represented a tradition of itinerant folk blues.
How did Muddy Waters get his name? “When I got big enough to crawl around, I would play in the mud and try to eat it,” he once told me. His nickname, “Muddy,” bestowed by his grandmother, celebrated that early fondness for mud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Big Bill Broonzy died which two notable figures were his pallbearers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ethan-brosh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ethan-brosh/</guid>
      <description>When was big Broonzy born? Big Bill Broonzy, byname of William Lee Conley Broonzy, (born June 26, 1893, Scott, Mississippi, U.S.—died August 14, 1958, Chicago, Illinois), American blues singer and guitarist who represented a tradition of itinerant folk blues.
How did Muddy Waters get his name? “When I got big enough to crawl around, I would play in the mud and try to eat it,” he once told me. His nickname, “Muddy,” bestowed by his grandmother, celebrated that early fondness for mud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is coach Mike Brown now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mike-brown/</guid>
      <description>Where is coach Mike Brown now? May 10, 2022 at 8:30 a.m. SAN FRANCISCO — Mike Brown&amp;rsquo;s Monday was one for the books. On the morning of the Warriors&amp;rsquo; big Game 4 against Memphis, it was confirmed that Brown would be the Sacramento Kings&amp;rsquo; head coach. He signed a four-year deal and will move to his new role after the Warriors&amp;rsquo; playoff run.May 10, 2022
How much is Mike Brown paid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is James Bourne now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bourne/</guid>
      <description>Did Busted write their own songs? Busted wrote their own songs, played their own instruments and weren&amp;rsquo;t scared to say what they thought.Jan 15, 2005
Who was bigger McFly or Busted? Regarding the McBusted Tour, Judd said, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s bigger than what Busted ever were and it&amp;rsquo;s bigger than what McFly ever were&amp;rdquo;. On 6 July 2014, McBusted announced that they would be headlining British Summer Time Hyde Park, with the Backstreet Boys, Five, Scouting for Girls and dance troupe Diversity as special guests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michelle Branch now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michelle-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michelle-branch/</guid>
      <description>What was Michelle Branch&amp;rsquo;s first song? Fallen
In what year was Michelle Branch popular? Michelle Branch first charted in 2001. Her last appearance in the charts was 2003. She had chart topping singles covering a span of 3 years. See if Michelle made the list of most famous people with first name Michelle.
What happened to singer Michelle Branch? In 2015, Branch filed for divorce from her husband of eleven years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who got Marc Bolan&#39;s money?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marc-bolan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marc-bolan/</guid>
      <description>Was Marc Bolan a good guitar player? Rex album and the perfect encapsulation of Marc Bolan&amp;rsquo;s genius. Having spent years toiling away on the club and festival circuit with his acoustic duo, Tyrannosaurus Rex, Bolan fully embraced the sound of electric guitar and the spirit of rock &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll to score his first hit with Ride a White Swan in 1970.Jul 20, 2021
Was Marc Bolan and Bowie friends? One day, Conn hailed them both into his office, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for professional reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who got Marc Bolan&#39;s money?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcie-bolen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/marcie-bolen/</guid>
      <description>Was Marc Bolan a good guitar player? Rex album and the perfect encapsulation of Marc Bolan&amp;rsquo;s genius. Having spent years toiling away on the club and festival circuit with his acoustic duo, Tyrannosaurus Rex, Bolan fully embraced the sound of electric guitar and the spirit of rock &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll to score his first hit with Ride a White Swan in 1970.Jul 20, 2021
Was Marc Bolan and Bowie friends? One day, Conn hailed them both into his office, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for professional reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Dave Brock?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-brock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-brock/</guid>
      <description>Who is Dave Brock? David Brock (born June 5, 1967) is an American football coach who was the wide receivers coach of the Atlanta Falcons of the National Football League (NFL). He previously was the head coach of University of Delaware Fightin&amp;rsquo; Blue Hens football team from 2013 to 2016.
How rich is Dave Brock? Dave Brock net worth: Dave Brock is an English singer, songwriter, and musician who has a net worth of $1 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is James Bowman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-bowman/</guid>
      <description>Who is James Bowman? James Edward Bowman Jr. He was a professor of pathology and genetics at the Pritzker School of Medicine at the University of Chicago. He published more than ninety works across the fields of human genetics; population genetics; and ethical, legal and public policy issues in human genetics.
What did Dr James Bowman advocate for with regards to genetic screening and counseling? Later in his career, Bowman focused on ethical, legal and policy issues raised by human genetics and mandatory screening tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is James Bowman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-boyd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/will-boyd/</guid>
      <description>What did James Bowman do? An internationally recognized expert on pathology, inherited blood diseases and population genetics, Bowman was the first tenured African American professor in the University&amp;rsquo;s Biological Sciences Division. He also was a powerful advocate for minority scholars seeking access to academic medical careers.Sep 29, 2011
Who is James Bowman? James Edward Bowman Jr. He was a professor of pathology and genetics at the Pritzker School of Medicine at the University of Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is John Bolinger?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bohlinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bohlinger/</guid>
      <description>Who does the Premier Guitar Rig Rundown? Rig Rundown: JD Simo. The Nashville-based power player uses classic-style guitars and amps to create big tones that echo from the past to the future. Our last Rundown with J.D. Simo was eight years ago.
Who owns Premier Guitar? Gearhead Communications, LLC
What tuning is all them witches? All the guitars take D&amp;rsquo;Addario NYXLs (. 010–. 046) and are typically tuned to D standard or drop C (C-G-C-F-A-D).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Tommy Bolin leave Deep Purple?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-bolin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-bolin/</guid>
      <description>How old was Tommy Bolin when he passed away? Tommy Bolin died young, at 25, just as he was coming into his own as a rock musician. The one-time lead guitarist for the group Deep Purple was found dead of drug overdose in a Miami hotel in 1976.Dec 22, 2017
When did Tommy Bolin leave Deep Purple? December 4, 1976
Who did Tommy Bolin replace in Deep Purple? guitarist Ritchie Blackmore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Bono called Bono?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/adrian-borland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/adrian-borland/</guid>
      <description>Is Bono embarrassed by U2 music? During an interview on The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rsquo;s Awards Chatter podcast, Bono revealed that most of U2&amp;rsquo;s songs embarrass him. “I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the car when one of our songs has come on the radio and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the color of, as we say in Dublin, scarlet,” Bono said (per Vanity Fair). “I&amp;rsquo;m just so embarrassed.”Jan 23, 2022
Is Bono disliked? Bono remains a world-renowned figure and someone who, indifferent of his past or future achievements, will remain fiercely disliked by a large contingent of rock fans and passionately loved by many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Bono called Bono?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bono/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bono/</guid>
      <description>Is Bono embarrassed by U2 music? During an interview on The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rsquo;s Awards Chatter podcast, Bono revealed that most of U2&amp;rsquo;s songs embarrass him. “I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the car when one of our songs has come on the radio and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the color of, as we say in Dublin, scarlet,” Bono said (per Vanity Fair). “I&amp;rsquo;m just so embarrassed.”Jan 23, 2022
Is Bono disliked? Bono remains a world-renowned figure and someone who, indifferent of his past or future achievements, will remain fiercely disliked by a large contingent of rock fans and passionately loved by many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Bono called Bono?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nicke-borg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/nicke-borg/</guid>
      <description>Is Bono embarrassed by U2 music? During an interview on The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rsquo;s Awards Chatter podcast, Bono revealed that most of U2&amp;rsquo;s songs embarrass him. “I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the car when one of our songs has come on the radio and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the color of, as we say in Dublin, scarlet,” Bono said (per Vanity Fair). “I&amp;rsquo;m just so embarrassed.”Jan 23, 2022
Is Bono disliked? Bono remains a world-renowned figure and someone who, indifferent of his past or future achievements, will remain fiercely disliked by a large contingent of rock fans and passionately loved by many others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
