<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Drummers on Musicant Family Brain</title>
    <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/tags/drummers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drummers on Musicant Family Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://musicantfamilybrain.info/tags/drummers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are Chad Smith and Will Ferrell friends?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chad-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chad-smith/</guid>
      <description>Is Will Ferrell and Chad Smith twins? Of course, the stars are not related, with Chad Smith born on 25 October 1961 to Joan and Curtis Smith in Saint Paul, Minnesota while Will Ferrell was born on 16 July 1967 to Betty Kay and Roy Lee Ferrell in Irvine California. However, it&amp;rsquo;s never stopped the comparisons.Oct 25, 2021
Does Will Ferrell have a twin? Will Ferrell Has a Drum-Off with his Twin, Chad Smith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Paul and Ringo still friends?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ringo-starr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ringo-starr/</guid>
      <description>Who is the richest Beatle member? McCartney
What is Ringo Starr&amp;rsquo;s net worth? $350 million
What were John Lennon&amp;rsquo;s last words to Paul McCartney? &amp;rsquo; She said that the last words that John Lennon said to Paul in the hallway of the Dakota building were, he patted him on the shoulder and said, &amp;lsquo;Think about me every now and then, old friend. &amp;lsquo;Sep 17, 2020
Did the remaining Beatles go to John Lennon&amp;rsquo;s funeral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Dennis Chambers read music?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dennis-chambers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dennis-chambers/</guid>
      <description>Did Dennis Chambers play for James Brown? When Dennis Chambers was just 13-years-old and gigging around his hometown of Baltimore, he was already so precociously talented that he was asked to join James Brown&amp;rsquo;s group.Feb 21, 2019
Did Dennis Chambers play for Steely Dan? Dennis has played with many greats throughout the years including John Scofield, Steely Dan, Santana, and many others. He also became part of the Sugar Hill record label and can be heard on many hip-hop classics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Stewart Copeland and Sting get along?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stewart-copeland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/stewart-copeland/</guid>
      <description>Who is Stewart Copeland&amp;rsquo;s wife? Stewart Copeland/Wife
Was Stewart Copeland&amp;rsquo;s dad in the CIA? In it, he digs deep into the life of his father, Miles Copeland Jr., a musician, businessman, and secret CIA operative (who was interviewed for this magazine in 1986).Oct 20, 2020
Are Sting and Stewart Copeland friends? As long as they don&amp;rsquo;t make music together, they are close friends. During an interview last year, Stewart Copeland stated that they have different reasons for making music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Jim Gordon become Batman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jim-gordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jim-gordon/</guid>
      <description>Does Jim Gordon Trust Batman? In most modern story arcs, however, Gordon is often skeptical of Batman&amp;rsquo;s vigilante methods, and hesitant to work with a guy dressed as a bat. Over time, however, Gordon learns to trust Bats and comes to recognize the necessity of his role in Gotham. A mutual respect develops, and eventually, a friendship.Feb 7, 2022
Who is Batman&amp;rsquo;s closest friend? Batman And Alfred Pennyworth Batman and Alfred is the first and most important friendship most fans came to know in comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Neil Peart pass away?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/neil-peart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/neil-peart/</guid>
      <description>Why Neil Peart is the greatest drummer of all time? Neil Peart was the fantastic drummer for the band Rush. He was chosen as the drummer for the band because he reminded them of Keith Moon from The Who. When it was all said and done, the only thing he had in common was his hard-hitting style.Nov 11, 2020
Where does Neil Peart rank as a drummer? No. 3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did Tony from Hi-Five died?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-thompson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-thompson/</guid>
      <description>How did lead singer of Hi-Five died? On June 1, 2007, Thompson&amp;rsquo;s body was discovered by security officers at around 10 p.m. near an air-conditioning unit outside of an apartment complex in his native Waco, Texas. An autopsy later determined that he had died from &amp;ldquo;toxic effects of chlorodifluoromethane,&amp;rdquo; or inhaling a toxic amount of freon.
Who died from Hi 5? Roderick &amp;ldquo;Pooh&amp;rdquo; Clark, an original member of Hi-Five, has died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How good a drummer is Alex Van Halen?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/alex-van-halen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/alex-van-halen/</guid>
      <description>Do Alex and Eddie Van Halen have the same parents? Eddie &amp;amp; Alex&amp;rsquo;s parents, Jan and Eugenia Van Halen circa 1951 | Eddie van halen, Van halen, Alex van halen.
Was Eddie Van Halen a twin? Both brothers were trained as classical pianists during childhood. Although Alex is known as a professional drummer, he began his musical aspirations as a guitarist, with his brother Eddie taking up drums.
Is Van Halen ever going to tour again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Mick Fleetwood related to Eric Clapton?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-fleetwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-fleetwood/</guid>
      <description>Did Fleetwood Mac sleep with each other? Stevie Nicks had an affair with Mick Fleetwood in 1977 Shortly after her breakup from Buckingham, Nicks fell for and began having an affair with fellow bandmate, Mick Fleetwood, while Fleetwood Mac was on tour promoting Rumours in 1977.Jan 11, 2021
What is the meaning of Tusk by Fleetwood Mac? The &amp;ldquo;Tusk&amp;rdquo; is slang for penis, so the song is basically about sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How old is Manu Katche?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/manu-katche/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/manu-katche/</guid>
      <description>Is Manu Katche a good drummer? Not a household name but Manu Katche&amp;rsquo; might be one of the most under-rated or perhaps under-the-radar drummers of all time. His resume is nothing short of a who&amp;rsquo;s who of rock and roll ranging from pretty much everything Peter Gabriel has done from the album So to today.Jul 26, 2018
Who played drums Peter Gabriel? Manu Katche
Who played drums on In Your Eyes Peter Gabriel?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bernard Purdie the most recorded drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-purdie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bernard-purdie/</guid>
      <description>Did Bernard Purdie play with the Beatles? While it&amp;rsquo;s true that Purdie&amp;rsquo;s name appears on hundreds of albums released during the past 40 years, he has never been officially credited for his work with The Beatles. In fact, the only known source for this astonishing bit of music trivia is Bernard Purdie himself!
Is Bernard Purdie the most recorded drummer? Purdie, who has played on over 4,000 albums, is widely regarded as “the world&amp;rsquo;s most recorded drummer”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Billy Cobham a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-cobham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/billy-cobham/</guid>
      <description>What kind of drums does Billy Cobham play? Billy also was integral in the creation of the original Gong Bass Drums. Cobham did not initially play a large kit with two bass drums (The Inner Mounting Flame and early live Mahavishnu gigs were done with a smaller, single bass drum kit), and he wasn&amp;rsquo;t the first jazz drummer to play with two bass drums.
Is Billy Cobham a good drummer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Carlos Santana still married to Cindy Blackman?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cindy-blackman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cindy-blackman/</guid>
      <description>Is Santana&amp;rsquo;s drummer his wife? Cindy Blackman Santana, a drum dynamo in jazz and rock, riffs on music, her all-star new album and famous husband. How did acclaimed drummer Cindy Blackman Santana react when her husband and musical partner, guitar legend Carlos Santana, first suggested she make an album featuring her singing?Oct 5, 2020
Is Cindy Blackman still married to Carlos Santana? Soulfulness has defined Blackman Santana&amp;rsquo;s playing since her breakout in the mid-1980s, and it&amp;rsquo;s the lifeblood of Give The Drummer Some, her joyful new jazz-fusion record featuring a cast of A-listers, including her husband of 10 years, Carlos Santana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Carmine Appice a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carmine-appice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carmine-appice/</guid>
      <description>Are Carmine and Vinny Appice brothers? Vincent Samson Appice (born September 13, 1957) is an American rock drummer best known for his work with the bands Dio, Black Sabbath, and Heaven &amp;amp; Hell. Of Italian descent, he is the younger brother of drummer Carmine Appice. Brooklyn, New York City, New York, U.S.
Is Vinny Appice a good drummer? Vinny Appice may not be the most recognized drummer because his brother often overshadows him, but he is certainly one worth studying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Clem Burke a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clem-burke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clem-burke/</guid>
      <description>Who is Blondie&amp;rsquo;s partner? Christopher Stein (born January 5, 1950) is the co-founder and guitarist of the new wave band Blondie.
Did Clem Burke play drums for the Eurythmics? Clem went on to lay down drums for Annie Lennox and Dave Stewart in Eurythmics, joined The Ramones for a spell, played with Iggy Pop and then rejoined Blondie when they reunited in 1997 with a hit comeback album, No Exit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Danny Carey the best drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/danny-carey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/danny-carey/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Danny Carey at the airport? Danny Carey, the renowned drummer for rock band Tool, was arrested for misdemeanor assault at Kansas City International Airport after getting into an altercation with a security guard, according to reports.Dec 13, 2021
Is Danny Carey still in Tool? Daniel Edwin Carey (born May 10, 1961) is an American musician and songwriter. He is the drummer for the American rock band Tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Dave Grohl deaf?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-grohl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-grohl/</guid>
      <description>Why did original drummer leave Foo Fighters? What happened to Foo Fighters original drummer? The original drummer for the Foo Fighters was William Goldsmith. The reason for him leaving the Foo Fighters was Dave Grohl&amp;rsquo;s perfectionism.
When did Dave Grohl leave Foo Fighters? A few months later, his bandmates said that they wanted to replace his wife, Gloria Bujnowski, as their manager. Grieving and feeling betrayed, he left in December 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Derek Trucks kin to Butch Trucks?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/butch-trucks-and-jaimoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/butch-trucks-and-jaimoe/</guid>
      <description>What are the names of the original Ohio Players? The band formed in Dayton, Ohio, United States, in 1959 as the Ohio Untouchables and initially included members Robert Ward (vocals/guitar), Marshall &amp;ldquo;Rock&amp;rdquo; Jones (bass), Clarence &amp;ldquo;Satch&amp;rdquo; Satchell (saxophone/guitar), Cornelius Johnson (drums), and Ralph &amp;ldquo;Pee Wee&amp;rdquo; Middlebrooks (trumpet/trombone).
Are any of the original Ohio Players still alive? They were unable to resolve their disputes and the ensemble disbanded in 1980. Of the original Ohio Players, Clarence Satchell died at the age of 65 on December 30, 1995, Ralph Middlebrooks died on November 15, 1997, at the age of 78, Robert Ward died on December 25, 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Larry Mullen Jr a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-dave/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/chris-dave/</guid>
      <description>How much is each member of U2 worth? The Irish group formed in 1976 consists of singer Bono, known name of Paul David Hewson ($700 million), guitarist The Edge, by-name of David Howell Evans ($400 million), bassist Adam Charles Clayton ($400 million), and drummer Larry Mullen ($300 million).Apr 6, 2021
Who is the richest rock star? Paul McCartney
Is Bono a billionaire? According to a leading media portal, Bono&amp;rsquo;s net worth as of 2020, is estimated to be roughly $700 million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Larry Mullen Jr a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-mullen-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/larry-mullen-jr/</guid>
      <description>How much is each member of U2 worth? The Irish group formed in 1976 consists of singer Bono, known name of Paul David Hewson ($700 million), guitarist The Edge, by-name of David Howell Evans ($400 million), bassist Adam Charles Clayton ($400 million), and drummer Larry Mullen ($300 million).Apr 6, 2021
Who is the richest rock star? Paul McCartney
Is Bono a billionaire? According to a leading media portal, Bono&amp;rsquo;s net worth as of 2020, is estimated to be roughly $700 million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Matt Cameron a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/matt-cameron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/matt-cameron/</guid>
      <description>How was Matt Cameron in Soundgarden and Pearl Jam? If you think you heard Matt Cameron&amp;rsquo;s name before Pearl Jam, you are right. He rose to prominence as the drummer for Soundgarden, a Seattle-based rock band he joined in 1986. Soundgarden developed the grunge sound and became legendary worldwide, achieving its biggest success with the 1994 album “Superunknown.”
Where does Matt Cameron rank as a drummer? Prior to joining Soundgarden, Cameron was a member of the Seattle rock bands Bam Bam and Skin Yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Terry Bozzio Italian?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/terry-bozzio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/terry-bozzio/</guid>
      <description>Is Terry Bozzio married? Terry Bozzio/Spouse
Is Terry Bozzio Italian? Virtuoso drummer Terry John Bozzio was born on December 27, 1950 to Italian-American parents in San Francisco, California.
Who is Terry Bozzio married to? Terry Bozzio/Spouse
Are Dale and Terry Bozzio still married? During her work with Zappa, she met drummer Terry Bozzio in 1976. They married in 1979 after Terry had become a member of the band U.K. They divorced in 1986 with Dale retaining her married name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tomas Haake a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ralph-molina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ralph-molina/</guid>
      <description>What drums does Tomas Haake use? &amp;ldquo;To me, SONOR drums are the perfect symbiosis of sound, craftsmanship and inventive solutions down to even the most minute details! Reliable, thought-through, beautiful and most of all - They sound awesome!!!&amp;rdquo; Haake is noted for his technical abilities.
What snare does Tomas Haake use? Tomas Haake also uses Trick Pro1-V pedals, Evans heads (G2 Clear tom batters, G1 Clear tom resos, EMAD2 Clear bass batters, Hybrid snare batter, and Hazy 300 snare reso), Vic Firth Tomas Haake signature sticks, and Shure microphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tomas Haake a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tomas-haake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tomas-haake/</guid>
      <description>What drums does Tomas Haake use? &amp;ldquo;To me, SONOR drums are the perfect symbiosis of sound, craftsmanship and inventive solutions down to even the most minute details! Reliable, thought-through, beautiful and most of all - They sound awesome!!!&amp;rdquo; Haake is noted for his technical abilities.
What snare does Tomas Haake use? Tomas Haake also uses Trick Pro1-V pedals, Evans heads (G2 Clear tom batters, G1 Clear tom resos, EMAD2 Clear bass batters, Hybrid snare batter, and Hazy 300 snare reso), Vic Firth Tomas Haake signature sticks, and Shure microphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tony Williams related to Kanye?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joseph-zigaboo-modeliste/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/joseph-zigaboo-modeliste/</guid>
      <description>Who did Miles Davis admire? More recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to keep up on all the &amp;rsquo;80s stuff. I had all of it, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really listened to it — Decoy, and those live albums. My favorite period was with Wayne Shorter, Ron Carter, Herbie Hancock, and Tony Williams.May 26, 2016
Who did Miles Davis get influenced by? He wanted someone who could play modal jazz, so he hired Bill Evans, a young pianist with a background in classical music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Tony Williams related to Kanye?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tony-williams/</guid>
      <description>Who did Miles Davis admire? More recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to keep up on all the &amp;rsquo;80s stuff. I had all of it, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really listened to it — Decoy, and those live albums. My favorite period was with Wayne Shorter, Ron Carter, Herbie Hancock, and Tony Williams.May 26, 2016
Who did Miles Davis get influenced by? He wanted someone who could play modal jazz, so he hired Bill Evans, a young pianist with a background in classical music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-drumbo-french/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-drumbo-french/</guid>
      <description>Why did Vinnie Colaiuta leave Sting? After three intense and challenging years with Zappa, Vinnie decided that it was time to pursue his dream of becoming a session drummer and left the band with Frank&amp;rsquo;s blessing. &amp;ldquo;I wanted to play all different kind of music,&amp;rdquo; he explains.
Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer? Vinnie Colaiuta His contribution to the work of Sting, Frank Zappa, Joni Mitchell, Herbie Hancock, Chick Corea and Jeff Beck has for a good many years made him the go-to guy for any artists needing a man capable of absolute mastery of sublime rhythms, odd-time and incredible chops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vinnie-colaiuta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/vinnie-colaiuta/</guid>
      <description>Why did Vinnie Colaiuta leave Sting? After three intense and challenging years with Zappa, Vinnie decided that it was time to pursue his dream of becoming a session drummer and left the band with Frank&amp;rsquo;s blessing. &amp;ldquo;I wanted to play all different kind of music,&amp;rdquo; he explains.
Is Vinnie Colaiuta a good drummer? Vinnie Colaiuta His contribution to the work of Sting, Frank Zappa, Joni Mitchell, Herbie Hancock, Chick Corea and Jeff Beck has for a good many years made him the go-to guy for any artists needing a man capable of absolute mastery of sublime rhythms, odd-time and incredible chops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Clifton James in Dukes of Hazzard?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clifton-james/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clifton-james/</guid>
      <description>Who was JW in Man with the Golden Gun? actor Clifton James
Was Clifton James in the A team? The A-Team (TV Series 1983–1987) - Clifton James as Sheriff Jake Dawson, Warden Beale - IMDb.
Why was JW Pepper in The Man with the Golden Gun? Pepper as a racist small-town southern sheriff, setting him up for mockery as a foolish pompous figure that the audience is meant to side against.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Hal Blaine a good drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hal-blaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/hal-blaine/</guid>
      <description>Was Hal Blaine a good drummer? Blaine was a prolific session player and by his estimation played on over 35,000 recordings, including 6,000 singles. He is widely regarded as one of the most in-demand drummers in rock and roll history, having &amp;ldquo;certainly played on more hit records than any drummer in the rock era&amp;rdquo;.
What drummer has 150 gold records? Hal Blaine
What cymbals did Hal Blaine use? Hal always used Zildjian cymbals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did Earl Young do?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-young/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-young/</guid>
      <description>Who designed the mushroom houses in Charlevoix Michigan? Earl Young
When was the Mushroom House built? The Studio (also known as the Mushroom House) is an ornately fanciful home built by architect Terry Brown in the Hyde Park neighborhood of Cincinnati, Ohio. The one-bedroom house features a cone shaped addition and a spiral staircase entry. It was built between 1992 and 2006.
Where are the mushroom houses located? Charlevoix, Michigan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What disease does Tommy Lee Jones have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-lee/</guid>
      <description>Who was the guy who stole Pam and Tommy tape? Rand Gauthier has become a household name again thanks to the Hulu series Pam and Tommy. The electrician became known for allegedly stealing the infamous Pamela Anderson and Tommy Lee sex tape in 1995.Feb 23, 2022
How did Pam and Tommy tape get stolen? In real life, Rand Gauthier did break in and steal the tape in 1995 after being unceremoniously fired without pay from doing contracting work on Pam and Tommy&amp;rsquo;s house renovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What disease does Travis Barker have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/travis-barker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/travis-barker/</guid>
      <description>Where does Travis Barker rank as a drummer? Today, Rolling Stone published its list of the “100 Greatest Drummers of All Time,” and spoiler: Meg White is ranked higher than U2&amp;rsquo;s Larry Mullen Jr. and Blink-182&amp;rsquo;s Travis Barker; Red Hot Chili Peppers&amp;rsquo; Chad Smith comes in at No. 64; Phil Collins is at No. 43; Tool&amp;rsquo;s Danny Carey and Dave Grohl are ranked No.Mar 31, 2016
Who is considered the best ever drummer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Bill Ward?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-ward/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-ward/</guid>
      <description>Did Black Sabbath regret firing Ozzy? On April 27, 1979, after various attempts to get Ozzy back on the team, Black Sabbath fired their lead singer. “We just couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue with Ozzy,” guitarist Tony Iommi said. “As much as everyone wanted us to, we just couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it. Nothing was happening and it would have meant the end of the band.Apr 27, 2022
What did Ozzy Osbourne do in Black Sabbath?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Carter Beauford?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carter-beauford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carter-beauford/</guid>
      <description>Is Carter Beauford still with DMB? Dave Matthews Band Members Stefan Lessard and Carter Beauford Reunite After Hiatus in Irvine. Dave Matthews Band bassist Stefan Lessard and drummer Carter Beauford rejoined the group for two performances in Irvine, Calif.Sep 12, 2021
Is Carter Beauford a great drummer? Carter Beauford is the groove-meister and founding member of The Dave Matthews Band. A powerhouse and technically gifted drummer, Carter&amp;rsquo;s open-handed approach to drums open him up to be an incredibly musical drummer, creating unique rhythms and grooves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Carter Beauford?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-dejohnette/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jack-dejohnette/</guid>
      <description>Is Carter Beauford a great drummer? Carter Beauford is the groove-meister and founding member of The Dave Matthews Band. A powerhouse and technically gifted drummer, Carter&amp;rsquo;s open-handed approach to drums open him up to be an incredibly musical drummer, creating unique rhythms and grooves.Nov 2, 2021
How much does Carter Beauford make? Carter Beauford net worth: Carter Beauford is an American musician, drummer, and percussionist who has a net worth of $65 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Carter Beauford?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ramon-tiki-fullwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ramon-tiki-fullwood/</guid>
      <description>Is Carter Beauford a great drummer? Carter Beauford is the groove-meister and founding member of The Dave Matthews Band. A powerhouse and technically gifted drummer, Carter&amp;rsquo;s open-handed approach to drums open him up to be an incredibly musical drummer, creating unique rhythms and grooves.Nov 2, 2021
How much does Carter Beauford make? Carter Beauford net worth: Carter Beauford is an American musician, drummer, and percussionist who has a net worth of $65 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened Meg White?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/meg-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/meg-white/</guid>
      <description>When did Meg and Jack break up? After a long hiatus with no new releases, the duo reported that they were disbanding. Taking to their official website on 2 February 2011, they wrote: &amp;ldquo;The reason is not due to artistic differences or lack of wanting to continue, nor any health issues as both Meg and Jack are feeling fine and in good health.Mar 30, 2022
Are Jack and Meg still married?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Cozy Powell?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cozy-powell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/cozy-powell/</guid>
      <description>Was COSY Powell a good drummer? He is one of the best drummers the hard rock and metal industry has ever had. Cozy was best described as talented, reliable, and versatile. Talented because he was an innovator. He came up with different styles of making music every time he held the drums.Jul 14, 2021
Who is the best technical drummer? Having played drums since the age of two, Virgil Donati is regarded as one of the most technically proficient drummers in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to football player Steve Smith?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/fred-below/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/fred-below/</guid>
      <description>Who is Smitty on NBA TV? NBA Champion Steve Smith is a studio analyst for NBA TV, appearing on the network multiple nights each week. A star guard at Michigan State, Smith had a 14-year NBA career playing for the Miami Heat, Atlanta Hawks, Portland Trail Blazers, San Antonio Spurs, New Orleans Hornets and Charlotte Bobcats.
Did Stevin Smith play in the NBA? Professional basketball career During the 1997 NBA season, Smith signed two consecutive 10-day contracts with the Dallas Mavericks, and received his only NBA playing time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to football player Steve Smith?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-smith/</guid>
      <description>Where did Steve Smith go? NFL.com Analyst joins the NFL Network as an analyst after 16 seasons in the NFL. Smith will appear on numerous NFL Network shows, including NFL GameDay First during the NFL season, which airs every NFL Sunday at 7 a.m. ET.
Is Steve Smith Sr still in the NFL? Steve Smith Sr. Smith Sr. last played in the NFL back in 2016 with the Baltimore Ravens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Jeff Porcaro?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-porcaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jeff-porcaro/</guid>
      <description>Who from Toto died? Mike Porcaro
Why did Bobby leave Toto? The late drummer Jeff Porcaro, Toto co-founder, was designated band spokesperson on the day he was asked to leave, Kimball said. “I was told that I didn&amp;rsquo;t follow rules. Well, I really didn&amp;rsquo;t like taking orders from anyone.”Jun 27, 2011
Who is the current lead singer of Toto? Toto/Lead singers
How many lead singers did Toto have? Today Toto is comprised of four key members: Lukather, Paich, Steve Porcaro and Joseph Williams, the singer who first fronted the group in the late 80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Jimmy Chamberlin?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-chamberlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jimmy-chamberlin/</guid>
      <description>What happened to Jimmy Chamberlain? He is currently active under the Jimmy Chamberlin Complex name. In addition to his current work as CEO, Chamberlin has joined Chicago jazz saxophonist Frank Catalano for a string of 2013–15 performances in the Chicago area. An EP by Catalano and Chamberlin Love Supreme Collective - EP was released on July 29, 2014.
What happened to the lead singer of the Smashing Pumpkins? He is best known as the lead singer, primary songwriter, guitarist, and only permanent member of the rock band the Smashing Pumpkins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Keith Moon?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/keith-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/keith-moon/</guid>
      <description>Was Keith Moon a fast drummer? Generally speaking, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to hear the drums as the lead instrument in a song by a four-piece band, but that&amp;rsquo;s the case here. After 35 seconds of subtlety, Moon&amp;rsquo;s hyper-fast drumming goes to work, starting and stopping at various points during the song, essentially controlling the entire dynamic.Aug 23, 2015
Who is considered the greatest drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Levon Helm?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/levon-helm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/levon-helm/</guid>
      <description>Why did Levon Helm not like The Last Waltz? In his 1993 memoir This Wheel&amp;rsquo;s On Fire, Helm details his dissatisfaction with The Last Waltz: Scorsese, he claims, focused on and exalted Robbie Robertson, the Band&amp;rsquo;s songwriter and frequent frontman, to the near exclusion of everyone else in the group.Apr 20, 2012
What happened to Richard Manuel? Richard Manuel, the singer, pianist, songwriter and occasional drummer with the rock group the Band, was found dead Tuesday in his motel room in Winter Park, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to Steven Adler?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steven-adler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steven-adler/</guid>
      <description>Who is touring with Guns N Roses 2021? Mammoth WVH
Will Steven Adler rejoin Guns N Roses? Drummer Steven Adler&amp;rsquo;s campaign to rejoin Guns N&amp;rsquo; Roses full-time alongside Slash and Duff McKagan fell short a couple years ago, but the band is still celebrating Adler&amp;rsquo;s guest appearances on the &amp;lsquo;Not in This Lifetime&amp;rsquo; tour.Jul 14, 2021
Why isn&amp;rsquo;t Steven Adler playing with guns and roses? &amp;lsquo;” Adler was fired in 1990 after his addiction issues ran out of control, while Stradlin left the following year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What illness did Ginger Baker have?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ginger-baker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ginger-baker/</guid>
      <description>What illness did Ginger Baker die of? chronic obstructive pulmonary disease
What happened to Ginger Baker after Cream? Ginger Baker, performing with Cream in 1966. There are lots of firsts and superlatives in the career of Ginger Baker, the drummer and bandleader who died Sunday morning at age 80. His death was announced by his family on social media; they had said on Sept.Oct 6, 2019
Who is still alive from Cream?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Gene Krupa known for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gene-krupa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/gene-krupa/</guid>
      <description>Was Gene Krupa the best drummer? Krupa&amp;rsquo;s reputation still looms large in pop culture: Rolling Stone recently put him at Number 7 in its list of the 100 greatest drummers of all time. Yet among jazz critics and historians, and many musicians, it has become part of the received wisdom that Krupa was an unmusical drummer, and that he played too loud.Mar 15, 2018
Can Gene Krupa read music? Gene moved to New York in 1929 and was recruited by Red Nichols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was Charlie Watts illness?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-watts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/charlie-watts/</guid>
      <description>What was the official cause of death of Charlie Watts? Throat Cancer Symptoms As Cause of Rolling Stones&amp;rsquo; Charlie Watts Death Unconfirmed. Charlie Watts, legendary drummer for the Rolling Stones, died at the age of 80 on Sunday.Aug 25, 2021
What sickness did Charlie Watts have? Watts, a smoker until the 1980s, was diagnosed with throat cancer in 2004. He is said to have fully recovered.Aug 25, 2021
How did Charlie from Rolling Stones died?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What were John Bonham&#39;s last words?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bonham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-bonham/</guid>
      <description>What is the most famous drum beat? I was definitely curious, so I did some research and found that the “Funky Drummer” beat by Clyde Stubblefield has been the most sampled drum groove ever (over 7 million times!). It&amp;rsquo;s just a basic 16th note groove, but the hi-hat part, ghost notes, and overall feel make this beat one of the hardest to play.Oct 24, 2021
Who is considered the greatest drummer of all time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Jerry Allison now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerry-allison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerry-allison/</guid>
      <description>Is Buddy Holly&amp;rsquo;s wife still alive today? Buddy Holly&amp;rsquo;s widow Maria Elena Holly is still alive today, and although their time together was short, they share a love story that won&amp;rsquo;t soon be forgotten. Buddy Holly met Maria Elena Santiago while visiting Peer-Southern music publishing company in New York City, where Maria worked as a receptionist.Feb 3, 2022
Where did Buddy Holly grow up? Lubbock
Who was Buddy Holly&amp;rsquo;s guitarist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Max Weinberg now?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/max-weinberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/max-weinberg/</guid>
      <description>Why is Conan&amp;rsquo;s band leaving? After many years on the air, Jimmy Vivino and the Basic Cable Band made their final appearance on tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode. Host Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien discussed the show&amp;rsquo;s format shift, expressing his sadness that his band wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be joining him in the new year.Oct 4, 2018
Are Conan and Max Weinberg still friends? “I don&amp;rsquo;t know why Max and Conan aren&amp;rsquo;t together anymore,” E Street guitarist Steven Van Zandt told Rolling Stone after it was revealed that Weinberg was permanently leaving Conan&amp;rsquo;s house band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Michael Shrieve today?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-shrieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/michael-shrieve/</guid>
      <description>How good of a drummer is Michael Shrieve? Over the course of his prolific career, musician Michael Shrieve has written, produced and played on albums that have sold millions of copies worldwide. In 2016, Rolling Stone listed him among the “100 Greatest Drummers,” and in 2011 the same magazine&amp;rsquo;s readers chose him as one of the “Top 10 Drummers of All Time.”
What happened to the drummer for Santana at Woodstock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who did Earl Palmer play for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-palmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-palmer/</guid>
      <description>Was Gene Krupa the best drummer? Krupa&amp;rsquo;s reputation still looms large in pop culture: Rolling Stone recently put him at Number 7 in its list of the 100 greatest drummers of all time. Yet among jazz critics and historians, and many musicians, it has become part of the received wisdom that Krupa was an unmusical drummer, and that he played too loud.Mar 15, 2018
Can Gene Krupa read music? Gene moved to New York in 1929 and was recruited by Red Nichols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who did Steve Jordan drum for?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-jordan/</guid>
      <description>Who is John Mayer&amp;rsquo;s current drummer? Aaron Sterling (born July 9, 1980) is an American drummer, producer, engineer, and session musician who lives in Los Angeles.
Who is Steve Ferrone playing with now? In 2019, Ferrone recorded session drums for Stroke 9&amp;rsquo;s studio album Calafrio. On 10 July 2019, Ferrone was inducted into the Brighton Music Walk of Fame in his hometown of Brighton, England. On 1 Feb 2022, it was announced that Ferrone would be a part of the band for John Mayer&amp;rsquo;s Sob Rock Tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is considered the greatest drummer of All Time?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jr-robinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jr-robinson/</guid>
      <description>What was Michael Jackson&amp;rsquo;s last words before he died? “I can&amp;rsquo;t function if I don&amp;rsquo;t sleep. They&amp;rsquo;ll have to cancel it. “And I don&amp;rsquo;t want them to cancel it, but they will have to cancel it.” According to the doctor who was the last person to see the singer before he was rushed to hospital, these were his final words.Mar 17, 2021
What was the last word Michael Jackson said?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is John jab?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clyde-stubblefield-and-john-jabo-starks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/clyde-stubblefield-and-john-jabo-starks/</guid>
      <description>Who invented the funky drummer beat? James Brown released a seven-inch single called Funky Drummer in March, 1970 – a loosely arranged jam session showcasing the talent for improvisation of drummer Clyde Stubblefield, who was employed in Brown&amp;rsquo;s band at the time.Mar 26, 2020
Who started the funk sound in music? James Brown
What is funk drumming? Funk drumming often features syncopation and rhythmic displacement, rudiment-based hand patterns, hi-hat openings, ghost notes, and linear patterns—when no two limbs play at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Questlove and what is his background?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ahmir-questlove-thompson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ahmir-questlove-thompson/</guid>
      <description>Who are the parents of Questlove? Questlove/Parents
Who is Questlove and what is his background? Ahmir Khalib Thompson aka “Questlove” hails from Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and was born January 20, 1971. He is a drummer, DJ, producer, culinary entrepreneur, designer, New York Times bestselling and James Beard Award-nominated author, and cofounder of Philadelphia&amp;rsquo;s most influential hip-hop group, the Roots.
Is Questlove&amp;rsquo;s father Lee Andrews? &amp;lsquo;Roots&amp;rsquo; Drummer Questlove On His Late Father Lee Andrews Fifties doo-wop singer Lee Andrews died Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who played drums in Aretha Franklin Respect?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roger-hawkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/roger-hawkins/</guid>
      <description>Do people still record at Muscle Shoals? Muscle Shoals Sound&amp;rsquo;s business model relies heavily on merch sales and studio tours. Recording sessions and fundraisers comprise Muscle Shoals Sounds&amp;rsquo; third-largest revenue stream. In 2018, after renovations, Muscle Shoals Sound began hosting recording sessions again.Jun 23, 2020
Is Muscle Shoals still making music? Still a working studio, this is where the Muscle Shoals Rhythm Section got its start. FAME was host to artists such as Aretha Franklin, Wilson Pickett, Duane Allman, Otis Redding, the Osmonds, Paul Anka and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Nirvana&#39;s first drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dale-crover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dale-crover/</guid>
      <description>Who was Nirvana&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Aaron Burckhard
How many drummers did Nirvana have? Grohl joined the grunge outfit in 1990, replacing &amp;lsquo;Bleach&amp;rsquo; drummer Chad Channing. Dale Crover and Dave Foster had previously played drums in Nirvana, while the band had also worked with session musicians Mark Pickerel and Dan Peters.Apr 6, 2018
Why did the original drummer leave Nirvana? During the sessions, Cobain and Novoselic became disenchanted with Channing&amp;rsquo;s drumming, and Channing expressed frustration at not being actively involved in songwriting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Nirvana&#39;s first drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/greg-errico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/greg-errico/</guid>
      <description>Who was Nirvana&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Aaron Burckhard
How many drummers did Nirvana have? Grohl joined the grunge outfit in 1990, replacing &amp;lsquo;Bleach&amp;rsquo; drummer Chad Channing. Dale Crover and Dave Foster had previously played drums in Nirvana, while the band had also worked with session musicians Mark Pickerel and Dan Peters.Apr 6, 2018
Why did the original drummer leave Nirvana? During the sessions, Cobain and Novoselic became disenchanted with Channing&amp;rsquo;s drumming, and Channing expressed frustration at not being actively involved in songwriting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Nirvana&#39;s first drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerome-bigfoot-brailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/jerome-bigfoot-brailey/</guid>
      <description>Who was Nirvana&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Aaron Burckhard
How many drummers did Nirvana have? Grohl joined the grunge outfit in 1990, replacing &amp;lsquo;Bleach&amp;rsquo; drummer Chad Channing. Dale Crover and Dave Foster had previously played drums in Nirvana, while the band had also worked with session musicians Mark Pickerel and Dan Peters.Apr 6, 2018
Why did the original drummer leave Nirvana? During the sessions, Cobain and Novoselic became disenchanted with Channing&amp;rsquo;s drumming, and Channing expressed frustration at not being actively involved in songwriting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was Sheila E to Prince?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sheila-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/sheila-e/</guid>
      <description>Did Sheila E and Prince have a relationship? Sheila E. joined Prince&amp;rsquo;s backing band as their romance grew, and as she recalled in a 2016 Billboard interview, they became briefly engaged after Prince proposed in 1987. However, by the 1988-89 Lovesexy Tour their relationship fractured, and Sheila E. subsequently left Prince and the band once it came to a close.Jan 24, 2021
Why did Sheila E not marry Prince? “We just grew apart,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the drummer for the Ohio Players?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-diamond-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/james-diamond-williams/</guid>
      <description>Who is the woman on the Ohio Players album cover? Ester Cordet
Who is on the Ohio Players album cover? Ester Cordet
Where did the Ohio Players record? The Ohio Players released their debut album, Pain, in 1971 on Detroit&amp;rsquo;s Westbound Records, a label shared by George Clinton&amp;rsquo;s Funkadelic band. They followed their debut with Pleasure a year later, then Ecstasy in 1973.
Who was the guitar player in Ohio Players?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the Motown drummer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/benny-benjamin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/benny-benjamin/</guid>
      <description>Where did the Funk Brothers name come from? In the Standing in the Shadows of Motown documentary, Joe Hunter stated that the name &amp;ldquo;The Funk Brothers&amp;rdquo; came from Benny Benjamin.
How many of the Funk Brothers are still living? While Motown recordings utilized many musicians, the film focused on 13 players, of whom five were already dead. Just four Funk Brothers are alive now. Jones is survived by his wife, June, and three children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the singer for Bad Brains?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-hudson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/earl-hudson/</guid>
      <description>What happened to the lead singer of Bad Brains? Singer Chuck Mosley, who had played with Bad Brains in the early 1990s, died in November 2017. Sid McCray died in September 2020.
Who inspired Bad Brains? Bad Brains formed in Washington in the late &amp;rsquo;70s, first as Mind Power, a jazz fusion group inspired by Chick Corea and Mahavishnu Orchestra, but eventually changed its name and vision after discovering the Sex Pistols and the Damned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did ACDC fire Phil Rudd?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-rudd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-rudd/</guid>
      <description>Is ACDC drummer good? In my humble opinion, Phil Rudd was the foundation of the AC/DC, always consistent, always on time, and always holding it down. His timing and precision are impeccable and if you ask me, He&amp;rsquo;s one of the best drummers… in the world!
Who was the bald drummer for ACDC? Chris Slade
Why did AC DC have so many drummers? During the 2015-2016 Rock or Bust tour, three different members of AC/DC were taken out of action by serious medical problems (Malcolm Young, Brian Johnson) and legal issues (Phil Rudd, arguably self-inflicted) over the past couple of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Bill Bruford quit drumming?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-bruford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/bill-bruford/</guid>
      <description>Why did Bill Bruford leave Genesis? Later in 1978, Bruford reunited with John Wetton and formed the progressive rock group U.K. After their debut album U.K. (1978) and several tours, Holdsworth and Bruford left the group due to disagreements on the group&amp;rsquo;s musical direction.
When did Bill Bruford leave Genesis? July 19, 1972
When was Bill Bruford in King Crimson? Bruford played in King Crimson for his third and final tenure from 1994–1997, after which he continued with a new acoustic configuration of Earthworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did David Garibaldi leave Tower of Power?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-garibaldi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-garibaldi/</guid>
      <description>Why did David Garibaldi leave Tower of Power? After ten years with Tower, in 1980 Garibaldi felt it was time to move on and left the San Francisco Bay Area for Los Angeles, with the hopes of building a career in the studios.
Who is the lead singer of Tower of Power today? For the past few years, Marcus Scott has been making a name for himself as the lead singer of the legendary band Tower of Power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Ian Paice leave Whitesnake?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ian-paice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ian-paice/</guid>
      <description>Why did Richie Blackmore leave Deep Purple? Blackmore&amp;rsquo;s marriage had broken down and he was going through the process of a messy divorce. He would later sum up his input on the album as, “There wasn&amp;rsquo;t as much guitar because in a way I was going through more personal problems, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the people there that I wanted to record with.
Who did Tommy Bolin replace in Deep Purple?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Janet Weiss leave Sleater?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/janet-weiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/janet-weiss/</guid>
      <description>When did Janet Weiss leave Sleater-Kinney? Ultimately, Weiss decided the shift in her role signaled it was “time for me to move on,” as Weiss tweeted in July 2019 after announcing her split from the group.Nov 20, 2019
Is Sleater-Kinney still together? Sleater-Kinney Releases A Last Album, Ending An Era For the Indie Rock Trio : NPR. Sleater-Kinney Releases A Last Album, Ending An Era For the Indie Rock Trio Sleater-Kinney&amp;rsquo;s longtime drummer is leaving the band — but not before they release one last album together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Lombardo leave Slayer?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-lombardo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/dave-lombardo/</guid>
      <description>Is Dave Lombardo one of the best drummers? The innovator of thrash drumming has been beating drum kits into submission for 40 years. Having sat atop the drum throne for Slayer, Fantomas, Dead Cross and many others, Lombardo is always in the conversation for the best drummer on earth. Lombardo&amp;rsquo;s drumming the most consistent aspect of Slayer&amp;rsquo;s legendary career.May 6, 2019
What is the band Slayers net worth? 11- Slayer And the members have retired in 2018, after making their final world tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Mick Avory leave the Rolling Stones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-avory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mick-avory/</guid>
      <description>Who is considered the greatest rock drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.Sep 14, 2021
Who is the goat of drumming? Neil Peart, Rush – The G.O.A.T.Sep 10, 2015 Why did Mick Taylor quit Rolling Stones? Taylor admitted in the documentary Crossfire Hurricane that he had become addicted to heroin while living in the eye of the Rolling Stones maelstrom and decided to leave to try to protect his family from the band&amp;rsquo;s caustic lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Mick Avory leave the Rolling Stones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/micky-waller/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/micky-waller/</guid>
      <description>Who is considered the greatest rock drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.Sep 14, 2021
Who is the goat of drumming? Neil Peart, Rush – The G.O.A.T.Sep 10, 2015 Why did Mick Taylor quit Rolling Stones? Taylor admitted in the documentary Crossfire Hurricane that he had become addicted to heroin while living in the eye of the Rolling Stones maelstrom and decided to leave to try to protect his family from the band&amp;rsquo;s caustic lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Phil Collins go deaf?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-collins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/phil-collins/</guid>
      <description>What vocal effect does Phil Collins use? Sounds about right. the AMS 1580 dual delay harmoniser is what is used on phil collins vocal along with a Lexicon reverb probably a 300.Feb 15, 2008
Who are Phil Collins 5 children? His five children, Joely, Simon, Lily, Nicholas and Matthew, are equally as talented and have started to take over Hollywood. When he was just 5 years old, Phil had already begun to play the drums and set his sights on making it into the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Scotty Moore stop playing with Elvis?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/d-j-fontana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/d-j-fontana/</guid>
      <description>Who performed Jailhouse Rock? Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s
What happened to Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s band after he died? Tours with other musicians: After the TCB Band disbanded Before Presley&amp;rsquo;s death in 1977, several former members from the TCB Band went on to form Emmylou Harris&amp;rsquo;s Hot Band and The John Denver Band. These musicians include James Burton, Glen D.
Who was Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s first drummer? Dominic Joseph Fontana
Who was the drummer Jailhouse Rock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did the Grateful Dead have two drummers?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mickey-hart-and-bill-kreutzmann/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/mickey-hart-and-bill-kreutzmann/</guid>
      <description>When did the Grateful Dead have two drummers? 1967- 68. Toward the end of 1967, the Dead were rapidly developing their reputation as a mind-blowing live act. To expand their sound, they brought in Mickey Hart on drums and percussion. The addition of a second drummer gave the band a distinct power, not only in live performances but in the studio too.Nov 12, 2014
What is the point of two drummers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Tommy quit the Ramones?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-ramone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/tommy-ramone/</guid>
      <description>What made the Ramones great? Ramones was the first so-called punk album. It made us think: “We&amp;rsquo;d better crack on here.” But the Ramones and the Pistols were different animals, with a different flavour. They were more basic, three-chord rock&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;roll. Great songs, really catchy, all two and a half minutes long.Feb 2, 2016
Did the Ramones do drugs? He had used hard drugs since he was a child, had been diagnosed as bipolar, and often mixed mood-disorder medications with cocaine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Elvin Jones is important?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/elvin-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/elvin-jones/</guid>
      <description>Why did Elvin Jones leave Coltrane? But in 1966, Jones left Coltrane&amp;rsquo;s group after Coltrane decided to add a second drummer, a decision Jones felt was inconsistent with his own musical direction. Coltrane died the next year. Jones went to Europe, played with Duke Ellington&amp;rsquo;s band for a couple of weeks and returned to the United States.May 20, 2004
When did McCoy Tyner leave Coltrane? 1965
Why Elvin Jones is important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is John Stanier cymbal so high?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/glenn-kotche/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/glenn-kotche/</guid>
      <description>Why is John Stanier&amp;rsquo;s cymbal so high? John: I didn&amp;rsquo;t want any cymbals but the hi-hats at first. Then I was like, “Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll use one,” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want it near me because I&amp;rsquo;d use it too much. So I set it high so I&amp;rsquo;d have to work to get to it. I wanted it to be significant; I use it as a marker.
Why did Helmet break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is John Stanier cymbal so high?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-stanier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/john-stanier/</guid>
      <description>Why is John Stanier&amp;rsquo;s cymbal so high? John: I didn&amp;rsquo;t want any cymbals but the hi-hats at first. Then I was like, “Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll use one,” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want it near me because I&amp;rsquo;d use it too much. So I set it high so I&amp;rsquo;d have to work to get to it. I wanted it to be significant; I use it as a marker.
Why did Helmet break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is John Stanier cymbal so high?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ronald-shannon-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/ronald-shannon-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Why is John Stanier&amp;rsquo;s cymbal so high? John: I didn&amp;rsquo;t want any cymbals but the hi-hats at first. Then I was like, “Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll use one,” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want it near me because I&amp;rsquo;d use it too much. So I set it high so I&amp;rsquo;d have to work to get to it. I wanted it to be significant; I use it as a marker.
Why did Helmet break up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Steve Gadd so good?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-gadd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/steve-gadd/</guid>
      <description>Who played drums on Frosty the Snowman? Description: This holiday classic is always a favorite of young people, and Mike Lewis&amp;rsquo; swinging jazz chart is ideal for the younger band. Mike has come up with some clever ideas for this one, yet this chart will require only minimal rehearsal time.
Who plays drums with Paul Simon? Steve Gadd is the longest band member in Paul Simons group, starting to play with him in 1975.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why was Buddy Rich dishonorably discharged?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buddy-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/buddy-rich/</guid>
      <description>Is Buddy Rich the greatest drummer of all time? Buddy Rich has been called the greatest jazz drummer of all time—a statement that few would argue with. Buddy was born on September 30, 1917, and his drumming career spanned seven decades, beginning when he was just eighteen months old and continuing until his death on April 2, 1987.
Who is considered the greatest drummer of all time? 1: John Bonham Easily topping our list of the best drummers of all time, John “Bonzo” Bonham was the rhythmic powerhouse behind hard-rock legends Led Zeppelin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why was Carlton Barrett shot?</title>
      <link>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carlton-barrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://musicantfamilybrain.info/post/carlton-barrett/</guid>
      <description>What was Carlton Barrett contribution to reggae music? Carlton Barrett is featured on all the albums recorded by the Wailers. Barrett popularised the one drop rhythm, a percussive drumming style created by Winston Grennan. With Carly&amp;rsquo;s beats and his brother Aston&amp;rsquo;s bass, the Wailer rhythm section planted the seeds of today&amp;rsquo;s international reggae.
Why was Carlton Barrett shot? Carlton Barrett, 35, drummer in the band led by the late Bob Marley, was shot dead at the gate to his home in 1987.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
